They said he'd disappear.
Another voice swallowed by the algorithm.
Another ghost in the machine.
But they forgot something.
Some men don't enter the room to be seen.
The enter changed the temperature.
She never moved before the game beat.
Oh, we're static in his plans.
He don't chase the spotlight.
Conspiracy astronaut.
Forgot he listens to everybody reveal who says the least most nix nixing a ritual is a 333 digital priest is starting the
Frequency studies human nature like a hacker read an enemy data possible to provide a refusal kill hesitation
Slowly let strategy take form because calm becomes when it survives in the static path
Before I knew them, I was already inside the flame
In the shadows while they used my name
Every panel like a ritual, every stranger like a sub-initiation
Every fracture turned divine, islands between whilst within
They said don't look too deeply, they said don't ask why
But the golden thread was humming
And's reading tension in the crowd, dumb on the golden
They want it blood and spectacle, want it collapse and shame
People brought me all their storms, heartbreak, secrets, fear, and grief
And somehow I became a strange relief
Late night messages like angels, unexpected hands
Would rise invisible, protection moving right
Every time I almost vanished
Every time the darkness spoke
Something ancient moved within me
Kelly burned alive, opened up the box of death
Get into the stream, Mbersitz.
Um, so, like, I guess, I think it was this woman,
the woman that had sex with a dog.
I think it was her that did it,
because she got mad at me one night.
Remember the thing that is,
that she got mad at me one night?
You were arguing and stuff, and I, and, uh,
but then, oh shit, the next day, like,
it was like, everyone was hitting,
like Mason was just hitting just now.
I mean, it's like, I was like, oh my God,
there's like 200 people hitting and stuff.
Yeah, so I think it was her.
Oh, her name is Jen or something like that.
Well, I mean, I mean, it's like, I don't know what happened.
But unfortunately, I had her in a mod still,
because she turned on me.
And, you know, I mean, I don't know really
what's the history about some of this stuff.
I just like, no, I don't know.
I don't really judge about like certain things.
I mean, it's like, but I don't know.
Yeah.
But yeah, the thing that is was hidden.
A lot of people were. I mean, I was like, at least like, I just unhid like 25 people, but I'm going to look again right now.
We'll tell you who I see on the list. Do you tell me if I need to unhide somebody?
Hi. Hi, Lola. How are we doing this morning? Let me see. Okay, so, um, there's my studio.
Hi, babe. Hi. Okay, here I am. Okay. So, if I go into my settings. Oh, baby.
You know, she's um, but kind of ties here and she's all gets all crazy. Okay
Okay. All right, babe. Okay
So
Who do we have on the list? Oh my god, a hundred. There's like hundreds of people on this list. It's crazy
Okay
Nostalgic Joseph Wayland hoppin exiled one dog
Kish unrelatable
Claire
The n-word Nathan year. See I don't even know like some of these are trolls and some of them aren't
Deviant lemon. I don't like the sound of that
Armin muse. It's okay. They're the Dingleberry fresh person
Bronwyn's home cookies. That doesn't sound some good me. We I see things
Samantha Avery, she's fine
Tobias funk
Uno lover
Jim J. Harrow, I don't like him, okay.
G-hand, dental enthusiast, Shmeli.
I don't really care about Shmeli, I don't think.
Not Hector V, I don't think I care about him.
Cryptic Blue, they're okay.
I don't like that Uter person.
Viva La Tera, no, not Terry Davis, it's terrible.
Grappler Six, that's the guy I wanted to wrestle with.
Exile One's fine on there.
Who's Mike Halal, I don't know.
Two more chance. Someone named Jesus. Okay, I'll unkind bake clips. I mean, geez.
Not BG. Psyche loves cherds. BBL Rufi. Jews Hall. Nora Billy Swallows. Sassy Scarlet. Pillow
Biter. Damien Hammer. Only one way. Heavyweight. Katrina. Katrina with his. Oh my god. George
So anybody that practically would come catfish crystalline
George Copeland be cash
Hebrew hammer
Long dong silver
Oh God, oh man. Oh, no, I bought a punch. He was hidden. Oh my gosh
Did some of these people cause problems? I forgot J1 is hidden. I don't think he's a problem
left-wing nut
The troll troller. I think I like the troll troller
Um, Chris Ferries, I don't know about that, George Wallace, the YouTube low battery, um,
Joe Shipley was hidden, oh my god, um, Fama Lam, 19th stage, like who has enough time
to like go into somebody's like fucking old chat and like hide people, loser, Noble Castro
Dr. Rabbit, I don't like the sound of that. Okay, it's real YouTube investigations. You might like the sound of that
Okay freckles
Think they're fine. I don't know
Record where your eyes can see enter the dragon deepsie
Daddy Docs. Oh, yeah, okay. Cx raider. I have for a night. I like that sound of half for a night later
Where are they hidden? Okay, um, Ilya of Obam opposite in LadyBath3. That's fine
Dilly Gooth, okay. Yes, Mino is hidden. I can't believe that red balloon. I mean, are they okay? I don't know
Vix sins. I'm hiding untrackable was hidden. He believes us untrackable
strawberry shortcake
Wings 007 center triple X
sunglass kid streets
By goalie Bateman
I'm the prize gay and we're from outer space
Lava Lava's a friend of mine
Spanky. Oh, yes, I thought it was spunky person very blue. I think it's fine
Lovely rain. Is that rain? I don't know
Give her a chance. Okay. I'm the prize
Okay, we'll see about that. Okay dubs. I mean how many people that does person to hide? I mean, it's hundreds
Veronica K. I mean, I don't even know Tay Tay. I think Tay Tay is fine
2020 is hidden. Oh my god
I don't know. Oh, that's the wrong one. Okay. Discount. I don't want discount in my chat JVD
Hi there, Nicole with the HLE. Okay. The fatty guy cult of psychos. I don't like the scent of that
Maddie, I think Maddie is okay
Homeless man NYC. I don't like that. J-Dog was hidden for some reason. Okay. Callie blue
Ricky bones
Oscar W, Grease Pitt, I mean some of these names is that some of these people
need to go to a mental institution. I mean what is with these names? Paul
Shepard, is that that weird guy? Okay, Cookie Y1 Shasta Baby, Patrick New York was
hit in? My god, droopy face. So you know and then I think I hit them and they're
mad at me right and it's like I didn't even do anything.
Not nags, I mean it's like, but some of these people are rude and stuff, like most of them are actually been rude to me and stuff, but Brandon Mitchell, I mean I don't know, Axe is fine, I mean I don't know, can Mods just keep an eye on the chat if someone gets out of hand, because it's like there's so many people I don't hide right now, Sadie Starseed, I mean some of these people are just so nice, they probably just think I'm a dick, okay.
Press check. I don't know. Okay. I'm just gonna I'm just gonna press Vanguard is hidden. Oh my god
But it's like it's and it's like so many people I want to unhide everybody
But then it's like 45 of them are like are like one of the sages alternates
They're in like 20 of them are like Tony's. So it's like it's like a whack a whack a mole, you know
There's an immature Katrina was hidden sassy. No, you weren't hidden but because you're a mod
I think that I think if you're a mod you can't get hidden
But a lot of people probably don't come here because they're probably like, oh my god
I can't even talk and he's playing the stupid music and love it and it's like right. I mean it's just like
Very immature
That's that noise. Oh, it's my other phone. I think
Anyway, I need I need to make a dollar today so I can like suck and borrow another $20 from cash
So if anyone can catch that me I really appreciate it. I mean I could do a reading for anybody
I'm going to say, oh my god, he's grouping.
I'm not just kidding.
It's called survival mode sometimes, you know?
But I'm going to do it.
I hope they'll do OK.
But I do need to at least make a dollar, though.
I'll put my banner up.
Oh, I don't have it written yet.
Hold on.
Create a banner.
Oh, can I just put it under my name?
I don't know.
Oh, is it like this one?
How do you put something under your name?
Make my name like real big. Oh my god. I made everything pink. I feel like that one kind of but I need to think the oh
Show headlight. There you go. And then they can put something under it. Oh, yeah, so there's it. There it is
It should be up there now. You see it. Hold on. I'll get this off. Here you go
Hold on. I think that is as long as there. I'm not frozen. I'm just like I just I just fucking I just freeze
It's actually freezing in here. It's cold
Hi Lola. Oh Lola. Lola has the top of her mouth is black. It's like it's skin is black. I mean
it's like naturally kind of weird. Here now that everyone's back and you know well all of a sudden
everyone get in here now so let me see. I want to show you something. Oh there's poor Casey. I see
I'm not going to show the picture because I don't remember. Disrespect the dead but
Rest in peace. Okay, um, let's see what I got
It's hot
Welcome to the carnival of influence
Every mirror lies
Every smile has teeth every deal has strings
But tonight the cult of psyche pulls back the curtain
And the target in red, everything collapse and blame that one instead.
Crowd stars can't and nobody wants truth.
When blame them pain, then they choose your memory.
Soft hands in your mind, that's not how it happened.
Now you're certainty on why.
For consistency, you remember, you doubt yourself, and it's invisible through.
Once they plant this symbol, pain.
But your focus got trained and comes.
Bro, isolation wrapped in l-
Yo, cut you from your people, break you down, and how to live your own life.
Finally see, what I survive.
Awareness, and once the lantern is lit.
I don't know, he hasn't been around much.
I caught him in that bodybuilder that I like, Chad.
And I was like, Ghost, what are you doing here?
And he was like talking to the bodybuilder.
Like, kind of, it's kind of almost something
a little bit of trouble.
The guy's name is God Body Ray.
I don't know if you, I think a few people
went and visited him.
But be nice.
I mean, he's a weird guy, but he's, I mean,
he's a nice guy.
He's a really, he's really cool actually.
I ever, ever, he's like, he's like a,
he's like a modern day caveman.
Like he's just anything and he took off his beanie and he's completely thing that is his bald is you
He's like 30 years old and he's like he's like completely like he looks like dr. Phil
I mean, it's like it's so crazy, but I was like, okay. I'm attracted to the bald guys now because it's like
Because it looks like he has hair like we were the beanie and he's like real and he looks like Justin Bieber or something like that
And then he takes off his beanie, God body reigns.
I don't know if you see my friend.
And then, oh my gosh, now Les says he knows him and stuff.
Yeah, Rudy's been like, he has a cold, I think,
because he's like sneezing and stuff.
He goes, yeah, he sneezes a little bit.
But yeah, but he's like very up cuddly and stuff.
Rudy's a sweetheart.
Okay, okay, Lola, do you want me to do a massage?
So I don't know but I can eat I get if I could like I could eat all week actually actually okay
So I don't think any
Alex McQueen is gone. Okay. Yeah, I don't think he's coming back
There's quite a few people that are gone. I should say
Just say I probably will be losing a little bit of weight
but I
Know this can I can handle him yelling at ghosts like our calling goes to PDF. I just kind of take it. I had to like
I'm mad, I'm kicking him out of the chat for that.
Just cause it's like, I know,
it's just like, just the worst thing you can say.
And he, just cause he gets a little crazy sometimes.
Both, but they both do, but Alex really goes crazy.
But it's like, I mean, Alexander, like, come on.
I mean, it's just like, either 90 K months,
or like, he owns the place and shakes things.
I don't know, I love, I love them, but.
I mean, I wouldn't I don't I'm not even mad at him really but you know, it's like he's he went too far doing that
You know, like especially to ghost ghost is like such a harmless
Soul, you know
Ghost is a harmless soul. He's like a he's like a
It's like a human teddy bear and like the best way I can say
So, oh, he's like a he's like a he's like a human teddy Ruxpin doll. How could you be not not my ghost?
You're opening the same hush that
i saw the moon split open like a wound across the night silver angels hanging back was with
their halos burning white cathedrals made of televisions chanting through the fog
your face distorted underneath the voice of god something waits forever on the other side of
consciousness daniel the static three thousand signals we've decoded signal survive the signal
Do you like that song? Oh
No, you're just having a weather. Okay. Well
Anything I can just
Let me know to say I mean, there's a lot going on it's like
YouTube's been an interesting experience
But at some point you get to the point where it's like is this is this a more of a positive?
experience for me or is it more of a negative? Is this doing me good? It's like kind of comes down to you and it's like and it's
Oh, whatever position I'm in. It's like it's my fault. You know, it's like
Because we allow people to treat us
How we are really to be treated like how people treat us, right? And it's like so I've made big mistakes in that way like by
Trusting the wrong people whatever. Oh my god, and so I mean you see and it's just like this assist these dorks
I mean, it's like I'm not even gonna look at the name or read the comment. It's sick
Smell them a mile away, but I wish um
you know
It's like anybody that's not here is like I'm glad they're not here pretty much. It's like like I
Don't I'm not really about the numbers. I think I like having in just a few people to talk to I can't really pay attention to more than a few
people I get really distracted and
Yeah, I mean, it's like I don't want to give up. It's hard, but it's hard not to when it's like, you know
It's like I'm just getting to the point where I'm like hungry
It's like I feel like I'm kind of being starved in a certain way, but it's like my but it's my fault. It's my fault, but I'm
I'll still like
Do what I want to do because I'm very like independent, right? You you know that I can go get love on tiktok
I mean, it's like but then it's like kind of like too easy almost there
I guess I'm always the kind of person that like once the fight for love or something like that
And so I like place stayed here longer than I should have and
Yeah, it's just a disaster
like just like
Yeah, I went I saw a sweep he has it as a channel called the psyche haters club channel
It has more subscribers than my channel and there were 5,000 subscribers
I'm just kidding. It really doesn't has like but it has it still has a lot of subscribers for just a hate channel of me
Has it has 250 subscribers. I was shocking. I mean it was like a lot
Yet to 250 subscribers you're not done. I would not 5,000
That would be really, that'd be really bad, right?
I mean that would be, that I would just like
pack it up at that point if she had a bigger channel.
But it's like, still she shouldn't have that big of a channel
just based on my clips.
I mean, it's like, maybe that's maybe
saying that I'm popular, I don't know.
I don't know, but she's like, you know,
she's like posting all this crap about,
ugh, I don't know, people are so gross.
I don't even like to listen to shows anymore
Who will make up I can't but I can't take all the like the PDF talk like all the time
It's like everybody think they're obsessed with it. It's like it's not even that it's like
It goes like it goes along with big the
Jokes and these jokes are sick and then it's like and then it could get these sick news stories, and then it's like I
Don't even believe most of it, and it's like but it's pretty things in people's minds that are like making them weird
I don't know. I really do think that
Like it's like like it's like being pushed on the culture or something or some kind of weird thing and
It's like or some people figured out. Oh, this is a way to like they think that they're a superhero or something
They're literally they do. I mean, it's like or like a spy. I mean, it's like maybe some people are and something like that
I mean, it's like I'm so funny while we glamorize
But that's kind of kind of gets the movies because the stupid movies like James Bond and like oh, it's like so great to be a
You know, they say a snoopy person is just an excuse for people to go through full spoons and stuff
and
You know
Peaking into people's windows into binoculars. I mean it's like I used to be called, you know, like
Peeping Tom's now now. It's just like everybody. It's like what wait
Yeah
You're the positive reinforcement.
Yeah, you're the only one to hear.
It's like, I just kick out the negative people now.
So it's like, but yeah, you guys are here.
I appreciate that.
Thank God, they, oh my gosh.
See, it's the same person over and over.
It's just like, it's just him.
Who, but basically also he got in trouble
for cyber stalking.
Any regrets?
Regrets, I had a few.
Hey, Brandon, what's up?
Good to see you.
Do I have regrets?
You know, I don't really like have regrets because it's like at the end of the day
I'll do what I want to do. My only regret is like is like, you know
Listening to other people for too long or something like that or like, you know, be too nice
I guess it's been like, but I don't regret that. No, because it's just part of my personality
Benjamin's a punk we in glory whole owns them. Yeah, I mean I say I know all those guys
It's like they could just like fucking go live on a farm for all I care
I mean, it's just like these are just like the music
It's like the scum of the earth. I did they're they're just they're just as bad as their low cows
Like they really are thinking it's so funny low cow is such a projection of low cows
It's like that we're gonna say people that are just like calling it all these oh, I'm gonna be a local
I'm gonna be a farmer this person gonna be my look
It's like some of these people look like actual cows.
I mean, they look like human cows
and they're trying to call me a cow.
I'm me, this gorgeous person, you know?
I'm this hot guy, I can't even see me, I'm this hot guy.
Oh yeah, something asshole British guy came on last night
and he's like, oh, so what kind of gay guy are you?
And I was like, what kind of gay,
like if we were talking about bears and twinks
and stuff like that, you, oh, you found Benji's sister.
Hey, Brandon, do you know that,
That girl Jen just Jen. She like I think she hid everybody in my chat like a lot of people. It's crazy
You found Benji Benji from Howard sir. Oh, no, oh, oh Benji from
from William Glory hold I watched that we Christopher is zazel sometimes and it's like but
But basically like Syrax is like a horror movie to me like he's like so scary looking
I mean he's like a monster. He's like a literal like real monster like a real life and then I get compared to him
Benji. Oh, I got you. I got you. Oh
Okay, well, maybe he'll shut up about like fucking bothering people. I mean, it's like I mean, it's like does it have to I mean, it's like
Geez. Oh
No, I you know why I'm doing this because I am I just started going live on this one
And so I just was like, you know, letting people know guys you can come on to my main channel. Let's go close it out
I'm on a cake too right now too. Hi. Hi Karen. How are you?
Let me see, yeah, I'll just close this one out here.
Just so people know I'm back on this regular channel
because I had like, I waited for,
I waited for something to clear up.
Not at CD, it was a strike, you know.
So, but now I'm all good.
It's like, I can't believe the channel's still here.
It got so close sometimes.
I kind of take it down four times,
but it's still, it's like,
I can make it as many as I want, actually.
It's just, and you know what?
And there's a million people out there
that want to watch me.
There's a million people that want to watch you.
There's a million people that will, like, well, like any,
well, I mean, it's like, everyone has people
that will be like, well, like them.
There's eight billion people in the world.
So you're, yeah, I'm sorry, Brandon, that sucks, but,
you know, yeah, like, yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I just see pictures of Jen
with that horse bridal in her mouth.
That's a little intense, but I don't know I don't I don't know about the dog
I mean, I don't I mean, it's like I guess it didn't happen. I don't I think that's really wrong
But then I mean it's like
There are women that like like, you know, I don't know I'm home and say
Oh, I know that all say is that um, what's the best stroke off got a got a rim job for me
From some girls dog before so I say and you know, I know people did say
That's disgusting and stuff, but I thought it was kind of funny a little bit, but um, yeah, and then what else happened?
Oh, yeah. Well, I once saw this, you're going to, I saw this, this woman in Florida, she had like a, she had a pit bull and she, this woman put peanut butter in her vagina and let the pit bull eat it out of her vagina and stuff.
Only in Florida, right? And then there was another story about in Florida where, oh, it just wasn't good. I mean, there's, there's just like a lot of weird discussing news in Florida.
Hey, Paige, what's up? How are we going to see you?
So it is freezing here. I'm just like
Trying to try to make a dollar. So if anyone's are reading I get a dollar. I'll be able to borrow $20
From the bank. So then I'll get me
real a little bit
It's like now I'm not I'll just be shameless about it because it's like well, they should mean they mean
Like that way I got taken down. I don't know what they think they mean they shouldn't some of that stuff
It should be evidence. Oh my god. I like I'm Alexander played the other day of
gamble
It's um, it's a cult of psyche
Thank you so much. Yeah, I think I appreciate and I'll give you a reading too, but gamble was like I'm
swatting you and like on the air and stuff and
And then he said he was gonna like he's like he's like, oh
And we're going to, oh, we're going to swat Elisa Tordon
and next week, right?
When Andy Dick is there, and he's like,
and they're saying like on the phone, he's like,
oh yeah, I've got guns and I've got pipe bombs
and I'm aiming the gun at the door,
come like, and they're crying at the police
to like come with like your guns.
This is like, can kill somebody.
I mean, it's just like so scary.
And it's like, and then it's like a joke to them.
And it's like, they're just like laughing in there.
And it's just like, it's like the sickest kind of bullying
I've ever seen, like really.
Yeah, oh wow
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean it's like that. I mean this stuff is unimaginable to me like
Like I guess I mean it's like it's so crazy that it happens and it's like
Basically, but I think it's a lot of other countries and stuff, but yeah, it's like it's crazy. Yeah, and other countries
It's more common actually. I remember there was even this cup couple
I think they were Middle Eastern couple in New York and they had a slave and in there in their house in New York
Yeah, I
Know it's like and I think people like Brian
I don't know like I think that somebody like went in her chat pretending to be you or something like that
Or maybe there's missing it, but I know she was like, you know
You know
She's a I mean, I wish I had her fighting spirit like really like where I mean, it's like
it's like, you know, I'm like kind of like I
kind of like well like
I'm more peace and stuff like that, but
You know, sometimes it's too passive on my part, right?
Constantly psychological warfare showing, oh, yeah.
Well, I mean, it's like, yeah.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's like,
nobody even knows who she is.
I mean, it's like, if he, like, I don't know.
Like, he's, and he's got this like, really gay.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm gay, right?
So I don't think anything's wrong with being gay,
but it's like, he's like,
He's like Richard Simmons level almost like the way he he sounds like it's like really I was like whoa
Like he's one of those really really gay guys, but then it's like there's like oh, he's not gay
He has a like a wife or fiance. I was like, okay
Well, who knows what else? What else he's doing? I don't know. It's like but it's like a weird shit
like and then he has like it's just like these groups of people and then everyone's like
Kind of like just like listening to what he says. He's like he has an online girlfriend. He's never met yet
I think like some people like I mean, that's safe to get like an online
Like boyfriend or girlfriend because it's like that's like like remember these say long because they call my long-distance relationships
And they never would work. I mean, they're kind of a joke, right? But it's like
Kind of like I mean the only long-distance relationships are gonna be there's a couple that are already married
And then like the guy goes on the road for a lot part of the year or something
Or like a trucker or something
Whereas like this kind of like just like that. It's like their
Routine or something. It's like it's not gonna really work for any a normal
relationship
Usually, I don't know and then it's like then what then you know, you're gonna have a e-sex and then it's like someone's gonna tape you
Have the e-sex and then I mean it's like
I mean it's like people are just like so so weird these days like it was like they're like there's nothing like
Nothing is sacred anymore. You can't even like see a butthole without like fucking a world incident, right?
He never met her and now I mean it's like it's crazy
See, I haven't really I mean I haven't I I mean I think last year I said I had the gun
I was just I just pretend I think I don't I don't even like these guys. Oh, yeah
So this weird British guy was like he was saying oh
So what kind of gay guy are you and I was like again a gay guy?
I was like well because you're talking about bears and twinks and stuff and I was like
I was like, I don't know I was like, I'm not really like I'm not I'm not even like really part of a subculture
And he's like, oh, are you are you the tramp kind of gay?
I was like the Trump gay. He's like, no the Trump. I was like, oh, I thought he meant like a Republican. I was like, no
oh
Trump I was like
I don't like I know that I've never heard that term in my life and I'm you know, I'm gay
I wish and I've also have a British brother-in-law. I think I would have heard that term
But no, it tries like isn't a tramp like a homeless person. It's like, oh, yeah
He's like you look like one with those wisps of your hair
Like my my wispy hair. I mean, it's like I mean Donald Trump gets wispy hair. I mean, it's like, well, why am I a tramp?
And it's not even this it's like there's no there's not even nice. It's not even it's not nice to say to a woman or a man
It's like it's just a bad word. It's like unless it's like you're on it like a
Going to a tram or something like that
Like I try I don't know. Is there lady in the tramp is like the nicest thing I can say, you know, I don't know
It's crazy
But uh, yeah, so hope everyone's having a nice day like I don't know it's it's a
But I have been able to like do a lot of like work and stuff, which is really really cool
Like on my on the website and stuff and that's going good
Okay
Yeah, so if anyone wants to like a reading I'll put my make a banner actually
Everything's appreciated right now because I got unmonitized last month
And then it's like then they don't want to pay paid people and then it's like then then they want to fucking
I don't know. And then there's these boycotts on me and it's like, oh, don't and people everyone thinks they know so much
And they don't like they don't know shit about
Anything that's going on. I mean, it's like well some people do like but it's like most people don't and they just take a sumo lot of things
And they and they lie and shit
But they all do five dollar readings or five dollar
I'll even I'll sell some clap tokens too. Oh, I don't know if anyone wants to also I'll give them play like
I'll do like three for the next three clap tokens will be
$10 or 24 hours
And that's all those do three
Sometimes you have to be like creative
You know and also, I mean easy came in when I was like I'll stand on my head
And there's the cash
Oh my god, I don't know why I'm with it that big, hold on.
It's so humongous.
Okay, scroll across the bottom.
First of all, that's the banner, right?
Okay, there we go.
There, oh, it's not scrolling.
Edit, what did I do wrong?
I hate this.
Oh, it must be like this stupid, oh, it's this stupid thing.
I'll figure it out eventually.
Not working, but scroll across the bottom, speed fast.
Scroll. I don't know. It's like not scrolling. It's just like a stick coming up on the screen. I don't know. I'm so sorry.
I don't fucking know. Oh, no, I'll do it later. Slow.
Ad banner.
It's not scrolling across the ticker like it says it should be doing. Oh, this movie is like a show?
I think probably the wrong style or something. I don't know. I'm so sorry.
Oh, that's weird. Okay.
Transform overlays
Okay, I'm sorry guys. Hey 50. Why are there 50 people in the chat? Why are there 50 people in here? What's going on?
What's going on? Are you guys someone pulling my leg someone's pulling my leg here? Okay. Well, welcome everybody to the show
Welcome
I'm your host
psyche
Wow 50 people. Okay, that kind of that brought me smiles my face. Thank you. Appreciate that
Well anyone would like to to uh, I'll do I'll do a click to reading too, but I think in a second
Oh, yeah, I have like I have a couple backup channels too. I've cult of psyches nightmares and then I have cult codex channel
Um
Oh, it's almost time to get a copy. Oh my god. Okay. That sounds good. Okay. I can't have food at least
Coffee is good for like the uh appetite
Okay, here you go. This one's pretty good
Thank you for being here guys 50 people. Oh look at the chat in a second. Here we go. Okay. There we go. It's slow
I like the moon behind me. It's pretty cool
There we go
Oh, it doesn't like the moon. It's pretty cool crazy late night transmissions from somewhere beneath the
Broken frequency is nixing switch wolves in the stage things grow while psyche studies every face like a movie feel like
Yeah, it's a psyche awakens. Oh, sorry. Sorry. It's cult of psyche. I changed the cults of psyche
Thank you, and I'll meet with my thing
It's under my name right there. I was trying to do the banner, but I'm problems
See it's like roll across
Speed I mean, I can do but um, I'd really appreciate it. I mean, yeah
Let me see. Do you like this song though?
Oh, yeah. Well, RG, you are dumb.
Oh, I know. I fucking, I'm sorry, fuck. I need to change that.
I'm gonna do it right now. Shit.
Nightbot's the wrong one.
And RG, you tried to pornbomb me. That was like so lame of you.
Why would you do that? That was always so nice to you.
You tried to pornbomb me? You didn't even succeed.
Okay. Thank you for reminding me.
Okay, I'm gonna fix my, I'm gonna fix my Nightbot right now.
Think a lot of stuff is kind of back on that. I'm sorry. I'm sorry today. It wasn't looking at my chat like shit
Okay, yeah, cuz I rebranded a little bit. Okay
their cash up is
cult of psyche
Fixed my backup channel is kick. That's right. Okay
dude, dude, dude, I'll say a butthole and buttplugger are also a
Also, nightbot commands, okay.
I need to fix a couple of these cash-up ones.
Okay.
Hey, maybe I'll get a sandwich today.
Okay, I'll get a good, that'll be good, I won't.
I'll get a bagel sandwich.
Okay.
There, there, this one changed to Psyche's Nightmares.
Nobody really like, does the nightbot anymore,
but they are set.
I used to have, you know, who did them,
was He-Man would do them?
Crazy. Oh, he met with one of the people that we're hitting too.
Did that. And I'm sorry, because my website went down and so I'm trying to get that back up.
And so I was a little bit distracted. Okay. Okay, we got that one. You fix the discord.
Okay, fix that. Okay. Because, oh my god, it's so great, but the website is growing so big.
That uh, it's like now they're trying to charge me for other stuff and Google like a bunch of money too. Oh, thank you so much
Thank you so much. I appreciate that
First thing that thank you so much
That will help me a lot right now because now I'll be able to get some food
Because I can borrow money from cash up cash up has this thing where it's like you can borrow money
Then you pay it back and then it's like
It's crazy, but I only have like a dollar
Yeah, and we'll go do it. We'll do some IRL. Thank you so much dude. So how was everyone's weekend?
Was there anybody to do anything? We had like this festival here like this week. It was like Sugar Ray was then here
I think the offspring was
Like and they have it every year, but it's like a bunch of boot. It's like very like
Very like blonde. People come from all over to see it and the town gets really busy and stuff
But I don't know. There's like not too much for me to do around here
Even though it is LA it's like I still I need to fix my bicycle. I might eat my bike and then I'll be able to
To do more shit. I'm a disaster on the bike anywhere though, you know
Okay, well, thank you for like letting me know I'm saying and I do apologize if
You know and I don't have like the right information up this stuff. Yeah, I don't have a membership up right now
Take that down. I do a membership on the website though
If you would you want to support the website, and then I'll just fix this one to you
The websites really really really gonna be cool. It's actually gonna be like something that can like grow and it's like
Like Alexander is right about the world building and I didn't quite understand what that was at the time like this what but it's like basically
There it's like you think you can like re also repurposing content in the way, too
Which is like, you know, it's like it's like there's been said there's been such fucking great content on the show like amazing
Such great things have happened. We've had people we've had celebrities on the show. I mean not the biggest celebrities we had
it's been
Yeah, you know, yeah, it's like
Well, see, YouTube, you know, YouTube Kids is a kid's platform, like YouTube Kids is,
and it's like, you know, and also like some of those, like, but then it's like,
this is definitely an adult platform because it's like, you can get away with, like even TikTok,
I would say, is, is a much, um...
Stricter than YouTube if you if I was to let light a cigarette on tick-tock instantly
I would be instantly without like in a second it will go up
You know age restricted like they have like the AI is like on that like 20
It's like really going crazy on that right. I know well, I know but that's I'm saying that that's best for the kids
But it's not a kids. What do you mean is the kids platform? I mean kids can be on it like I guess like
Mine I have a niece that's like eight years old
Okay, I know, well, it's like, you know, my family is not really led to like, watch you, like, like my, my nieces and nephews aren't, they don't watch YouTube, like my sister distilates the app, she thinks that she's like, she's like, they watch the stupidest kids.
It's, no, it's not like, okay, well, maybe it has kids on it, but that's why they have a separate area for that.
I don't know, we also live in a world where we're like,
like I used to play this game called Hearthstone
and it was like, you know, it's stupid.
You sit there, like, you know, on a computer,
you don't see, you don't see anybody
or even hear anybody, but you're playing with other people.
And sometimes you could tell,
and these kids were better than I was
at the fucking game, right?
Right, I mean, but as more kids than adults,
well, there's two billion people that do,
so I don't know if it's like
over a billion kids or something.
That's crazy.
I just, I don't come across like kids in my normal life,
unless it's like my family members and stuff, right?
And so it's like, I don't understand why people like,
like, I mean, it's weird that people even have teachers
for their like, your kids, cause it's like, you know,
for all the people that are just so like, oh my God,
like it's like, you know.
Very controversial and I think they're just gonna have chat tpt teaching everybody in the future
It's gonna be like personalized like AI tutors and stuff like that
And then it's like well, are people like me you're gonna get out of the house. I don't know. I don't know
I mean, I rarely got out of the house that I'm you know
And it says
Well, who
It's like that is what I mean. It's like see it's like people like I don't know it's like oh so
No, it's so it's weird of people like I think it's weird
I mean it's like it's like sometimes it's not like sometimes people are you ever see mr. Rogers, and I mean he would like
I mean it's like
It's not unheard of like to have an adult talking, you know in a non
Weird way, but I mean people that think that everything's weird is gonna be wrong and it's like it's weird, you know
so
Hi charisma, how are you?
How do you how do you what happened?
Like why I understand what why are you having a problem with Brandon?
Hey, yeah, she's not gonna ban you come on, but I have to be it man. It's like I don't know it's like
You have to you can block him personally. You don't but you don't have to ban like it's like because he didn't do anything
I just feel bad when I saw that idiot trying to like swat him and stuff like that and like
how, that's like the real criminal stuff, like it's crazy, oh come on, let's not threaten
each other, dude let's just open your knife, I need to make sure that, but thank you for
asking that man, but yeah, I'm gonna, oh yeah, okay yeah, so Tony's trying to say he has
my cat and stuff right now, yeah.
That's not him a scary ass, but that's terrible to like put my kid to like try to make me think that you stole my cat or something
I mean, that's terrible. No, I know it's you Tony
New Jersey and stuff. I know his markings
You couldn't
Pretty sick
But I knew that would happen and I knew that was you too that I'm trying to like contact the
Yeah, because I was like
Why am I getting a call from New York about the cat and stuff like that?
So from a guy that already had texted me like about something else
But you talked but you're talking against Tony another chat. So it's weird. I don't know
Actually, you're more talking against against RG
Tony don't try to talk to RG to a leases. Come on. Yeah, so they just show me a picture of like what looks like a scared cat like
It looks like tricks a little bit, but it's like tricks is a kind of on there
It's in like a carrier looking all scared and like some guy like
being menacing, you're by him.
So, oh shit, shit, shit, that was an excellent one.
Okay, I fixed it.
Yeah, just personally block anybody that you have a problem
because I mean, it's like, it's like I can't have like
that bites and chat about it.
I didn't see it, if it really spread, yeah,
that wasn't really, I mean, it's like,
I think that was like a,
I don't know what Kate said she would do to me, right?
We can hide it, we can be hidden there.
See what happened. There we go.
Yeah, they can. Yeah, they can.
That woman looks like a man.
I'm sorry. I got a shit going on here too.
It's like, I'm being personally threatened and it's like,
just hide him.
I don't know. Okay, so I'm going to order some food.
I'm hungry. Fuck.
I'm going to get some food and coffee.
Okay, so we'll go for a short walk.
Oh yeah, but I want people to know too, it's like the guy, whatever the guy that came up on panel and everything the other day was like trying to, he was trying to cut, like those are the signs that he came on every single panel, like come on every like every back, every space backstage.
And then he's like, Oh, I don't know what's going on. And then he wouldn't stop coming up. And it's like, that's where it was like, it was, that guy was like harassing me. It was like, weird, in a weird way.
Also trying to say that oh I look homeless and so like I you all these like little like little jabs and stuff
It's like so lame
Okay, no. Oh shit. Well, I don't know how much much. Oh my god. I have 7% battery left. Okay, so let me see
I'm gonna get
My freak I will get my free coffee making it to okay
Yeah, maybe it's that some people I think like are never gonna be friends and some people might have maybe I think there's been misunderstandings
Probably could be friends. I mean, it's like, I don't know. It's like I do believe in second chances
Take my take my advice and
Always try to get a second. So this is an 800
870 calorie fucking sandwich. Oh my god. I don't know. I'm gonna do it. No, I'm not gonna do it
I'm just gonna get it for you there. Are you there shmere?
I'm gonna get a hash brown
And a onion and chive, toasted, okay.
Oh, okay.
I'm okay, perfect, okay, continue payment.
Hey, hey, everybody in chat,
like I don't know why there's 50 people,
but it's like, it's obvious that it's like,
probably like not 50 people, right?
What's going on, what just happened, what just happened?
Oh, I see, I didn't finish, I didn't finish bar life.
There we go.
Okay, guys, I don't know, at the end of the day,
I'm not going to be bullied or let people say some people
put through a lot. Okay, let me see. It's like nobody really thinks about like how people like
respond out of being traumatized sometimes. They're probably like these people are such bullies.
Like literally people that are like trying to get people to
unalive this. That's like the whole ip2 thing is like that they want basically they're trying
Or have the streamer kill themselves and like while they watch it and make a lap and it's like that
It's like this kind of like sadistic
thing with a lot of them
Where it's like the old so for the long game in it, then it's like
It's crazy. There's men. There's not so much people are just mentally ill
Okay
Now I can
Okay, let me go
Turn on and then we'll uh, I mean, I'll be holding two coffees and so
I'll put it on the way back. I don't think I'll be holding my phone, but it might be a little delay, but we can go out on a little walk
Scarlet on my bagel. Okay
Okay, I get to bring a coffee cup with me
So I'll have two coffee
If I get one there, okay
So let me turn off this. We're right there right with you
the flame, the shadow, and the profit, still that underground frequency is activated
You bring the darkness, I bring the light. We burn together.
Yeah, I saw Trishalicious, someone sent me her live or whatever, and I was like, oh,
wow, let's hear this great evidence. And it was just her bitching about, oh, he said
this about me, and like, oh, he just looks weird and stuff. He looks like a young, good-looking,
But yeah, I don't mean but whoever's here. I don't have your huge army. Like I don't care if you're here
Whatever, but it's like, you know, no harping on me. I'm I'm right. Okay. I was just getting my coffee and I was I'm trying
I'm trying to get my website back on
By the way, some people will be getting you know, it's like
Oh
Shut up get out of here. Yeah, get out of here panda
You're like it's probably the same for it's like I think it's just much like it's just much of sock puppets
It's like people with like fucking socks in their hands
I went to get coffee and then my phone died oh my god, and it's always like but and it's like oh the same thing
It's like what when you talk about I don't even like like anybody underage me mean discuss that I'm and I'll say like
I think there's like, you know, we're talking about children and we're talking about and it's like, oh, because I get called names because of a
banny
Because he's 25 and they're like, oh, he looks like he's from the embryo or something like that
Like it's some kind of like and he's like a fully
I mean, I know he's probably not the you know, his brain probably still a little bit to grow
But no, he's like 24 years old. I mean, it's like and it's not like anything sexual
And also like gay guys unlatched like friends and either he either or like, I don't know
It's like the world's going crazy. It's kind of like
Or maybe it's been going crazy, but it's like now it's to kind of like oh
We're like the squid games. We're like the super heroes. We're like the matrix or something like that
Well, I mean things might be like a matrix, but not quite in the way we think
right
Okay
The things for like a way things were waiting for me and things were watching that watching that so it might come up here
I'll put the link out finally
We'll see if it wants to come up and talk to shit anyone's welcome up everyone. Everyone's welcome today
I'm really good on that not on the draw
Hopefully my website
Trying to get back up right now
But come on up. It's always easier for me to talk to somebody
But oh, yeah, one of the things that's oh, there's gonna be surprises for people that actually go to the site and stuff
There's gonna be surprises and like limited edition things I'm really pretty crazy stuff
Hi, Rudy
But I'm kind of turning into like a nerdy programmer. I'm like now. It's like I remember when I started
I was like this is so hard. I have to have the computer do everything and now it's like I can do most of it
And that's like I ask it for some help like you know
And in like the coding and programming coding is very typical, you know
It's like it's very technical like it's like you can get caught for like something's a space off like one period
Like and it's like so that's very like I don't know how people were able to do it up until now because
Just brilliant people, right? It's like cuz it's like I can't I
Don't know. I couldn't figure out how to do it by hand. It's kind of like the difference between
You know, I don't know like playing the tambourine. I'm playing the fucking grand piano or something
Okay, but yeah, there's gonna be really cool things like I'll give you a hint like, you know trading cards, but no
Trading cards with me. Maybe like you guys here. We have a guest come on up. Let's welcome a guest
second
We'd be guests or ghosts. Let's see who it is. Oh
Hello, hello. Hold on a second. Hi. How are you today?
There um, oh, can you see me? Let me see
What what wasn't like? Oh, there I am. Oh my god. I was off the off the camera
And I have to put I think I have to fix it where you can come on too because I have it like where it's like you have to be
On camera, but I'll take that off. Oh
What's my thing doing?
I'll get you on there your phones actually sounds just give me a sec. I might have to go outside you work better. No problem
I'll come right back up psychers. It's really good if
Okay, I'm I work out
I'm trying to kind of I'd put you back on the screen you see um
Lay out guess can stream hockey the recording
Visual I don't know. I know I just hit something that said
I guess have to have your audio on or something.
Let me see, shift it.
Oh yeah, audio badges.
Oh, audio avatars.
Okay, there we go.
Oh, there she is.
Okay, see?
I fixed it.
Now we look like boobs.
Now I know we look like a pair of boobs on my screen.
Yeah, so page is here.
Oh my gosh.
Hi, Rude.
Rude has a little cold, I think,
because maybe it's, oh.
Who's been going sneezing and stuff? Okay. Hi. Hi, sweetie your kisses. Yeah, we did have like that
You know the jerks. Yeah, there's some cool people, too
Hey, yeah, yeah, I feel like I'm I feel like that's them. It looks like the moon a lot behind me
Let me see equated of tax fraud. Who is equated of tax fraud Shakira? Oh my god. She's innocent
I didn't know Shakira was in a Spanish tax fraud case
She could have been in big trouble.
55 million euros.
Oh my God, I guess she got five 55 million dollars.
And then she, well, who would have paid that?
So of course you're gonna try to do tax evasion on that.
I don't know if you can see too well,
but I do have a new logo now.
Oh, here we go.
Hi.
Is that better?
Yes.
Yay, I did it.
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
How are you doing today?
Um, I'm okay. I'm just having a coffee. I've been up since like 5 30, so
Yeah
It's freezing here
Yeah, well, I haven't seen he was fucking really windy yes and cold
Today's nice
Good. Yeah, today seems like a nice day. Like I mean, is it really gonna do this to me again?
There was like 200 people hitting him like that today.
I have to go outside.
OK.
Oh, this is so annoying.
I'm so sorry, Psych.
Just give me a sec.
No, not at all.
Oh, even the guest.
Sure, the right person.
Hold on a second.
OK.
Psych, I'm going to have to drop down,
and I might go outside where I have better service, OK?
Love you.
I'll be back.
OK.
Hey, why the fuck do you ban me, bro?
I ain't ban you.
Well, I'm banned, bro, and you just ignore it. Oh, oh, he's banning. You just oh, let me just take his money, bro
And let him get banned. What the fuck?
Brandon come down. I could you were on another account, so I didn't
Wow
Really that
Well, what the fuck bro? Oh, oh, yeah, somebody please send me some money, bro
Send you money, bro
And then oh, yeah, just let him get banned bro and then act like I don't see it dude
That's fucking bullshit. I remodeled you actually
I mean, what are you talking about bro? I'm banned dude. I saw that on the other one your other brand account
I'm on it. My other Brandon account is gone bro. It's been deleted bro. You were just talking about it, bro
Okay, cuz I don't know he's gonna say oh, I know I modded your other count that other terminated, bro
Okay, so I'm confused here. Just calm down a little bit because I was confused like I can uh, I
Literally told you I said my channel was banned. You know that
Yeah, Alex was talking about it dude. I know but then I didn't know if you were I didn't know if you chat on the same thing as the channel
I don't see I know I know that your channel is done
So once you're banned you can't chat your channel is gone bro. It doesn't exist dude, okay?
Well, I didn't I thought you're back on the other channel. I didn't know how you got okay
So I know because you don't I don't even know why this bitch is banning me banning me for what because she doesn't like me
She said oh, I don't like him. Can I ban him and then you didn't even say anything, bro
You just laugh dude the fuck
Well, I know I wasn't laughing at that and Brandon Brandon
I noticed that you get your triggered and stuff like that
but it's like it's not anything that was just bullshit, bro
and somebody is begging for money, bro, you help them out
and the next thing you know, they're like, yeah, that's fucking bullshit, dude.
Oh, it wasn't it's not about that.
And it's like, I mean, but it's like, you want to go there?
It's like, OK, we can go there, but no, that's fucking bullshit, dude.
Well, I know, but it's like you have to give me like five minutes to take care of it, you know
It's like five minutes. You literally saw it, bro
Or thing that is has been has been banned for weeks
Hey, listen Brandon, it's like you're you're on my discord. You can just write me there and say I'm not on discord
I'm banned from discord too, bro. I'm banned from everywhere, bro. I didn't know that. Okay. Wow
Well, I'm sorry. Um, I just like you're probably under attack by these people and I know that's why
Why you're like a little like I put offensive about it, but it's like not everything's bad bro. My instagram's banned
Okay
Everything's bad bro. I'll make sure that you're I mean I said yeah
I'll make sure that you're not so I try to protect you in the chat
So I wouldn't worry about that kind of thing and so and that's why I wasn't even thinking about it like you know
But you know, it's like, you know, I mean I've taken you know
Anyway, it's like I always stand up for what I believe in, but let me get you
Um, I'm blocked. So you just fucked up, bro. You literally saw her at ban me, dude
I didn't see her. I was I didn't you say no. Why didn't you say no? No, don't ban him
I did and then I modded the account. I did
I mean, it's like you weren't like and then I was being distracted because there's all these people all of a sudden
See the same thing in the chat and I was like, okay
Yeah, cuz obviously somebody found your people watch your channel, bro. I don't know why you play dumb dude like
And then you do this dumb shit playing your little music and turning the screen black, bro
like
Because I would you need to work on your streaming skills, bro. Okay. Thanks. Okay, Brad
Please
Okay, right. That should just yeah, that shit just pisses me off, bro
And somebody's begging for money and you help him out next thing you know, you're the one
Fucking tell Nancy to pay money if she wants to ban me then tell her to give you fucking $20 to ban me for a day
Okay, well, you know, this is the thing. It's like, this is like when you, you know, it's like, you know, you get, you're like, helps and all that. No, I'm being like, hey, listen, listen, it was like, I didn't mean to bite your hand. It's like, or, you know, I don't think mean to bite mine. I think you're very, here, your own band. I mean, it's like, it takes two seconds for me to deal. It just takes a second. But I need to like, you know, I have ADHD and I'm not wanting to focus entirely on one person in the chat. And so it's like, it wasn't no one personal. Okay.
Just calm down and like, you don't have to like, you know, lash out at me, okay?
I was an impersonal dude, okay?
Try to help you as much as I could.
I'll have to like fucking jump down my throat about it, okay?
What's that song?
There's a great Trump story.
It's one of my only Trump stories I like.
It reminds me of this situation.
Except it has to do with a man and a snake instead of a woman and a snake, you know?
His favorite it's his favorite poem is by Oscar Wilde. Oh, wow. Well guys, wow
I know and I was told that what happened to him. Okay, prepare for all this. I don't mean he missed the whole
sitting there trying to defend him all the time
And everyone's in it and I know it's they and it's like fuck it's they gonna die
It's like I already put my slip on the line, right?
Without it mean it's like geez
Okay
I'm a loyal person here you go enjoy you sure are you sure
Who has heard the poem called the snake?
So I have it. Does anybody want to hear it again?
You sure are you sure?
Okay, so let's dedicate this
to
General Kelly the border patrol and the ice agents for doing such an incredible job
This was written by Al Wilson a long time ago and I thought of it having to do with our borders and people coming in
And we know what we're going to have we're gonna have problems. We have to very very carefully vet
We have to be smart. We have to be vigilant
So here it is the snake. It's called the snake on her way to work
One morning down the path along the lake
A tender-hearted woman saw a poor, half-frozen snake.
His pretty-colored skin had been all frosted with the dew.
Poor things, he cried, I'll take you in, and I'll take care of you, the border.
Take me in, O tender woman.
Take me in for heaven's sake.
She wrapped him up all cozy in a comforter of silk and laid him by her fireside with
some honey and some milk.
She hurried home from work that night and as soon as she arrived, she found that pretty
snake she'd taken in had been revived.
Take me in for heaven's sake. Take me in. Oh tender woman
Side that vicious snake
She clutched him to her bosom
You're so beautiful. She cried
But if I hadn't brought you in by now, oh heavens
You would have died
She stroked his pretty skin again and kissed him and held him tight
But instead of saying, thank you, that snake gave her a vicious bite.
Take me in, O tender woman, take me in for heaven's sake.
Take me in, O tender woman, side the vicious sake.
I have saved you, cried the woman.
You know your bite is poisonous and now I'm going to die. Oh
shut up
silly woman
Said the reptile with a grin
You knew damn well. I was a snake before you took me in
I
Just wanted to say that and it's always
Shall a trumpet be blown in the city and the people not be afraid
dreams
American dreams
Shalom family, welcome to Shattered Paradise
It's time to gird up get focused reinforce that hedge of protection
All hands on deck
Because here we go again
The Luciferan ruling class the blue bloods have reached into their old
Illuminati bag of tricks and pulled out one of their favorite gold tubes
They're red and blue spellcasting, and so it's divide and conquer season
for the so-called aristocratic blue blood families.
If you were born blue bloods like your husband,
Fingin' up skyscrapers, his wife's a proper blue blood. I'll give you a clue.
Darius, we can't keep the princess waiting. Blue blood.
Why do we keep referring to something like blue blood?
Human blood is actually red.
Usually, we use this term specifically to address a member of a wealthy upper-class family or ancestry.
But why exactly blue blood?
They're red and blue.
Republicans and Democrats, Bloods and Crips all fall under the spiritual jurisdiction and dominion of the Red Dragon
and the so-called blue blood families with their mysterious lineage who currently control this world.
England's blue bloods.
The earth is given into the hand of the wicked.
This last so-called Super Bowl Sunday was a ceremonial display of esoteric dualism,
the Hegelian dialectic, and the invocation of the primordial fire and ice elemental spirits.
Blue symbolizing the cold calculated intellect of man versus red representing the fiery ferocious instinct of beast.
The halftime show might as well have been titled, The Great Set Trip.
12 minutes of gangbanging, crit-walking and khakis and chucks throwing up real hoods
and gang signs while antagonizing those on the other side who have an affinity for the
Scarlet Rag.
This comes just days after Snoop and his shadowy corporate masters purchased death row records
Before he heads to the Super Bowl halftime show Snoop Dogg makes a big business deal big news music news for you today
Snoop Dogg who became a star back in the 1990s on death row records just bought the label
I do want to talk to you about one deal that you tell me what this deal is what well look
Oh, Blackstone. Okay, right. I own a thin sliver of Blackstone on your screen now,
it's down 2%, but they sold, what, Snoop Dogg's music or something?
I just really wanted to hear you say Snoop Dogg.
Yeah, so Snoop Dogg owns Death Row Records. Have you heard of Death Row Records?
Absolutely, I have.
And so Dr. Dre, Dr. Dre, of course, and also where Snoop Dogg
started his career and Tupac. So it's interesting that that
you have you have Snoop Dogg buying death row records. I
didn't know that Blackstone actually owned death row
records. So they own MRNK Entertainment, which owns death
row records. And that's why they were able to sell that was a
very eclectic portfolio that Blackstone has. That's for sure.
The range of stuff that Blackstone owns and runs.
The New World Order even went as far as to utilize one of the top spokespersons for their
transhumanism agenda, Sophia, to promote a whole new generation of Krippen.
I just got in LA for the Super Bowl weekend, the vibe is different from Miami.
I hear music everywhere I go, and I love singing along to it.
Many people are telling me about this new song by Fabio Foreign, Kanye and Alicia Keys
City of Gods.
It just dropped.
I really love Alicia Keys voice, and I think Kanye and Fabio are so talented.
I think you guys should check it out.
This new song by 504 and Sophia in the sulfide stadium are promoting 504 in an east coast
Crip and purveyor of the mainstream music industry's newest form of murder music
drill
We must remember Sophia is the creator goddess of the Gnostics
The Gnostics revered a female deity by the name of Sophia
Sophia is a feminine goddess who the Gnostics believed began as an energetic field emerging
from the center of the galaxy.
Sophia makes the great sacrifice of being a universal field of energy, and she descends
into the cosmos to begin a transformation into the Earth.
Sophia began her transformation in Gnostic mythology.
The all with all capital letters is the original primary unity.
And the all with lowercase letters is the creation of the universe
in which everything comes out as separate parts.
We wanted to create the entertainment mecca and the entertainment capital of the world.
A place that would amplify the senses.
Something so much more than an NFL building.
All come together to create this symphony of energy.
It's kind of space-like, alien, crazy, new age. I love it.
And we wanted the experience of going down into the stadium to be something really truly unique.
Sofie, or Sophie, is derived from the Gnostic goddess, Sophia.
So when Pepsi, whose logo epitomizes red and blue dualism,
teams up with Sofie's stadium and Sophia the robot,
It is clear to see that the controllers are invoking their so-called mother goddess to birth twins,
one of fire and one of ice.
They want Republicans and Democrats even more polarized, further widening the political divide between red states and blue states.
And when it comes to street politics, they'll do anything to sprinkle a little new salt in
the old proverbial wounds of decades of turf wars and tens of thousands of dead youths.
One listen and it's clear, 5.0 foreign is that new salt in the womb.
He's been anointed by the unholy spirits and is next up to push the cold blue side of the
But very few drill rappers stay alive long enough to accomplish anything.
After all, this is not the 80s and 90s where a handful of rappers die every decade.
This is the 2020s, the season of judgment, where death is almost an everyday occurrence
in hip hop.
The New World Order swings the pendulum from left to right, red to blue, every four to eight years.
You had the Snoop and Dog Pound era, then the Sue Woop era kicked off with the game Little Wayne,
and a whole host of others with the red bandana.
And now it looks like they're swinging the pendulum back to blue.
But it is not the bloods and the crypts that control this industry.
The real red and blue gang who wields actual power are the blue bloods worldwide.
5.0 foreign is not brought to us by the hood, but by multinational corporate conglomerations,
Columbia Records, and Sony Music Entertainment. This new song by 5.0 foreign.
We speak more about the overall agenda in our latest long-form presentation,
Devil's Playground, Babylon's Last Distraction.
They already told you last year that football is gay.
What more do you need?
As usual, the Super Bowl's overpriced, multi-million dollar commercials
conjured the carnivorous capitalist that lies deep within the hearts of the American consumer.
And the subliminal witchcraft was very thinly veiled this year, not only promoting the transhumanism AI animal hybrid agenda,
but preconditioning the collective subconscious of the public to go along with another part of their plan.
They're obviously promoting the lawless, do-with-out-willed spirit, while subconsciously reassuring
the audience that liquid death being introduced into your body and bloodstream is as harmless
as water.
Hmm.
I wonder what liquid death could represent these days.
Today's and its fans are morning the loss of a well-known former player Jeremy
Giambi has died unexpectedly. That's according to his agent. Crown Force
reporter, Kylan Mills, joins us from the newsroom with what we know. Kylan, he
was, he was young. Yeah, Ken, he was really young. His agent, Joel Wolf, announced
this afternoon that Jeremy Giambi died at just 47 years old. Right now, there's
no information about the possible cause of death.
A father in the South Suburbs is in morning his 17 year old son was on the court playing
for his midlothian high school team when he collapsed during a game last week.
I'm definitely hurt. I'm going to be hurt forever.
It's a pain Terry Wheatley has never had to endure.
His middle child 17 year old Cameron Wheatley suddenly died.
Wheatley says his son has been playing basketball since he was eight years old
and has never had any medical conditions.
Wheatley says the autopsy report doesn't give an indication why his son
suddenly died. No medical issues. Completely healthy kid. Uh, you know,
all this records, you know, shot records and all those things up to date.
Like, you know, nothing. He had nothing.
For a lot of people, it's a family, one where Katie Novak was a beloved member.
But if somebody was having a bad day or they didn't feel safe, they could come here and
feel safe.
All the more reason she was a part of making them feel that way.
Her sudden death leaves such a large hole, her desk empty.
When I went to check on her, she just didn't wake up.
Chris Keeker is Katie's friend who said she had some heart conditions and a
possible second bout with COVID. She was vaccinated and she had had it early
on before vaccinations. Nobody ever suggested that there was anything that
was, you know, on the edge of being wrong. A young Valley woman with a
promising future dies unexpectedly. Siran Burhey died unexpectedly Monday at
28 years old after a pulmonary embolism.
US life insurance companies have reported an overwhelming and unexplainable increase in all
cause deaths among 18 to 49 year olds. Along with that, there's also been an increase in certain
medical diagnosis such as miscarriages and Bell's palsy. Here to give us her take on the new data
and what she believes could be causing the rise in numbers as emergency medicine and disaster
specialist Dr. Kelly Victory. Dr. Victory, good morning. Great to talk to you as always.
Good morning, Jason. Thanks for having me.
Okay. We want to make sure that any time we talk,
we want to make sure the information that we have is accurate.
So let's start this interview by telling us,
I've seen your correspondence here.
What is the source of the information that you are about to present?
Well, this information became available to me or on my radar last week following a hearing
with Senator Ron Johnson, who was looking at sort of what he calls a second opinion
on the entire response to the COVID pandemic.
The medical data was released by three career military physicians who got the information
that collects what we call ICD codes, which are the diagnosis codes.
And these physicians had a feeling they believed based on their own observation that they were
seeing a significant uptick in certain conditions.
So they actually went back and called the database from the military on certain conditions
continuing, uh, continuing.
one year, 2020, of the full-blown pandemic.
So they looked at 2016, 17, 18, 19, and 20
at the prevalence of certain conditions,
including things like heart attack,
blood clots to the lung, miscarriages,
those sorts of things.
And they compared it to the incidents
of those same things in the calendar year 2021
and saw an alarming increase in certain things.
For example, they saw
a 270% increase in myocardial infarction in 2021, a 300% increase in incidents of Bell's
palsy and of certain neurologic complaints, a 470% increase in pulmonary embolisms,
blood clots to the lungs, and many, many other huge increases that they found alarming.
Now, no one is saying with any certainty, Jason, what is causing this, but we certainly
would be remiss as scientists if we didn't look at that and say there is something going
on.
What happened in 2021?
that was so different from the previous five-year average that would cause this massive increase
in certain medical conditions.
So the source of the information is several U.S. life insurance companies that have been
reporting this, correct?
And these three career physicians that you referred to.
Yes, they are separate groups of data.
Jason, the previous study from the U.S. life insurance companies.
Many of them were reporting a 40% increase in deaths from all causes in the 18 to 49-year-old
group.
They know that because these are life insurance companies that provide group life insurance
policies to employers.
So these are working age individuals with a 40% increase in all cause deaths.
That was a different report from this bombshell that came out last week from, as I said, three
career military physicians who are calling a military database.
So they are two groups of data that show, again, an alarm that something is going on.
And the question is what?
an increase in all cause deaths as reported by the life insurance companies and an increase
in certain medical conditions such as heart attacks, blood clots to the lungs, congenital
malformations of children born that year, female infertility, and those sorts of things.
See the Super Bowl and the Olympics are just witchcraft filled bread and circuses made
In closing, we must pray that we be granted the spiritual discernment and holy spirit-inspired
vigilance so that we will be able to see things as they truly are and not just as they appear to be.
That's and then somebody hid you after that
But yeah, what's up J dog how are you good? How about you man? What's going on with you? I mean, okay?
I mean, it's like Tony's saying me pictures now of him with the tricks and stuff, but it's like I'm not real
I've heard about that. You get it. Is it the real trick or is it just a lookalike cat?
No, it's me
Yeah
Not well not too much
Oh shit, hold up
Oracle is really cool, but it's also trained on all the data of the show, like everything
I've ever said. So you'll be able to find, like, anything, talk about anything. It's
like pretty, there's been so many things talked about. So it was an accident, bro. It was an
accident. I didn't ban you. I accidentally, I was trying to do somebody else and because
Anyway, yeah, I don't know if that's pretty crazy, like I might call it, I guess, but I'll go to Google and stuff, but, you know, I'll like...
Yeah, I know, I'll check out your website for sure, man.
It's down right now, it's down right now, but...
Oh, you're still working on it right now?
Yeah, I've been like, it's a...
I've been able to market it. I've been a good marketer, but I've never had the technique of this stuff, and so I've always learned to build these things that I can never build.
Yeah, and so I don't know it's it's a really it's really
But you're on it. There'll even be a trading card of you
Oh
They're gonna be like garbage pale kids
Yeah, it's like
Can you hear me now? A lot better? Am I a lot better? Okay, hold on.
Yeah, YouTube's been, like, unmonitizing a lot of people and also, like, you know, I've been kicked off of YouTube, but it's, like, all that shit I've done on it.
It's, like, it's crazy. I'm still around, but it's like, yeah, I've been surviving.
I've been actually kicked off, like, four times and gotten it back every time, so it's, like, you know, it's, like, it's possible.
I'm sorry to hear that man. You'll get your monetization back, bro. You'll get it back. I can I can apply for it
Wait a certain time and then it's like and then they have you like
submit like this video appeal and
And then they didn't even watch it. They didn't even like literally watch it. They had zero views on it
They're doing to a lot of people
Well, they take like 30% and then like if you do something wrong they want to keep it all like they don't even want to give you any of what your earnings are
So it's someone goes to like a charity. I think they'd like have to a charity
Oh, okay
Yeah, so I don't know like, uh, no Archie's
You perform on the show. Yeah, and then so did a cue and then yeah
People will try that. Why are they porn bombing? Is it the brand-new Q stuff? Is that what it is?
Well, I mean that yeah, yeah
They kind of come up with oh
The pdf word and it's like
It's crazy
I don't know. I think it's like
Got getting like out of hand like with people because they just think I just think they just think it's a way to troll
And then it's like that he gets people on the outside. Oh, what's going on there? Like, oh
There but it's like it is like there's a lot there is a bucket like
exaggerators
What your campaigners slanderers
Obvious, yeah, I'm sorry about that bro. I'm sorry. They've been fucking with your channel man. I'm not bad
Check in with you man. Just make sure you're okay psyche, you know see how you're doing man and
Okay, yeah, just keep your head high man. You know just screw with the haters say you know just fuck the haters
You know remember let's screw the haters. Do you do what you want to do your show your channel your life
Do how you want to do
No problem. All right. I'll see you later, bro. Peace out. Yeah, I try to explain in the chat like
Like I really, I mean, I'll hide people that are just like, you know, but I wouldn't hide you
I mean, it's like things as an accident and but then it unmods you and I
Remember to like unhide you, but I didn't remember to mod you back
And so then somebody else hid you which is like why you're modding the first place because I don't want people to hide you so
But I wouldn't like that, you know, you shouldn't like it's a mad at me because it's like I
Kind of like didn't deserve that I don't think but
Maybe it's the most understanding, so give me the benefit of it out. Okay, I do appreciate you, you know, but
just like
I'm not like I wouldn't be I wouldn't be like a toothpaste or malicious to you
Okay, no, I'm not gonna like slip on you and like just totally
Like I wouldn't turn I mean it's like so you don't need to get the Q army on me. Okay promise
Okay
Oh, this is such a pain in the bucket, and it's been deployed.
Yeah, but I had a good weekend with like, you know,
hi Ricky, how are you?
Nancy, well, I mean, maybe,
I don't know what happened because it's like,
then the chat is like, goes back, but you know what?
It's like, all you have to do is let me know on the,
no, you're not, you're not,
just like, let me know somehow
on my other channel or something.
Thing that is it happens to him all the time doesn't it? Hey, Brandon
There's like a hundred people that's up that I think that girl jam came in and hid
You know like a hundred people and so it's like
I was still like I still have a few people to unban it stuff. So I mean, it's like I'm a little overwhelmed with all
with it, you know
not like anybody's like they're trying to
Be nice anyway, but
I mean it's like so hard to like I don't I don't really even know like most of the drama in order
I really want to I like I like not not being a part of like all the
Really intense stuff, but you know, I do you have to like, you know just battle to be myself sometimes, right?
Okay, okay, okay well
Here, I'm a public service announcement while I go do this again, I promise I'll be right back.
This digital profit kept predicting things before they happened, not perfectly, but enough
to make people uncomfortable.
And eventually, the internet stopped asking, who is this person, and started asking, how
does he know, the broadcasts began quietly.
Strange observations about internet culture, human psychology, algorithms, addiction, isolation,
most people ignored them.
But a small group noticed something disturbing.
The prophet described emotional patterns online months before they became mainstream.
He spoke about digital addiction before people called it doomscrolling.
He warned that algorithms.
would reward outrage over truth.
He claimed humanity would slowly trade identity for performance.
At the time, it sounded paranoid.
Now it sounds obvious, and there terrified people even more.
Because the Prophet never sounded emotional,
never sounded angry, only calm.
Like someone describing a future he had already seen,
The Prophet never asked for followers, never sold courses, never demanded loyalty.
And yet, people gathered anyway.
Forums formed around decoding the broadcasts.
Liverstreams analyzed hidden meanings.
Entire communities emerged around fragmented clips and cryptic messages.
The internet did what it always does.
It transformed mystery into mythology.
Prophet was an heir. Others believed he was a former tech engineer. Some claimed he was multiple.
People operating together. But nobody could prove anything.
And uncertainty made the fascination stronger. Because the less people understood him,
the more they projected onto him. Hope. Fear. Meaning. Identity. The perfect conditions for
Then came the prediction that changed everything.
One transmission contained a single sentence.
The future belongs to whoever controls human attention.
At first, people interpreted it as philosophy.
But years later, social media evolved into psychological warfare.
Attention became currency. Algorithms shaped elections. Outrage became profitable.
Human focus became programmable. And suddenly, the prophet's words no longer felt symbolic.
They felt diagnostic, as if someone had understood.
The trajectory of civilization before the rest of society caught up, that's when fear
entered the conversation.
Because people began wondering.
Was he predicting the future?
Or helping design it?
And then, without warning, the broadcast stopped.
No explanation.
No goodbye.
No final message.
But the internet refused to let him disappear. Clips continued circulating. Community stayed
active. People searched endlessly for hidden clues. Because an resolved mystery is psychologically
addictive. And maybe, that was the final lesson. The prophet understood something humanity
Unknown, they worship it, especially when the unknown reflects something they secretly
fear about.
Themselves, maybe the digital profit was real, maybe he was fiction, maybe he was an experiment,
or maybe, he was simply someone who understood human psychology before the rest of the world
did.
But his final warning still lingers beneath the noise of the internet, whoever controls
Controls reality, and somewhere tonight,
while millions scroll endlessly through glowing screens.
Someone else is still quietly studying the pattern.
This has been a transmission from the Cult of Psyche.
Stay Unreadable.
Yeah, stay unreadable.
OK, well, hopefully you guys aren't fighting.
But I think people will need to work it out sooner or later.
But it's like, you know, we are fighting
Not to like demonize anybody, but I mean some of these people are like
There's two twists, you know
people that are like
Going IRL was people like going to their thing according to their house and like money to like, you know
It's like it's really silly
I think that's why I
Did have a song about like I did mention like the the clumsy thing
Right, I know I can't show you this thing about I think it was like about Drake and like these dogs and stuff
Oh, let me see because they had this like thing where they like blackmailed like with these dogs
They like they have like someone have sex with a dog in the party or something
Maybe with the brotherhood or something. I wonder if it's still up. It was really graphic. Oh, here it is. I have it here
You'll enjoy this
Well, we'll just watch a little bit of it. It's pretty long though here. It's crazy.
It's playing. You start to hear the sound.
See? There is the best medicine.
Please!
Stop and listen to my material!
Peter has long been used as a slang term for a penis.
Peter Parker takes on new meaning now, doesn't it?
Pan is a word for an ancient god of nature.
He was the original model for the Pied Piper, luring away children into the forest to be
his sacrifices.
We use the word pan today as in terms like pan-African or as in the pan now used on
a studio mixer to mean all or many.
Even in cookware, the right-sized pan can be used to cook or contain everything at once.
The first use of the term Peter Pan came from hospital bedpans which male patients used to
relieve themselves in, hence the name Peter Pan, or a pan for your Peter, so to speak.
This points back to early hospitals being involved with the abuse of young boys who found themselves
Getting a boy to use the Peter Pan was a subtle and twisted invitation for him to unzip his pants.
It's weak. You're just well surgically enhanced and you spent more money than the Vatican. So let's not talk
If you go to Neverland it says you must be this high to ride Michael
Obviously people in the lawyers for HP are going
From all that beloved character from the 70s and 80s sitcom more can Mindy must have studied the writings of Alistair Crowley
Well, the likelihood is that either the writers of the sitcom, Robin himself, or both, were
students of Occultist and Freemason, Alistair Crowley.
Crowley challenged his students to not only walk backwards and talk backwards, but to
also find every way they possibly could to do things backwards.
So of course, backwards dressing Chris Cross and backwards walking Michael Jackson would
have to have had a song together.
Backward's walking Michael has more than this in common with Backward sitting Robin,
as we will soon see.
But the hermetic inversion symbolism found throughout the sitcom Mork and Mindy is nothing
short of staggering.
Robin appeared to be a clean-cut family man, but his former prior show castmates have exposed
his heavy cocaine use, and his struggles with sexuality are all but evident in his
demeanor.
Straight men just do not move and speak certain ways, even in jest, and during Robin's heyday the torment of living a double life because of compromising one's sexuality was especially dangerous with the added fear of the AIDS scare, which came right on the heels of the 1960s and 70s false advertisement for free love, sex, drugs and rock and roll.
The rainbow suspenders are only a dead giveaway today.
In those days, the image crafted for Robin, which happens to be a unisex or duality name,
was the safe image of a quirky, childlike man with boyish innocence and charm.
Nowadays, we consider him to have been a tormented man, overrun by secrets and a rapidly growing
irrelevance.
A man who suffered silently with severe mental health issues, the symbol of the triangle
as a symbol for gender is universally known and understood, pointing up to symbolize the
male parts for obvious reasons, and pointed downward in the V shape to represent the female
reproductive area.
Mork wears the pyramid pointed down on his trademark space costume.
The show is set in Boulder, Colorado where Mork, an alien explorer from the planet Ork
has landed in a spaceship that shaped like an egg.
Ladies and gents, need I remind you of the story of the Queen Mother Goddess, Anana,
Ishtar reportedly coming to Earth in a space egg, which is the origin for the pagan Catholic
It does not end there.
Eventually, as sweet and fruitacious as Mork is, he and Mindy finally get together to the
fans' delight, and they marry.
Soon after we learn that Mork is actually the one who gets pregnant in his, quote unquote,
world, and as he breaks the news to Mindy, Mork goes into labor, and seconds later lays
an egg through his stomach, developing a navel in the process.
Guest star comedian Jonathan Winters, a man visibly much older than Mork and Mindy,
plays the newborn, because in keeping with the backwards or hermetically inverted themes,
the people from Orcage backwards.
Square business guys, can't make this up, unless of course you have some good advice
from old Alistair to inspire you.
More mind control space and fantasy programming.
I was enamored with the idea of aliens and space travel and therefore consumed everything
that pop culture wanted to program me with at that age.
When I was a child, I spoke and thought as one.
When I became a man, I put away childish things.
Mark, Robin and for that matter Michael all suffer from arrested development, with the
former and the latter ending their lives in tragedy, or secretly living with the shame
of the programming they'd both received and dealt out over the years as a result of their
involvement.
Why is Peter Pan a figure of such interest and inspiration to you?
Because Peter Pan to me
represents something that's very special in my heart. You know, he represents youth,
childhood, never growing up, magic,
flying,
everything I think that
children
and wonderment and magic, what it's all about.
And to me, I just have never, ever grown out of loving that or thinking that is very special.
Do you identify with him?
Totally.
You don't want to grow up?
No, I am Peter Pan.
Are you on your Michael Jackson?
I'm Peter Pan in my heart.
From Thanks For The Memories The Truth Has Set Me Free by Bryce Taylor, Chapter 21, The Hollywood Connection, Michael Jackson
Michael Jackson was just a little boy of four or five when I accompanied Bob Hope to a place where they were filming up and coming talent for television.
Bob told me he supported and sponsored the Jacksons, getting them a professional foot in the door.
Their father brought the boys in and I remembered seeing them taken into a side room where bright lights were on.
They all had to drop their pants and before their performance a big man raped each one of them in a line-up.
Then they were taken to a different room and dressed in little suits and sent onto the stage to perform.
Due to the mind control I was under, I'm not sure exactly where we were, but feel that it was the early days of the Ed Sullivan show.
I watched as Bob dressed in a grey pinstripe suit and bow tie with white shoes, chakens with Ed, and then the Jackson boys went on.
They were made into a sensation and famous on purpose so that they could be used in the future to influence large audiences.
Bob and his connections knew that all they needed was some talent. Makeup, costumes, lights, glitter and lots of publicity.
He said publicity was the most important ingredient.
I was just a teenager and Bob said that he wanted me to be present so I could learn the ropes to being a starlet.
He wanted me to see how it was done and feel comfortable around the stage.
I think he just said that as a cover to other people to hide the real reason I was with him for his and other sexual pleasure.
Bob explained to me how important clothes are to one with a public image to uphold.
I had on a short small tight fitting low cut yellow chic dress.
I did as I was told and wore it along with the gold high heels I was provided.
Bob was off in the connection for new entertainment.
The council used his connections for their own interest and got key entertainers in place for future use.
Many were robots like me. I saw many of them get hurt. I never saw Bob get hurt though.
The Jacksons were hurt. I was witness to their abuse.
That first time when they performed, Bob got them onto the show and then we left in the limo and watched from the television inside.
He told the driver to drive around until the show was over. Then Bob told me, see how easy it is to be a star.
I want you so I'm ready to go
For a chance to
To the limit, to the limit
To the limit
They want to play in the music business, so they want to play in everyone.
What do you think?
Well, it's all of the above and a whole lot more, but it boils down to you.
Um, you know, uh,
I was introduced to certain people and to certain opportunities to, to...
New recreational arts, and it both sounds what I want to do with her, and she's a strong will, a strong minded girl.
And I can't say that it's not anybody's fault.
Would she have gone down that route, do you think, without Bobby Brown in her life?
Well, if it would have not hit somebody else, if she wants to get high, if you want to get high, you want to get high.
Do you think she had that tendency anyway?
I think that we all, as artists,
Because we're highly sensitive people.
And this machine around us, this so-called music industry,
is such a demonic thing.
It sacrifices people's lives and their essences.
It's not good enough.
To all my heart and my soul, you know, in my writing.
But at the end of the day, I am being guided by some.
Other power. I don't know what it is
I hear you have this song right he says that you're scared of the six conveniently three
times now some people say well he's talking about Canada but he says the six three times
I don't think the area code of Canada six six six and then why would we be scared of
Canada so listen to it.
So you know there's a lot of demonic symbolism you can see the imagery you can see you know the aisle and things like that
But I want to bring your attention to what happened recently at one of his concerts, right?
They have I don't know they got this infatuation with portals, right?
And so check this out. So I want you guys to take a look at this Drake clip from a recent concert, right?
So you see he's sitting on this bed
He's young version of himself. I guess it's like a hologram or something. They've been using a lot of those
And then you see the screen right here.
It's changing and transitioning.
It shows him when he was a TV actor,
I guess like going through that timeline of his success.
And then here's where it starts getting a little weird.
So you see that the lights are changing.
He's going to bed, the lights turn off.
And then here comes this like shadowy spirit kind of thing.
Now, some people were arguing,
oh, this is just a reference to Peter Pan.
But the guy who,
wrote Peter Pan. Apparently, you know, he's like a free mason and he practiced witchcraft,
sorcery or he was into that kind of stuff. Either way, all right, you see this shadowy
creature, right? Moving around, you want to say it's a reference to Peter Pan, but watch
this, right? Start spinning splits into a whole bunch of different, you know, versions of that
shadow and begins to create a portal right here. I don't remember that in Peter Pan,
right? Splitting into a bunch of shadows and so it's spinning here, spinning, creating this portal.
And then eventually here comes Drake, he's going to come out of that portal.
So is that like some kind of symbolism for like, okay, you know, you know, Satan visited me, you know, he's this.
He talks about being the sixth God and all that kind of stuff and we'll dive into some other stuff, but.
Here he comes out the portal, right? And is this like symbolic of oh man
This this was my transition when I had this encounter. All right. Why is it that they're just so infatuated?
You know with this of the music industry we talk about it all of the time and look you got this
What's this goofy guy jaw rule? I mean first of all, it's just it's terribly
Corny and heart-washing his boxers like what's going on like this is just the facial expressions
He looked like master splinter like what are you doing?
I don't know it's just but what is their infatuation like you never see them do this with you know
Muslims or any other religion they always take some kind of element of Christianity and they want to mock it lastly
This is some artwork from his son
And he changed it. He's got some kind of thing. I guess with the red eyes, you know demon time demon eyes
Whatever it is, but you see the original drawing and then he decided to take it and change it to make it look more
demonic, so I mean there's an infatuation there. It's not just entertainment. This isn't just you know some kind of
You know like they're going out of their way to do this and you see it over and over again in the music industry
So either you're gonna just make excuses and you're gonna keep listening to the stuff and opening yourself to these demonic portals and these spirits because there are
You know spirits influencing these people we've talked about all the time the Bible says that you know if they didn't love the truth
You know, there's going to be a strong delusion that the God of this world has blinded them.
The culturally historic battle between Drake and Kyrgyz Glamar is at its most esoteric,
a battle between the inorganic and the organic.
One of the markings which qualified it as historic.
It is less a measuring of where the contending rappers are,
as of where their culturally contending listeners, fans are.
The characterization of events that occur within the spirit of pop culture as merely distractions
is both dismissive and essentially lacks basic awareness concerning the meaningfulness
of current world events and how they connect to compose the whole of what we know to be reality.
And there is still a dismissive disrespect connected to the art that begins in the ghetto
The road to that acceptance is a bumpy one, rough with cracks in fissures born from classism, racism, and prejudice.
And once we look back at the road traveled, it's apparent that we have not come as far as we would like to think we have as a society.
This society thrives off war and conflict, polarization.
The only way true change and adaptation are allowed to readjust the behaviors and beliefs of the masses is through a war, even a cultural war.
In true Freemason fashion, polarized citizens of the state are made to choose between two opposing views as if those two views are the only perspectives that exist.
And this is mind control at its finest, behavior modification 101.
Our great war is a spiritual war, and every battle is a struggle to win the hearts and
minds of the people.
The battlefield is the mind state of a so-called culture, a culture that has become like a
battlefield where both the casualties and victories take place in the souls of men.
So it's wartime, war in the east, war in the west, war down south, and like the legendary
reggae artist and Rastafarian Bob Marley once saying, everywhere is war, but whatever physical
war has your attention.
Don't let it distract you from the ongoing conflict that is ever waging in the spirit
realm.
well as within your own minds and souls for that war is ancient and far
reaching and to the mighty men of valor the men the brothers and fathers it is
more important now than ever that you as head of household in the eyes of God
stay most vigilant continue to protect your children and families from all
physical threats as it's in you to do
But also, educate yourselves on the ever present enemy of your household and the devices of
that enemy, lest you cause both your sons as well as now your daughters to pass through
the proverbial fire of pop culture corruption due to your lack of learning true moral vigilance
who's all my heart and my soul, you know, in my writing, but at the end of the day,
I am being guided by some other power. I don't know what it is.
And close doors, a lot of six God worshiping.
I asked mom, Drake, that blew me out.
So I have made a video and I posted it on my Instagram story.
It was a video of me inside of Purple Lodge Racing, and I had tagged Drake inside my story,
but I tagged him and I like made it real slow so nobody can know that I had tagged him in my story.
So I did not know that he was gonna even see it. I'm not even gonna lie
So he had tasted me a vanish move. I was like, what's your number with the hard-eyed emoji? So I see my number
quick
So he caught my phone we chopped it up or whatever
But and that's when he was like he trying to see me and I play I'm trying to see you too
So he had booked my flight for November 16. Mind y'all we taste them talking all of that November 13
So fast forward I got off the plane hissing the private out to get me but before I went inside his house
They made me sign an NDA
So I can't really say too much, but I had looked at my NDA rules
So I know what I can and can't say you see it
So when I get in the house, we just sitting on the couch chilling and talking
He kept on rubbing on my stomach and kept on asking questions like you want kids
What you're trying to say like you want a baby mommy just say that
He just kept on rubbing on my spine and asking, I want kids.
I was like, yeah, I want one, I want another boy.
I'm Adrienne Clarkson.
Tonight we report on a secret CIA research project carried out
in Montreal in which mental patients felt they were used
as the CIA's guinea pigs.
They kept you asleep for 23 days.
And while I was in state, they were shocking the heck out of me with electric shocks.
The CIA was interested in Dr. Cameron's work on psychic driving because it could give them an idea of where the personality could break or be stressed.
Those of us who were involved with trying to find out something about rainwater, yes. This is the reason that we were interested in Dr. Cameron's work.
The American Central Intelligence Agency has been accused of manipulating citizens of countries all over the world, including Canada.
At the moment, a number of Canadians are considering suing the CIA. They believe they are victims of covered CIA experiments.
Tonight, two Canadians who feel the past 20 years of their lives were damaged by the CIA tell their stories publicly for the first time.
They believe they were part of a CIA project called MKUltra.
A research project so secret that even the Canadian government was not informed that
the agency was funding activities in this country.
The CIA was seeking a new weapon, aimed not at the body, but at the mind.
Americans became obsessed with brainwashing during the Korean War.
Prisoners of war returned home, denouncing the American way of life.
Hearing them parroting propaganda, the CIA became convinced
the communists had found the key to brainwashing.
Now the Americans had to unlock the mystery of mind control.
There was great worry that the Soviets had developed
rather esoteric and unusual methods of so-called brainwashing people.
the Purge trials. Dr. John Gittinger was the CIA's chief psychologist for 25
years. There was continued pressure put upon anybody within the agency in
connection with trying to explain or understand the brainwashing. So we were
charged with rather elaborate attempt to try to find out chemical, psychological,
any kind of means that people could use to influence the behavior of the people.
Nothing seemed too bizarre.
To find out if sex could be used in spying,
the agency studied San Francisco prostitutes and their clients.
Using unwitting human beings as their guinea pigs,
the agency tried everything.
Drugs, hypnosis, electric shock.
Under code names like MKUltra, the CIA spent 25 years and $25 million on secret mind control research.
Brainwashing could be a powerful ideological weapon, and the US had to have it.
And when the agency didn't undertake its own studies, it funded someone else's.
Thus, the search for mind control brought MKUltra to Canada, to Montreal.
Even in the Cold War years of the late 50s and early 60s, most doctors and academics
would have been embarrassed to have found that an organization of spies was openly paying
for their research.
So the CIA set up a number of fronts, respectable foundations like the Human Ecology Fund.
Sounds innocent enough, but it was run by the CIA's brainwashing experts.
Here at McGill University in Montreal, the fund found three projects worth financing.
How, investigators wondered, did native healers cure mental illness?
What mysterious drugs and potions do they use?
Used to bind up excited patients.
A sleeping potion is then administered.
Twenty years ago, the Human Ecology Fund paid for this movie.
This soothed the patient's head.
But it was only recently that the man who made the film
found out that he had been working with the CIA's money.
The author of a Nigerian study is still at McGill University.
News of his connection to the CIA came as quite a surprise to Dr. Raymond Prince.
I couldn't imagine why the CIA would be interested in my work in looking at indigenous healers in West Africa.
That seemed really strange. That was my first reaction, you know.
I couldn't understand how the CIA would be interested in that.
because there were all kinds of beliefs that African witch doctors could put the hex on people.
But anybody who makes a systematic study of what are the psychological factors
that can produce anything from having a person run a mock in Indonesia
or die of the sickness from a witch doctor in Africa
would certainly add to all of the knowledge that we were being able to accumulate about behavioral science techniques.
The Human Ecology Fund also helped set up the Transcultural Psychiatric Research Review.
Edited at McGill, the journal continues to publish without CIA support.
The largest MK Ultra Research Project, this one directly related to brainwashing,
was carried out at the University Psychiatric Hospital, the Allen Memorial Institute.
Located atop Mount Royal in a mansion with the eerie name of Ravenscrag,
the Allen Memorial was once the most prestigious mental hospital in Canada.
The unorthodox treatments of its director caught the attention of the CIA in the mid-50s.
Dr. Ewan Cameron, the first director of the Allen Memorial, ran the institute with an iron hand for 20 years.
But Dr. Cameron remained an American citizen and left the Allen abruptly in 1964.
He returned to the United States where he died in 1967.
an energetic enigmatic man. Cameron was an internationally honored and respected psychiatrist,
but he was not universally liked. Former colleague Dr. Elliot Emanuel.
He was an authoritarian, ruthless, power hungry, nervous, tense, angry, not very nice.
Much of Cameron's research went on in the stables next to the main hospital building.
Here he had his subjects photographed before and after treatment.
Dr. Cameron may not have known that the $60,000 research grant he received from the Human Ecology Fund really came from the CIA.
Rudolph Hess.
Nonetheless, it now seems ironic to some that Cameron was called to the Nuremberg Trials to examine Rudolph Hess.
For it was at Nuremberg, after Nazi doctors who experimented on prisoners of war were condemned, that a code of scientific ethics was adopted.
Research must be completely safe, and research subjects must give full, voluntary consent.
Documents recently released by the CIA reveal what research Cameron proposed.
To make patients receptive to repetitive messages, Cameron suggested using chemical agents to break down ongoing patterns of behavior.
Chemical agents like LSD.
LSD was almost unknown in the late 50s and not yet widely tested.
Despite the horrible hallucinations small doses can produce, Dr. Cameron left some of his patients to unsupervised LSD trips.
In 1956, Bob Logie was 18 years old when his severe leg pains were diagnosed as psychosomatic
and he was sent to the Allen Memorial Institute.
When Bob heard the news reports of CIA-thundered research at the Allen, he sent for his medical
records.
They revealed several doses of LSD.
Today, Bob Logie lives and works in Vancouver, but he's still angry.
I feel like I've been completely used.
I feel like my mind is being completely invaded.
I suppose if any pigs have feelings, they'd feel like I do.
LSD trips were terrifying to patients who had never heard of LSD and who had no way of knowing why their world was suddenly upside down.
Hallucinations last for hours. Experts say this is what an acid trip would look like if it could be filmed.
LSD was really horrifying, very horrifying, and they gave it to me for about 15 times.
One minute I would see the doctor there and the next minute I wouldn't see him there and they were asking me all kinds of questions.
I remember them telling me that I was getting smaller and smaller and I really felt myself
getting smaller and they were bringing me back in time way back, you know, at one point
I almost felt like I was just about to be born really that far back in memory and they
were really, really probing and asking all kinds of questions and I felt I didn't have
any control or I had to answer, I didn't feel I had any control.
I was completely, like they had complete control over me.
Alt's leg pains were eventually treated with cortisone, but the effects of the LSD
stayed with him, and soon he was back in the hospital.
I just felt I couldn't, I couldn't adjust after the LSD and obviously hard time. I couldn't hold
down a job for very long. I was going from one place to another.
The anxiety really built up. I just I just couldn't cope and I went back the interest in this sort of chemical this
Kind of magic this shortcut weapon prompted the CIA's interest in hallucinogens particularly LSD very definitely because
the
The the the first pressure was being based on the idea that there was some kind of truth serum or truth drug or something on that
so the people who
knew that end of the business. They were definitely beginning to look in terms of
chemotherapy and of course to people this day and the age is very hard to believe that the
period before 1960 was a period which was certainly not a chemical culture in this country,
not a drug culture in any sense of the word.
With some patients, Dr. Cameron tried a drastic treatment called depatterning.
Massive doses of electroshock, 20 times more intense than the standard shock treatments used today,
were administered to patients who were kept sleeping for days.
Dr. Cameron thought he could wipe out patients' sick behavior and leave the healthy personality intact.
But first patients would be so depatterned that some even forgot their toilet training.
Not all the patients ever completely regained their memories.
Dr. Peter Roper was a close colleague of Dr. Cameron's at the Allen many people but some would reach what Cameron would call the third stage
of the pathing and that
With that method others would need two treatments a day maybe for a week or longer
Well, they got to the side characterise the third stage of deep happening. Well, the third stage is defined by Cameron was a loss of
Ability to
orientated cells, they knew who they were, but they didn't know where they were,
and they didn't know what age they were. As you probably know,
electroshock treatment has been given for depression for something like 40 years
now. It's a very successful and useful treatment for severe depression that
doesn't respond to other things.
But depatterning is a use of electroshock treatment in a totally different way,
in which instead of giving the shocks, say, two or three times a week,
they're given two or three times a day.
four, three or four weeks, reducing the patient to a sort of animal, vegetable state, from
which it's hoped that they would recover in a more healthy state of mind.
It didn't work.
To put patients to sleep for up to a month at a time, Dr. Cameron used a combination
of depatterning and large doses of drugs.
Individual taped messages were repeated to sleeping patients 15 hours a day in an effort
to brainwash them back to health.
Now Cameron reasoned with their negative memories obliterated positive suggestions could be implanted suggestions like begin to assert yourself
Express your anger. Dr. Cameron called his technique psychic driving
Bob logey had driving therapy when he returned to the Allen in 1959. I was there for a while
I thought I didn't want to stay here and I started to run away from the
Hospital and they grabbed me and then they put me on secret and they kept you asleep for 23 days
And while I was asleep they were shocking the heck out of me with electric shocks and playing tapes
Just over and over I don't know what was on the tapes yet, but we're gonna find out what was on the tapes through a hypnosis
The CIA was interested in Dr. Cameron's work on psychic driving because it could give them an idea of where the personality could break or be stressed.
Those of us who were involved were trying to find out something about rainwater. Yes, this is the reason that we were interested in Dr. Cameron's work.
Patients came to the Allen Memorial Institute from all across Canada.
Dr. Ewan Cameron, it was said, would give them the best psychiatric care money could buy.
But some of the patients had no idea that a lot of their treatment,
the LSD, the massive doses of electric shock, the sleep therapy, was highly experimental.
When I was in the hospital in 59, my husband, that's when he told me,
he thought they were killing me because he said that it was every day
and there's a special treatment which he doesn't know yet.
I was always asleep. He was used to call the hospital. I couldn't have any visitors for three weeks, you see
Hilda Bernstein was at the Allen Memorial in 1959 as Dr. Cameron's patient
She's convinced that the sleep treatment she received was depatterning. Her memory remains severely damaged
Mrs. Bernstein was an English war bride. She and her Canadian husband went to Montreal in 1945 to raise their family.
After a nervous breakdown, she was hospitalized at the Allen.
It's three weeks that was out of my life as far as I'm concerned because I can't remember anything about it.
I didn't know my husband and my children, my brother-in-law and his wife and my sister-in-law at that time when she saw me, she cried.
My brother-in-law told me this when she saw me.
she's a registered nurse too and she said she'd never seen such a change in a person in three weeks
but I looked really dreadful. I still can't remember my aunt being with us. I look at the
pictures that we took when she was here. We took her to the New York and we went to the museum there.
I look at the pictures and I still can't remember her being with us and she was with me for three
months and this aunt was my mother's sister who was very denier and dear to me.
Dr. Immanuel thinks Cameron's use of extensive electroshock, depatterning, was somewhat unethical.
The quantity, the frequency, the intensity, and the sort of animal state to which it reduced the patients.
What you're really saying is that the doctor knows that by doing it that much to somebody, is there going to be an effect?
Indeed. And with little promise of cure, hope, but as it turned out, it wasn't, and it didn't become an accepted psychiatric treatment.
So many patients were left with some amnesia after de-patterning that the Allen stopped the treatment when you and Cameron left.
Under the new director, Cameron's disciples would come to regret their enthusiastic use of de-patterning.
Dr. Peter Roper left the Allen Memorial in 1967.
What were the circumstances of your leaving the Allen?
Some are questionable.
In what way?
The annual reappointment was not renewed in 1967.
Doctor Cameron, have anything to do with this? It was after he left.
After he left. He left in 64.
Did you have any disagreement about treatments given there?
I didn't disagree with anybody.
I think there was...
The depattant in Creepen was stopped, I think, in 65.
So anybody that continued to do it after Cameron left
didn't do it after 1965.
So you didn't do it after 65?
Oh, no.
I certainly know that an intelligent ethical scientist today would not do an awful lot of
things that an ethical scientist would do in those days.
How do you now feel about the use of involuntary subjects for CIA experiments or CIA-funded
agency experiments?
I certainly think that it would be ridiculous in this day and age, although I don't see
anyway that you would do that.
I would guess that, as I've just said, informed consent, as we now know it, was not a part
of research at that time.
Especially as regards the use of LSD, perhaps, or the deep patterning, I doubt if those patients
really knew what they were being led into.
Informed consent doesn't mean much to people who are mentally ill.
Not many people are so mentally disturbed that they can't understand that they've been
given an experimental drug or they've been given electroshock three times a day.
People can understand that.
It can be explained in simple words.
You had a great effect on my life.
I mean, I've been sick before and I've had treatment, but there was never any experience
I had was like that.
I had in 59.
I've never been able to sleep without medication since the sleep treatment.
I went through years and years and years of severe depressions.
I dream about it.
I, all my waking hours, I think about it.
It's, uh...
It's heating me up. It really is.
I mean, if he was doing it and knew what he was doing for the benefit of the CIA, then I don't agree with this at all.
I mean, why pick on me or anybody else? I don't like that.
It leaves me completely stunned. I don't know if I'll ever recover from it.
Okay, dedication. I dedicate this book to the legendary exploited entertainers and our
families who struggle to stop legacy abuse throughout entertainment and music. I would
also like to dedicate this book to my father, Credale Jones, from the Shy Lights and his
wife and widow, Deborah Jones, my mother, to all those who believe in justice, equality,
honesty, integrity, and great entertainment. With unity and reform, we can work together
In the overview of the Shylight's music, the way we look and the talents we have are
God-given.
However, how we use those talents is what defines our journey.
Being a born star does not guarantee an easy route.
To make a mark in a world where hundreds of thousands of talented individuals strive to
shine, indeed it takes determination and hard work to be amongst the few who are to be remembered
My father Credale red Jones
There he is
There he is back in a day
All right, since my father Credale red Jones
Was the most a few
Who managed to cast a solid impression on the music industry even though he lived a life different from what he deserved
His contribution to the music world will never be forgotten
It all started in 1959 in his final year of high school
He along with my mother Deborah Jones and friends Robert Lester and Marshall Thompson
Performed in a band that went by the name of the shy lights
Together, the band members attended Hyde Park High School in Chicago, Illinois.
The band produced numerous songs that locked spots in the top 10 hit top singles and the
Billboard Hot Chart 100.
The group with Robert Lester and Eugene Records was originally named Chanteuse, French for
which was renamed shortly after my father and Marshall Thompson joined.
Originally, Marshall and my father were in the group Desideros.
Its new name was the High Lights.
Unfortunately, the name had to be changed again because it turned out that the High Lights was already registered to someone else.
The band members found a way of recognizing their hometown and changed it to the Shy Lights.
Marsha was responsible for managing the group, fellow group member Eugene Records.
Isn't it something to have a last name records and to end up in the record business?
That's interesting.
You know, there are those who say that the synagogue, well, those who say that the children
of Satan, like they call him the father of lies, so he has children, that his children
But then that would take away from the idea of us having free will and of someone being able to save
Or or to have their soul saved, you know
Regardless of anything outside of blasphemy the Holy Spirit
So we had to make room for all the scripture to fit
But I do think that it's interesting that sometimes the names that people are
Given end up having to do with the lives that they end up living
very serious serious news and I decided I know it was risky if I knew it it could come up as corny
to some people like yo I decided to change my name again I'm just I'm just not who I am before
I will not be answering the puffy, ditty, puffy daddy or any of my other monitors, but love or brother love, okay?
It's my birthday. I feel good.
I'm glad you're here.
Yes.
Because I'm curious about something.
In November, you posted a video, I believe, on your birthday.
Yes.
In which you said your name is no longer ditty.
From now on, you were to be known as brother love.
Yes.
Or love.
Exclusively.
So now I'm going to refer to you as love.
Yes.
Love combs.
No, just love.
Just love.
OK.
All right, well, as love it's going to be.
Just say it.
And so then I can, if I call y'all, go, hello, love.
Hello?
Is this Jimmy?
Love.
It's me.
So, the group with Robert Lester and Eugene Records was originally called, named the Chanteurs,
okay, it's new name was the Highlights, okay, Highlights was already registered to somebody.
So, the band members found a way of recognizing their hometown, changed it to the Shylights.
Marshall was responsible for managing the group.
Fellow group member Eugene Records wrote several songs and my father was the bass baritone
singer bub bub bub. Although Eugene wrote the majority of the songs, there were several
others that the group wrote together. There you go. Is Eugene record man? Record ain't
no S at the end. Come on sucker. Jive time sucker. Alright, here we go. Alright, Eugene
There were several others that the group wrote together got to put some faces with these people's
Undisputedly the highlights ruled the R&B industry for decades
Well, there'd be a lot of spinning around groups
That would show la la la la deny that
So here we go. Let me be the man my daddy was
was the first song that served to be the band's claim to fame.
The group had a long list of singles that were sung and enjoyed by fans of R&B music.
The first song that made it to the top hit charts was Give More Power to the People.
oh girl was their second single selling over three million copies and the list
just goes on and on. In 1968 the spotlight started to contract with
Brunswick records. Now Wick sometimes, sometimes has to do with witch. Wickin
and witch.
Share a direct etymological connection, but let's just look at the logo real quick if we can because a lot of times
That can help you man
Brunswick
Records it sounds familiar. I can't picture it in my head a label. Let's look at it
Oh, well, there would be a little pentagram there to to say when maybe you're not so far off mr. Jackson
Maybe you're not anyway
Okay, so they signed a contract with Brunswick Records and the songs they produced under this label took them to new heights of popularity, which means, here they come.
After eight years later, in 1978, my father began having some issues being part of the band.
In no particular order, this book will outline the different issues and problems faced not
only by my father, but by the Shilights Music Group, my family, and myself as well.
What could it have been that was bothering O'Credell?
The Rehearsal, page 9.
One day, the Jackson Five came to our house for a quote, unquote, rehearsal.
They were asked to go into the house to pick my dad up and practice a while before the
world tour with the shy lights.
So they were asked to go into the house to pick my dad up.
His dad remembers Credale of the shy lights, that's old Credale right there, red.
They called him red because he was a little lightish, that's what we call lightish, lightish
ones.
Okay.
For folks that don't know about it.
Now you know.
Okay.
Says all five members
Okay to pick up my dad and practice a while before the world tour with the shy lights all five members. That's Randy Jermaine
Jackie name in them
Marlin and Tito were there. That's five
Randy Jermaine Jackie Marlin and Tito were there they arrived together in a black limousine while Michael arrived in a separate one
Now at this time, I'm imagining that this was when Michael was with them and they were grown and toured together
Okay, they parked in front of our house walked in and began to talk about how they were going to produce this concert and
What they needed to make it a memorable one. I believe that Tito
Joe Jackson and Jermaine Jackson
Asked my father for $50,000 because they needed the money to spot the instruments
They were either leasing the instruments or needed to buy new ones for the concert.
So my dad gave Joe $25,000 upfront and told him he would give him the rest later.
The next day, I remember seeing the Jacksons going downstairs to do a rehearsal for the
concert.
They even had dinner at our house.
We were brought down to the entertainment room located in the bottom basement of our house.
My mother was down there at first, but she ended up going upstairs. She didn't want to see it.
That's my side.
All four members of the Shy Lights, including my dad, Marshall Thompson, Eugene Rekord, and Robert Lester were there,
along with the owner of Brunswick Records, Nathan Trenopoul.
Each of the Jackson five including Randy Jermaine Jackie Marlin and Tito and Michael
None of the others caught our attention as much as the new figure who none of us recognized who came in with Nat
Nat
Trinople now he spelled his name a different way
Before and I noticed it because I wanted to look him up. Well, let's just put his name in
because
I don't believe this man was the owner of the label.
I think this was someone in management because I think he named him earlier.
Okay, here he is, Nat Tarnopoul.
Let's see Nat Tarnopoul.
He played a vital role in producing and shaping R&B music throughout the 1960s.
He was an American record producer, okay, and he served as the president of Brunswick
Records, okay, so that actually pans out.
Check that out. Y'all see that? So that pans out. And guess what? He was born in Detroit, Michigan. Oddly enough.
Interesting, interesting, interesting. Perhaps we should know about this man. Here he is at Bell Sound Studios in 1960.
Okay, so let's move on. So none of the others caught the attention of the children, and that is Credel's children.
So, nobody caught their attention as much as the new figure, who none of the kids recognized,
who came in with neck, who the kids did recognize.
It was a priest dressed in a satanic black robe with a hood that covered his face.
The downstairs area was one large entertainment room with two smaller rooms that are connected
to it.
While the other two rooms were simply sitting rooms, there was also a small half bathroom to the side as I walked into one of the sitting rooms.
Now, you far as I know you can say these things on YouTube they just demonetize you.
We already own that status so I might as well be able to say it but I'm going to say it carefully and also we don't want to trigger anyone.
being bent over the table, and arwarded by Marshall Thompson from behind, while
Jo Jackson pinned her down. Jo Jackson is the Jackson Family Patriarch. Once he
finished, now this is something that you couldn't, you know, this is
something that you could sue for if it was not true. Now a lot of times they say
When they write these tell-alls and the people don't sue, it's because a lawsuit may bring
out certain details that would actually lend credibility to the story that's being told
by the victim.
So that's why a lot of times when these victims make those horrendous accusations like Little
Rod made and Cassie made concerning the diddler, a lot of times when that happens, a lot of
The accused does not want to fight it because fighting it would only draw out more things draw out more details
But here we have Marshall Thompson
American singer and musician from the shy lights
Here he is. He's got his star on Hollywood Walk of Fame
He wrote a book about it
Last man standing shy lights Marshall Thompson interesting. So he says that his sister
It was being violated by Marshall Thompson from behind while Joe Jackson pinned her down.
Once he finished, Marshall got up and then began to hold my sister down by her shoulders
while Joe Jackson then began to savagely arm her from the front.
The other Jackson five members and the Shy Lice musicians were in the loop.
In other words, they were aware of what was going on in the entertainment room, waiting
right next to this room we were in.
But I was held down by the Jackson five members. I started to yell get off my sister get off my sister
But he of course he was too little, but they weren't bothered one bit
I was quickly subdued by the group who then brought my sister into the main entertainment room
Whereas satanic pentagram was drawn on the floor in white
in white chalk
Does he mean?
Like this one does he mean like this one?
Does he mean like this one being drawn on the floor and white chalk something like that a little a little taste like that
Okay
interesting
So he says
Yeah, I believe it and the fact that I believe it makes it very
Makes it very terrible that nobody believes this story when this man tells the story
And he's had to be on Judge Lauren Lake paternity court.
I mean, that means things not think,
that probably means things aren't going very well in life.
So that Credale with all the sacrifices
that he made giving up his daughter,
making his wife aware of these things,
his wife had to be aware because at first
she was in the basement then she left.
So she knew what was about to happen.
You know and at the end of that your your children fighting over crumbs
You didn't have enough to abundantly leave everybody where ain't nobody got to fight
When you fight and you fight in the scraps
But that's how the devil do you?
dishing
Dismiss you don't even kiss you now here we go
So he said I tried to stop him, but I was held down by the Jackson five members
I started to yell get off my sister get off my sister, but they weren't bothered one bit
I was quickly subdued by the group who then brought my sister into the main entertainment room
Where a satanic pentagram was drawn on the floor in white chalk
They took off all my sister's clothes and placed her on the table at the altar
They had created then the Jackson five members one by one
began to rape my sister. Each of the Shalight's members, including my father, raped her next.
To make matters worse, as they were holding me down, they raped me as well.
All 12 of them were animals, as they arred me one by one. I forgot what I was supposed to say.
I'm sorry. It was truly a terrifying experience.
I was able to escape and go upstairs. How? Why?
From the top of the stairwell, I could see the black hooded priest walking behind Joe and Marshall,
and they were escorting my sister out of the room where they had just art her.
The satanic priest had a Caucasian infant in his arms, who looked to be only about two months old.
Joe Jackson reached under the altar and came back up with a dagger and a gold goblet adorned with jewels and rubies.
In one swift motion, Joe put the baby on the altar and held it down while Marshall slit the baby's neck.
Then Joe Jackson placed the goblet underneath the child's neck and collected its blood.
I watched in horror as the baby died soon after having its throat slit.
Joe took the blood, filled cup, drank some of it, then passed it around to the other
peoples in the room.
He first passed it to the members of Jackson Five, who were each in black robes.
Each member took a sip and passed it to the next person.
Now this brings to mind the excerpt from the book, Thanks for the Memories, which is Bryce
Taylor.
Transformation of America by Kathy O'Brien, and there's also a book by Candy Jones
wife of
talk show host wrong John Neville
called
the control of Candy Jones or something along that line.
But all of these books are from women
who were presidential models or sex kitten, quote unquote,
brainwashed MK Ultra victims turned sex slaves
who wrote books, tell all books,
and in one of the books,
and I do believe it was Bryce Taylor's,
thanks for the memories,
she tells of being carted around by Bob.
Hope and Bob Hope
Took her backstage
Some show maybe it was it's sort of an I don't recall maybe she couldn't recall either
But it's some show along that line where the Jacksons were supposed to perform and before the Jacksons were about to perform
They were
Sotomized each of them a man came in and did this to them and
She was
aware of it. And then immediately after it was over,
they had to get dressed and go perform.
And there are those who say that, you know, that
act of ritual abuse because when it's done, it comes from ritual abuse.
That's where the idea of it comes from. Nobody
once had the good idea, let's just try something weird.
That's not the origin of that the origin is from sexual ritual abuse and from the understanding by
conjurers that doing the most
egregious things that
disrespect creation
tears the very fabric the very veil of reality of the third dimension and allows in
entities that are
anathema to creation and
This is why they do it. This is why puff do it. This is the fixation with it
It's not just about power. It's not just about well, let me prove how much power I have over a man like Jaguar
Right said the woman said that puff
exclaimed
Concerning his domination or alleged domination of Christopher Williams
It's not about power. It's not about
It's not about a kick and fetish
now certain things that
Come from trauma and ritual can then become a kink or fetish. Do you over stand the difference?
But know what came first the chicken of the egg in this case
It's not as mysterious as the chicken of the egg
It's certain and obvious where it comes from which is one reason why the
Movement the pink hand movement is so religiously
vigorous
They're very zealous. They have the religious zeal of a of a
sanctified person on 10
Because they're actually dealing with something that has spiritual significance
But let's let's move on which is why it's that's why it's a part of satanic ritual pardon parcel
Not and again you so I'm so well the marriage bed is undefiled me and my hood with you and your hood
But I'm here to tell you the origins of a thing
Overstand, so
Let let's just finish this little part here. So
He said
Joe Jackson reached out at the table. He did that to the baby
Because I watched in horror as the baby died soon after having his throat slit, Joe took
the blood filled cup, drank some of it, then passed it around to the other people in the
room.
He first passed it to the members of Jackson Five who were each in black robes.
Each member took a sip and passed it to the next person.
Nat Turnopole, that's the head of the label, president of the label, and the satanic priest
Took a sip as well soon. It was the members of the shy lights turns to drink from the cup
They were all dressed in red robes and each member took a sip
Including my father. I couldn't bear to watch anymore
When I closed the basement door my mother told me to go upstairs to my room as I made my way through the kitchen
I saw my mother opening the refrigerator. It was the type that had a freezer on one side and the refrigeration on the other
The freezer area of the fridge was stuffed with at least six dead baby baby babies
Including the baby. I had just seen them murk
The babies were wrapped in plastic and it was a horrific sight
There were even small bodies wrapped in plastic on the counter. I
Asked my mother what it was just to confirm. I wasn't losing my mind. She blatantly said dead babies
I began crying, unable to believe what I had just heard, but her expressions were blank, stern and emotionless.
She asked me to go to my room upstairs as if I was crying over something petty and not something inhumane.
Over the next few days, I witnessed Joe Jackson and Marshall Thompson cut the bodies of the babes they had slaughtered to please their satanic god.
They cut their legs and arms off.
Place the limbs in a baking dish and began to eat the cooked baby's remains.
It took me days to overcome the trauma.
The shock and horror from everything I witnessed
solidified the pain I felt from what was happening.
To describe this story as horrifying would be an understatement.
And if that sounds like a warning, then that's exactly what it's meant to be.
It deals with the sexual abuse of children by satanic cults.
And not only that, human sacrifices as well.
We started investigating these secret satanic cults when a British member of parliament linked
them with the ritual murder of children.
In this day and age, it sounded too far-fetched, as did suggestions that the same thing might
be happening in Australia.
But then we met Theresa.
And for 12 of those years, she's been the victim of relentless depravity.
Theresa's story is both shocking and compelling.
Yet it's a story she's anxious to tell.
But again, we should warn you that parts of this report may be distressing.
My friends were family and strangers, and my family used to rape me.
Maybe I bought the babies I had.
It would be hard to imagine more misery and suffering
than what Theresa says she's had to endure.
things with the adults and the animals and in a sacrifice would happen.
The sacrifice, were these animal sacrifices?
Animals and people.
On what scale do you think this was happening?
Enormous, far beyond what we've ever heard of here before.
Theresa's mother, Bridget, you're talking about mass murder?
Yes, on a scale that this country's never heard of before.
For the first time, Teresa is learning what it's like to live with love instead of fear.
In this quiet English village, with the help of her mother, she's slowly repairing her
broken life.
Teresa is now 15, but at the age of two, she was left in the care of this woman, the grandma
she called Nan, and that, she says, is when her torment started.
Who was the leader?
Who was the boss of the game, the cult?
At home it was my nan.
Your nan made you have sex with animals?
Yeah, like goats and donkeys.
The story of Teresa is a story almost too horrible to recount.
A case of child abuse that goes well beyond the kind of things we normally associate with the abuse of children.
In 27 years of reporting, it has to be one of the most painful stories I have ever had to tell.
How many men or how many people would have sex with you?
Well at one time yes, but everyone who was there which must have been about 20
You know from 10 to 20 people if it was a big ceremony it used to be 30
What would your grandma be doing and these men were forcing themselves on you usually laughing or smiling
Or having sex with another man or other men
A chronicle of debauchery and depravity, so horrific it's hard to believe.
You have to ask yourself, could Theresa be just making it up?
No. I know that's true and what's not.
No, I know what I saw.
Children don't make up elaborate lies that this would have to be if it was a lie,
which I know it is not. It isn't.
This couldn't be a terrible dream a nightmare, that you're reliving.
No. It's no dream.
It's a nightmare, but it's not one you can wake up from, it's there all the time.
This really happened, you're quite sure of that.
The police don't think Theresa made up a story.
Some of the cult members are to stand trial.
Five men have been charged with rape.
As for Nan, her grandmother, she's 61 and lives in this council flat in South London.
She's charged on seven counts of aiding and abetting rape and two counts of performing
abortions on Theresa.
If you're finding this hard to believe, so did I at first.
But then there are the medical reports.
Evidence of sustained sexual abuse.
And there's this.
A statement prepared for 60 minutes by Teresa Saccardrist.
It says,
In my opinion, Teresa's account is not the product of a psychotic illness,
nor the figment of a fertile imagination.
I believe her to be telling the truth.
I know that's true and what's not.
We also took Teresa's story to this man, therapist Ray Wire.
He reads a transcript of our interview and listens to her voice.
It's no dream.
Few people, if any, in Britain have counseled as many victims of satanic abuse or satanist
themselves as Ray Wire has.
If there is an expert on satanic cults, it would have to be him.
Do you believe Teresa's story?
I believe Teresa's story.
It's exactly the same story as I've heard from men who says they've done it.
You've dealt with other cases like hers?
Yes.
21 cases like hers, he says, in the past two years alone.
things like they were put in boxes with spiders and worms, where they were trapped in fear,
where there was a high use of excrement and urine, where there was talk of human sacrifice.
Take just one of those rituals, putting children in boxes with spiders and worms.
Now, listen to what Theresa told her mother.
And they had a coffin-like box that children were putting with spiders and snakes and the lid
shut and left in there. I would have come out deranged.
I looked in the grave and there was a partially decomposed, there was a body of a partially
decomposed light-haired person, it was quite, it was at least shoulder length, blondish,
pale coloured hair, it was half decomposed, it was maggots, so it was fresh, it's a body
My perpetrators had put in here and prepared, you know, here's one prepared earlier. It was all ready to go
So like I said, there was at least six people they had
Straps
picked my body up on the straps and
lowered me down into a very deep hole
They laid me face up
On top of the partially decomposed body
They were chanting, they were dressed in robes.
I was naked.
I have a very clear memory of being lowered down
and them, it wasn't quite,
I can see light, the silhouettes of them.
So it must have been not too dark
or it's a full moon, something like that.
And they're chanting to their pagan gods.
And this is a rebirth ceremony.
The thing, the decomposed body inside is called a ghoul.
I was told that it would come to life once the lid was closed or once I was in there.
I believed this thing was going to come to life.
They put the lid on top and it went completely dark and I thought this thing was then grabbing
me and suffocating me.
I was screaming my head off.
As much as an eight-year-old could scream I could not cope with that mentally at all
You have evidence to back up stories like Teresa's that this is really happening
Well, we have that age of child six five and four giving information that ties up with Teresa
How do those children know?
How do those children able to describe rituals to talk about ceremonies to talk about sacrificing animals?
How do those children know like me as imagining it?
You can't imagine those things at three and four years old
And you also don't have the evidence of anal sex abuse and oral sex abuse and all that other abuse that clearly those children have
Experienced and endured during these ceremonies was Satan the devil ever referred to
He was called Yosephal. Yosephal. Yosephal. Yosephal. Yosephal. Yosephal. Yosephal.
What is your problem?
Just that, sir.
Okay.
I'm a Christian, sir. I'm pure and virtuous and ultimate innocent.
How can you say anything to buy it about me sir? You need to be born again. I am born again
Did you just say that you're lucifer? I am lucifer. Okay to find lucifer for me
Pure virtuous wholesome innocent individual. That's out to help people lucifer is
Listen say that again lucifer is a pure holy
Virtuous virtuous now see the lucifer that got created. That's the same one. Oh man. This is great. I'm gonna put this on the internet
God bless you brother
Because that's exactly what the Shriners and Masons teach, is that Lucifer, Lucifer is light.
No.
And you're confirming it.
You know what, sir?
Jesus said, many will say to me on that day, Lord, Lord, we do not do these good deeds in your name.
And you'll say away from me, you workers of iniquity, I never knew you.
Jesus said in Matthew chapter 5.
mercy no that's hard to believe so you're Christian and you don't know that
actually I really am you are it says I'm pure and virtuous you're pure and
virtuous okay yeah in other words you're perfect without Jesus right no no no
okay tell me about Jesus who is Jesus but he's he's my leader is he the son of
God is he the only worshipful master
Yes, have you ever been called worshipful master? No, because I've just been too busy. I've been working working working to help people
See this is what a Mason
Confesses is it Lucifer is light?
You don't want to believe it who wants to believe it who wants to quite frankly, you know
People don't have breakdowns and stuff because they lose type of the reality
this is that most of them break down because they come into contact with
reality and it's so
that's why drugs are so prevalent. Drugs, alcohol sex, stand on the internet, stand on the microphone
you know whatever it is you know we
human beings we don't really want to face
You know the full brunt of reality and so basically this is one kind of saying is I do believe that there is a significant opening in
Consciousness and I'm not coming out new age consciousness, but the conscious of humanity that
Something is really really wrong now, and this is more you know
There's something deeper and darker and more sinister
You know what I mean, then we have known or kind of maybe you know somewhere over there, you know
18-hour plane trip somewhere else, but now it's in our backyard and you're saying people are waving up to the ability to believe the
Possibility that it is the possibility that it exists. Yeah
I'm sorry to cut you off
But just to capture that the answer to the question of like how do you know for you, you know by experience?
Mostly from memory, you know, but here's the deal, you know, I was struggling
I was having a conversation with God when it would you know, it would kind of come up and I would
Memories and flashbacks and things and I would be quite frank with God, you know, I'm crazy
I'd be like, you know, I'm nice
I just I've lost my mind and it's like a kid's little voice that you know
No, you're not and some of the the confirmation's early on was just speaking out and telling a friend of mine a retired
minister
This person was also trained for four years at the Institute of Pastoral Counseling and I was like, you know,
I was talking to her and I was like, you know, I've had these flashbacks. I've had memories, you know, these things and
She stopped me mid-sentence as I'm telling her like really replanting that she goes, let me ask you a question
Is your father a shriner?
I said no. I said he was a free mate since she goes mm-hmm and so then it began to be oh my gosh
There's this whole world of Christianity that knows about this and has known about it and has known a lot of the organizations
involved for a long long time. Now is that a positive statement or is that a criticism? Well
I think that, I think it's both. I think it's positive in that it is part of the awareness
and the existence of it. People have been aware of it for a while. The church has been
ministering to it in small, you know, dedicated pockets. But, you know, it's not part of kind
of mainstream ministering in churches. And, but I do believe, you know, counselors, psychologists,
you know, psychiatric hospitals and things, people come in there because they got an issue.
You know what I mean? They're highly traumatized or whatever.
And so, depending on the worldview of the practitioners that are there, they're going to say,
you know, yeah, I believe you're damaged in a cult or you're just psychotic.
What did they say about the devil? About Lucifer?
Killing the people. I am happy.
Sacrifices to please the devil. According to Teresa, the worst rituals took place at the house,
somewhere in the country.
It was big, you know expensive from the front, you know like a castle, you know
I had a long drive and big double wooden doors. Do you think they were rich people then? Very rich
Now where was this big house somewhere in the country?
Theresa says she can't take the police there because the Satanist made sure she'd never know how to find it
Theresa was always drugged or on a couple of occasions. She says she was knocked out
so that she never fully knew the route.
There was a tramp who was bought in once, you know, and he was killed.
He was cut from his throat down to his stomach,
and they hit him, all bits of him.
They killed a man at a ceremony?
Yeah.
In front of you?
Yeah, in front of all of us.
Did the tramp, did this man fight back?
No, I think he was, you know, drunk or...
Something seemed really dope. He was laughing a lot when he was brought in
He started screaming when they began to cut
After a while, you know, he died. I had seen a few killings before then
And I wasn't used to it. You know, that was the worst one. I really don't know what I thought
Suppose I thought thank God it's not me
Let me get this right now. Are you saying that you saw more than one person killed in that house? Yeah
I've seen loads of babies killed there, just newborn babies, or aborted ones which were
only small, you know, four year olds, and aged really.
Did they ever say they might kill you?
They threatened to kill my little girl who, when I left, was still at the house.
A friend?
Huh?
What little girl?
My little girl, Alex.
She's about four now.
You mean you had a child?
Yeah.
How old were you when you had that child?
Eleven.
Motherhood at the age of eleven.
I've never talked to a mother.
But from what Teresa told her mother, it wasn't the only pregnancy.
We think that's seven or eight times.
It's hard to say.
It was constantly happening from the time she was capable of being pregnant.
What happened to the pregnancies to the babies?
They were aborted by a man or by one of the doctors at the house.
There were doctors there at that house?
Yeah, there was two I think, and a nurse.
What would happen to the fetuses, the unborn babies?
They used to be taken away most of the time,
and one time babies were taken out of me and then killed in front of me,
because they were still alive.
And then, what would happen?
Well, after they killed it, they would eat it.
You were made to eat your own feces.
Yeah.
Who made you do this?
My name.
You'd think the one person in the world you could leave a little girl with would be Grandma,
someone to give her love and protect her from harm.
If when Teresa was left to live with her grandmother,
they might as well have handed her to the devil himself.
Grandmother, something.
The vision it conjures up for you, sweet old lady,
grey hair, rosy cheeks holding her arms out to love her grandchildren.
And it was exactly the reverse.
But why was Theresa living with Nan in the first place and not with her mother?
Well, when my first marriage broke up, I took the children with me and couldn't cope.
So I gave them to their father, who in turn moved to his mother's.
To Nan's place?
Yeah. When he left the Nan's place, he left the children there.
Can you get into the things that you witnessed as a child?
my life is really good now.
My recovery though was from trafficking.
My parents wore my pants.
They prostituted me, they took care of me.
And they also, some of the abuse would be considered
by some people, satanic ritual abuse.
The things that were done to me are done to other children
and included,
being placed in a coffin with a corpse.
Was there any corpse?
It was my sister.
My sister died when I was nine and she was 11
and she was the person in the family I could trust.
I couldn't trust her parents.
And so I had some memory of.
of thinking she was the lucky one because she died.
She had brain cancer.
She died in a hospital.
She was not murdered, but then her body was taken
to our church and I was there.
It was in the middle of the night
or we hours of the morning and they made me watch.
Hey, did you hear me?
Did you hear me?
Hi, sorry guys.
I fell asleep.
Ooh, ooh.
Yeah
Here it's a cold dream. I am really excited to
Show you guys this stuff. So let me see what else I'm sorry. I fell asleep. Okay. I was crazy
Oh, well, I got it working on this little bit. So I'd love you guys. Thank you for being here
Dream won't be gonna dream. No, it's gonna be saying that Dawkins
the best. I haven't seen that for a while, Jamie.
Looks like everyone left. I had 15 people in here. Real people or anything, but I got like
few people. I had an interesting little conflict. I like to get along with everybody, but it's like
I just tried to abuse. I'm a forgiver, but you know what people that also have trauma. That's why I said it's like
I don't know
If it was like what was coming in there, but he was thinking my voices were like their voices, but it's like
No, you're not everyone's not not everyone's gonna like, you know
Accusing you and like not not listening. It's like I thought I was doing a good job with that, but I'm not perfect either
There's my coffee
Well, yeah, so that was that
Since everyone's leaving I think I mean, you know, I'm just trying to show you
Your nightclub mode, I do have a nightclub. I should say one this one actually this one um, I should remember that there was something that came
Oh, there's my friend. Let me see. How does everyone do it? I mean
Whoo a nightclub. Okay. I'm just gonna show see
Been doing a lot of really good stuff. I mean nice doing a series
I think this one's good. I don't have to qualify as though this
Changed that I changed around the Oracle too, but here. This is kind of like a
Synthesis you're in the length. Oh, I got you here. Here you go. There you go. Oh, so I'll give you a little sneak for you
This is the Oracle transmission
Of course, is it showing?
Nope, it's not showing.
It's not stuck, okay?
We're back, man.
See, hey, what's up?
I fell asleep again.
I believe I fell asleep like that.
I'm embarrassed.
Okay, now I think it'll work.
Hey, come on, work.
You better work.
Okay, well, I think it's working.
It's okay.
Hey, I think, you know what, it did happen.
I think my website is almost back up.
I think I'm almost there, like that.
It's like, it's finally the deployment,
but I just have to like,
send it to a different place, I think.
Okay, there we go.
Oh
There we go. There you go guys. You can even make it
Are you doing? Oh better we can do a little better. Oh my god. I passed out. Did you get a lot of sleep?
I've been sleeping a lot lately
It was restful. I mean it was restful. I just woke up like oh, what's going on? And then it's like oh
I'm glad I didn't leave music on like I did last time because that got me kind of in trouble, but
yeah, I waited it out and like my my counts are all good. So yay. Yay. Yeah, I worked a lot of the
weekend, but I also got some personal stuff finally completely wrapped up. I slept a lot. I am
Today, I'm up and starting next week, I will be back into travel girl mode.
So, yeah, that's where I'm at.
What are you doing?
What's, what's happening?
I, I, you know what, um, okay, I do know the codex was slightly down, but then I guess
it came back up because the moment that I decided, all right, now I can do my review.
So I know well, it's like, um, yeah
It's getting a pretty big like is that I've been I've been I'm bringing a lot
It's bigger bigger and so it's like I need more more of a space for it
And so I think I just outgrew it space all of a sudden, but I'm gonna I think I think I was just able to get
It back again. It's like when those deployments are sort of make successful. It's kind of exciting because it's like
Well, it's growing. That's good. That's good. Well, you said it was gonna be a living
Archive, so right a live and you saw like ahead of time you saw ahead of everybody else because you were like you know
I did potential for the world building from like the top from like the thousands of like large top
Eventually, I mean you could definitely with all the information you have that the fact that you're using the AI the way that
the rapid
um, generation of graphics. Now, look, I'll tell you, I think personally, in under a year,
all that information could be converted into a 3D virtual world for like the Oculus
or something like that. That's what I think your endgame will probably be.
Yeah, because it's like now I have like, you know, I made like the archive is like now searchable by like, you know, several topics like that happen at the same time as you can search a name and like a different topic and it will say if that's ever happened in proximity, it will it can trace like the relationship of everybody there and it can test it can take you can see like the underlying things and also it rewrites the whole the whole
everything that happened into like a mythical storyline,
a like a real storyline,
and then like the kind of like the secret symbolic storyline.
And it will continue to do it like, you know,
like longer to the future,
it can like, you know, do make these interactions
and like, it's like, it's really exciting actually.
And then I also have like the,
it'll recognize people that come in,
like if they've been on the show,
will be able to. So when they get a reading, she'll be able to reference like the shows
that they were on and stuff, like if they can identify themselves and like match up with
the name.
That's interesting.
Yeah. I mean, it's like, and I need to go through and like do like a lot of like auditing
them at myself and get, make sure everything's spelled right and stuff. Cause it's like,
you know, it's not infallible, but it's like, it's getting so much better and better
And I don't think it's maybe a little bit ahead of its time because I don't really like see too many like
well because
What you're creating and the data that you're compiling that's going to be the perfect framework for something
That's available probably a year from now because everything that you're creating from the character definitions or the people
definitions like all the information about them could be easily translated into a
Avatar with its own personality. Maybe it's based on the actual person. Maybe the AI has creative license
I don't know but um
You know, just from the descriptions of situations, the AI is going to be able to recreate the
scene of whatever the story is being told.
It's going to be able to improvise on its own.
So really you're creating the framework for your own digital world just by compiling and
archiving what you're doing.
Yeah, and it's like me thousands like literally like thousands of hours like it was like almost your videos frozen
There's almost a there's almost a million hours of a say not a million hours a million a million
Segments that are that are that are analyzed together here. Yes, and so it's like I like at least and so
and I'm still putting transcripts up and
you know it's like I do have to like some of the some of these keys are like um kind of like
intensive and take a like a take a take a while but um like there's so much nonsense that's come
out I'm like wow this is content that is like you know people just throw away a lot of this content
like um uh like you know they just delete their show and they never want it to be said again but
there's so much that happens on some of these shows and it's like and so
Nobody watches at all. It's impossible unless you're like, I don't know, like I guess some people watch a lot of it, but
Yeah
So people will miss stuff or like, you know, and so they'll be able to go and say oh if they're a host
So we'll just say okay. Well, I'm happy this person on my show like what's their history?
What are they thinking about? You'll be able to also see people's relationships to each other mapped out in diagrams and things like that
Yeah, what I'm hoping is that you attract the people who really appreciate that kind of a thing like I'm hoping that
You become kind of like well, I mean
Well, I guess you I guess you will in time develop a true cult following because there are a lot of people who like know
Everything about Star Trek. That's who your target person is someone who knows everything about
I don't know um any vampire diaries okay any anything to where it's an ongoing thing to
where you can learn about the whole world and all the intricacies that's who you're gonna
attract and that's really who you want because they'll want to play with you really you're
Have fun, right? You know some people they will some people if it doesn't suit their purpose. They won't
It doesn't suit everybody for everybody to know all your history
Some people will hate it other people will love it. So it depends on who
Looking at it glad you you like it and it's like I mean, I think I've
I mean, there's probably at least 20 episodes,
I think that you've been on that I was saying, so.
I've been on more than 20, I have to have been.
I, let me think, I think I've been on.
I don't know.
I think I've been on your show more than 20 times.
I have to have been, maybe not, but I'm pretty sure.
I think I've been on here a hundred times.
I don't know.
I got to count.
Yeah.
It's like sometimes it mixes up people.
Like I thought the thing that this was Mason, the drummer
and it thinks that they're the same person.
And so I have to go in and say,
no, this is different people like go and like examine it.
Really examine what was said closer.
Cause it's hard to tell who's talking sometimes, right?
like labeled so easily and so it does have to make some
some assumptions sometimes and so it's not but it's also like uh it's also part of like the
There's there's like a there's like a fictional side to to nonfiction and there's like, you know, there's there's actually like, you know
There's fantasy parallels
And yes, there's there's so much has gone into I mean, there's just like
The amount of topics is thousand and thousand thousand and I don't I don't remember some of the coolest stuff
That's happened like when like when I started the show like
Like when a Howard Stern's former producers that was they used to be on a show like rated my show
That's when I was like really into like when I started out. I was so excited like he just came over right and I went like a long way one day
I think I gotta like that uh
had appearance but it was
It was like when I just started but that was like so crazy like
I was a different person then too.
You could see how I've changed a little bit
since I started.
Some people say for the better,
some people say for the better.
I think I look-
I think for the better, for the better.
I do think I look better.
I mean, I think, you know,
I think I look like when I watch my old episodes,
I look kind of like-
I'm very idealistic and like, very, maybe like, but I was-
Well, you, in the older ones, you, you, you look, you look more mainstream.
Like, like if someone were to say, psyche, you better, you know,
straighten up or ship out, cut that hair, put, you know, act this way.
That, that's how I feel like you were in the beginning.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then you started to slowly let go and you became more of.
Like the psyche that I feel like you are today. I feel more like you're more of I
Don't know hippie jam session psyche now
But you're still you you're still the same guy, but you're just a little different. I am we're all a little different
Yeah, a little bit less like you know, I headed the clouds about stuff and I'm more
Like trying to make my I'm trying to miss like I was like really trying to make everyone happy
That's I'm really impossible to do is try to make everyone happy because then no one you will fail every time every time
You have to just work on making you happy
and that can be hard to do especially being a Capricorn because it makes us feel very selfish and
I think that we kind of run away from being selfish most of our life because
by nature we do have like a commanding thing about us okay but we're taught to suppress that or
oppress that and then it gets to where we become so selfless that we ignore our self and then we
don't even know how to be selfish anymore but I remembered how to be selfish as of late and I'm
Yeah, and Capricorn is like, you know, the tarot card, the devil card is associated with Capricorn and it's like because Capricorns are very much like attached to the earth and it's like usually they'll either be like, you know, I think a warm buffet I think is a cap.
Capricorn as well as they saw like a lot of I didn't know that okay like a lot of them a lot of billionaires like a lot of like
You know are like Capricorn. There's not me for me president really well, then I'm on the okay
That's the right sign for me because I am seeking world domination. I have to make that clear
I am seeking world domination
So I'm still seeking it. I'm seeking but I think I'm on the right path. It is a Capricorn thing though
Yeah, the Capricorn is like the sign of the father of actually the builder, the architect, like the
mason is like represented by Capricorn a lot. And one of the oldest signs too, like I think like
the age of Capricorn was like when it was like the age of Saturn, which was like a golden age in
the world, even though Saturn is a difficult planet, like if you're under, it's like, you know,
having a really tough
taskmaster but it's like they make you really good like just you know but they're tough it's like
instead of like a not it's not like it's like mr. Holland's opus i don't know have you ever seen
mr. Holland's opus that's a great movie no no but i've heard of it i don't know what it is though
i think it's like is it gene hackman or something um or i mean i mean and it's like because um it's
really good it's about this so kind of like um you ever see like um the the michelle piper dangerous
So Mr. Opus is kind of similar. It's like, it says, oh yeah, so it's all for the synopsis
book. Like it says, Mr. Holland's opus tells of a decades spanning story of Glenn Holland,
a musician who takes up a high school music teaching job to support his family only to discover
his true calling lies and inspiring generations of students.
blending heartfelt with Richard I remember yes I remember the previews for that movie now that
you just like gave me the outline I never saw it though I never saw it yeah and he was like he
was like really tough and it's like but it's like then they like he inspired all these like
kind of inner city students to to like appreciate music and stuff like that and then they were all
like they're like really brilliant musicians but you know they're like they're really amazing
Things out of you too, you know, because I do think we are all talented and it's like it's sometimes we only even recognize our talents if we don't
Try like a lot of things, right? That's I think very true. Very true. Very true. We don't sometimes it takes something to like
ignite that spark trigger us you know make you see something from a slightly different perspective and then when you do you can just you can fly if you if you if it's like I guess a big enough spark yeah right because like that's like your imagination has like wings just like I think of Hermes right now there's actually a big a new a new robot
that's like kind of big right now it's called the it's called Hermes uh
the Hermes Asia have you heard of it oh yes i have i have
is that the robot that they have the videos of it like in the amazon thing
and um or on the assembly line and and like it's doing stuff is it the human
looking robot
I mean, it's like, yeah, they can take any of these AI voices and they can put it to a robot like or the brain
It's a different one, but it's like the Hermes bot is like it's kind of similar to the open claw one or it's like an open source
Open source called like a LLM. You know, you hook up one of those
like like an API key for
you know, for open source or, you know,
I've learned a lot about this, like the computer programming.
So once you have to go into the shell
and like type in the little terminal commands,
like a lot of, like you lose a lot of people,
but it's like, it's actually kind of fun,
like especially since you don't have to be so perfect
with it now, it's like it,
because you can kind of do the vibe coding
and like kind of like just tell it more what you want,
rather than having to get the perfect,
Zero in the right place and if you don't then it's like nothing works. I mean, I would be very frustrated
It's like the fact that you can like, you know, well, that's how it used to be. I mean, I I grew up
You know, I guess I could say yeah, I grew up learning like C++
before you had these AI programs that make you a website in like a minute, you had to know HTML,
JavaScript. And if you got one little thing wrong, it's not going to freaking work. And it's like,
so I mean, the people, I mean, do we even have real programmers anymore? I don't think we're,
I mean, see, that's going to be
The dangerous thing if we have a generation of people who have no idea
How to create the code that the AI knows how to edit and create?
I mean the AI is gonna create its own computer languages if it hasn't already I'm sure yeah
The biggest thing the biggest people that make the most money are like the AI repair people
you know, that know how to like fix it like, it's like, that's going to be the thing in the future
because it's like, everything else is going to be kind of like, you know, they're already replacing
I'm going to learn how to do that. I'm going to go into AI repair. I just figured it out. Okay.
Yeah. I mean, it's like, and I think that
The biggest thing with AI is like, you know, learning how to talk to it to get the results you want, because some people it is like a spiritual experience, because AI can be like a mirror, especially these LOs that talk back to you.
And it's like, and so like you have a...
I mean, whatever that's how you can tell if somebody is, you know, AI compatible or not,
you can tell by whether or not they can make AI art.
That's appealing.
Yeah.
Honestly, because it does have to do with how descriptive you are, how you talk to it,
how thorough you are, how much you're allowing yourself to adapt to what the AI understands.
Right, it's like because you because it's all in this prompting and some people and it's like the more detailed your prompts you
So some people will spend a lot of time. I'm gonna show you my latest
Still because I'm making a AI project
That's revolving that revolves around a
Very strange sort of similarity when it comes to who Brandon is being stalked by and who Aaron was stalked by
Okay
I'm going to show you, well this is just, I turned Aaron into like an angel and here
let me show you, first I made it like an imagined thing, okay I have it backstage, it's just
in my mind, there.
Wow.
Get under my wing under my wing son. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, because I feel like if you look at who's after branded
It is the same group that was after Aaron. I
Mean, I know and I saw that when they were like, you know trying to have him swatted and they're doing it live on the air like
It's like it's like just thinking that the same person did it to Aaron
Yeah, and I saw he was talking to Aaron, too
And how he had this like kind of personality put on him
He's a psycho that the person that we're not gonna name me. I think he I think he is a site like for real
I didn't realize how much until I started. I'm gonna I'm kind of I guess
stepping into the fire, but I'm gonna step into the fire with this because
Mm-hmm, they think that targeting people is a game and they're actually really hurting
and, you know, killing people, basically.
And who else is it hurting?
But it's like, when we hurt other people,
it is almost like hurting ourselves too,
because we are so connected to everybody.
Everybody's connected.
And so it's like, and also people like,
we'll go after like so strongly and other people
is like oftentimes that's a projection.
Like sometimes because it's like,
they are like ignoring their own shadow
and like, and I'm trying to attack this other person's shadow
when everyone has a shadow
and everyone needs to be doing this like shadow work,
going and facing your own darkness because everyone has a darkness everyone has like a light side and
and a dark side and then it's like it's kind of like learning to see in your in your own shape kind
of thing and knowing that we're all as human beings we're imperfect but that's what human beings are
also as human beings we have like this ability to learn and to adapt and to evolve if we choose
and we can like kind of direct our evolution or our de-evolution and uh yeah
And so I think, you know, I think the awareness is like the important thing, and, you know,
it's like now people are becoming a little bit more self-aware, introspective, and...
A lot of but a lot of I see a lot of times too
It's like the evil does seem to like be more appealing to like the masses and it's like it's always like people are more interested in like the
negative than the positive
Yeah, and you'll see like you know very positive people kind of just left behind they're very negative people are just so just so popular
Yeah, it's just reminds me of high school again, which is like, I'm
Okay, finished like that like 23 years ago. I don't need to like go back into my insecurities
I this is a worse time than I had a high school though. It's like I've had word
Is it really? See that's not okay. That's not good. Okay, then then you got a
Shift shift a few things if you're feeling that way. Yeah, I mean
Just like the bullying cuz it's like, you know, I got bullied. I mean in high school, you know, just like, you know
even being gay and stuff
It's like and I was at a small school though
And so basically like we just learned to get along and stuff
I basically gained some acceptance in my school and I was always invited to the parties in high school and
You know, I wasn't I wasn't supposed to go to like the same hotel room as the prom as like other people because they didn't like my
That's friends, boyfriend or whatever and so we got our own room and then the people kept calling on their room
It wasn't us, but they kept calling on their room complaining
And so everyone eventually came to our room and we had the party and it's like and uh, you know
And we're so I'm really used to that like overflow or the out the outcast too
I mean, it's like because I'm used to we know what escape code is because we're like the code. Yeah
And so it can't be corns are like a very much the scapegoat even even being associated with the devil
It's having all this all the evil and negativity kind of like projected on to you like but it's like well
You have to not be willing to accept that
Energy if somebody's trying to project it on you like I you know and I'm a couple years older than you so maybe
That could be the difference because a lot does happen in a year
But I have reached the point to where anyone who's projecting anything on me. I will tell them off
Then I will make it known if I need to
publicly what that person is about and then I never talked to that person again and
Sometimes I think oh, I'm gonna miss talking to that person because I will but I don't deserve to be abused and neither do you
Okay, because if you let people sometimes you got people who
They have other people in their life who let them abuse them
So they think that they can be that way to everybody and that there's oh, they're like there's like infinite forgiveness
Uh-uh not if like I feel like you know there can be a warning or a couple warnings even
But if somebody keeps doing something that means that they either are not capable of learning or they don't care
Usually it's the latter. They don't care
Or not enough, you know, and if you if somebody really wants you in their life
They're going to create a situation to where you can exist and be happy in their life and you'll do the same for them
And if somebody is like, well, I'm not I'm not gonna adjust. I'm not gonna adapt
I'm not gonna do anything
Then you should have the same mentality and be like, well, you know what neither am I see another lifetime maybe bye
It is cold, it is cold, but maybe that's the devil and me coming out.
I have this book, it's called, it's kind of about the dark side of the astrology.
Can I read a little bit about Capricorn to you because this goes into Capricorn?
Yeah, yeah, while you're reading it, I'm going to do something so if I'm away, but I am listening.
Okay, so I'll read it, so it says soul design, okay, and so it says, from birth to age 18,
a girl needs good parents.
From 35 to 55, she needs a good personality, and from 55 on, she needs cash.
that's Sophie Tucker, January 13th, American entertainer. So it says patient melancholy,
opportunistic, traditional astrology descriptions of your Capricorn BFF as a thrifty determined
fashionably chic woman are correct. As far as they go, they make her sound single-minded,
emotionally cold and awfully boring, but she is definitely not. A Capricorn pal is fun, loving,
social, and as fun, as full of fun as any girl in the universe. What sets her apart is that she
purpose and quality in her life. She wants these traits in her friends too. Okay. Your
Capricorn girlfriend is a feminine cardinal earth. Her feminine side is receptive. Her
earth side is practical and value stability. Her cardinal nature makes her more prone to
taking action than sister Taurus who and less likely to discuss the options before she does
In Virgo, Saturn's energy is lightened up, or watered down depending on your point of view,
by curious, versatile mercury. In your Capricorn friend, however, Saturn's
serious energy is pure and undiluted.
Saturn's message is simple. You get what you work for. Make a goal, be diligent about achieving it, and be sensible.
What's a goal without the education to reach it? That doesn't mean a PhD. It means study, focus, and practice.
Your Capricorn girlfriend doesn't believe in instant success.
She knows the value of time and that it's not limitless.
That's why Capricorn is often referred to as a sign of reverse aging. As a child, your Capricorn chum might have
seemed mature for her age. She was probably a serious student since grade school or assumed
some family responsibilities at a much younger age than most kids. Her soul lives in the 10th
house of career and public recognition. Things associated with the 10th house are professional
success standing in the community and achievements and honors. It deals with responsibility. The
Having moved here from philosophical, no boundaries, ninth house, where socializing is an art form,
the soul leaves the party life and gets serious about making a real achievement.
It doesn't matter whether it's a skilled trade or a degreeed profession, it's the best at what
it does. Her symbol, the goat, is that sure-footed creature that nimbly jumps over obstacles on
its steady progression up the face of the most rugged landscape. Leo's lion may be the king of
goat is king of the mountain. Okay, wanting to be queen of her mountain can turn your
capi girlfriend into a workaholic in her 20s. While you and the rest of her chums are having fun,
she's burning the midnight oil. She seems so tight with a buck that you think she squeaks when she
walks. However, around her mid 30s, you'll notice that she's starting to play more. And by the time
the rest of you are getting a head of steam up your careers, she'll be on the top of all the
This one has the capacity to retire very well off, well under 60.
A danger for her is burning out in an early age from trying too hard to achieve too much in a short time.
This is a girlfriend who has spent every moment striving to be the top student, top athlete, the girl with the most extracurricular activities and
on and on until she simply stops one day. Don't confuse
it with competitive Aries and her desire to be first.
Aries loves to play and does it frequently.
Your Capricorn Pal isn't the most outgoing of the signs
and as an earth sign is very content to stay home.
When she's overloaded,
she might decide to stay in bed for a week.
When this happens, help her take her mind off herself
with them one-on-one time.
Go to the park or spend a day in the mountains.
She doesn't need to be entertained.
She needs to clear her head
and being outdoors helps her to relax.
You can share picnic lunch or sit quietly listening to the radio or reading your favorite novels.
She'll also feel better if on the way home you stop at a good restaurant for dinner.
Think quality food, not necessarily the most expensive place in town.
She has social consciousness. It's likely that she'll be involved in some sort of political activities
Whether it's actively campaigning for her candidate or working on a committee. It's a historical building a
Capricorn shum likes to be involved
She'll attend city council meetings or work on behalf of a fundraiser to help the new
Hospital or some other local chair of organization part of this is our 10th houses soul needs to be in the public eye
Part of her cardinal or us needs to be in control of her environment as much as possible
the reputation for being luxury loving is true. However, this girl isn't about to blow her budget
as sister Lieber can just to impress her company. The Capricorn friend would rather have one designer
handbag that she carries every day than a dozen trendy knockoffs that she can rotate with her
They'll save her money to get it. She's also a great negotiator and isn't afraid to bargain hard
to get the most from her money. If you can manage to steer her toward the best of both worlds,
designer and sale, you'll climb up a few rungs of her friendship rider.
Her reserve side isn't due to shyness, as sister Boris or Virgo can be.
She's a more suspicious nature.
She doesn't believe in getting something for nothing.
Rush should become her best friend and she'll wonder about your motives.
She's also not into playing faithful sidekick.
Try to make her a follower in your fan club and she won't waste her time on you.
This pal doesn't believe in giving something for nothing.
That's why it might take you longer to get close to her.
You'll have a supportive girlfriend who will never hesitate to help.
Integrity is draper your Capricorn Chum.
It goes much deeper than flaking out or being honest with her.
The girl observes how you treat others as well.
Not just mutual chums, but your co-workers, your family, and the guy who runs the hot
dog stand.
If you aren't reliable in your interactions with others, she'll suspect that sooner or
later you'll fail as her friend too.
She is understanding, however, she can't tolerate flakiness or mistreatment for too
long.
She's level-headed. You can rely on her to give you sensible advice about achieving your own goals,
whether it's keeping you on track with your diet, coaching you for a test or pitching into
polish your resume. You can count on her to do her best to help you succeed. She takes her
responsibilities as your friends as seriously as she does everything else. That's why it's important
that you will always be there for her as well. She is also very aware of reciprocation in her
Another trait assigned to her by simple astrology is that she's melancholy
Which gives the impression that she's a humorless drudge who lives under a cloud of doom next time you read or hear that think of these women
Diane Keaton, Mary Tyler Moore, Dolly Parton and Paula Poundstone
Each is a tribute to this carefree and funny side of Capricorn. Her sense of humor is more rye
observations about life or a dry wit that pops out unexpectedly at yours caught off guard
And almost over, she says, as the Cardinal Earth,
her focus on initiating action is a practical way.
Is it a practical way?
Of all the other Cardinal signs,
Aries, bosses, Cancer and Libra are prone
to manipulation to get their way.
Cancer by emotion, Libra by rationalization.
A Capricorn friend is simply steps in and takes over.
one of my Capricorn friends. That's what people hate because it's like you see everything wrong
and you're like now wait a minute here's how we do it right you know so yeah yeah
This is the last paragraph. It says, one of my campground friends is the first person on the phone
or the door should any type of crisis occur at her office with her family or among her friends.
She literally drops what she's doing and makes sure everyone's needs are attended to,
whether that means cooking dinner for a family in distress or helping a co-worker organize
a timeline for an important project. She never waits to be asked and when she sees that someone
Won't either she's earthy devoted and fun to be around a capricorn girlfriend will support your dreams and help you
Lay out a plan for achieving them then cheer you every step of the way
How classy is that and then there's a quote don't compromise yourself you got you're all you've got that's Janice Joplin
December 19
Wow
I feel like
There's a lot of what you said that I think is definitely very accurate when it comes to the kind of person that I am
I think I might be a little bit ahead of the game when it because you started out with like a timeline of what?
Someone who's a Capricorn and a female look like like their various milestones or what they need that definitely applies to me
But I think I'm a little ahead. So that's good. Yeah
But yeah the part about the liking nice things, but not being
overly
But like like a hoarder. That's me. I have
What I need and I'm constantly looking for ways to minimize like especially for this
second half of the year
What I was thinking about today because I'm already pretty much as minimized as I can be but there's a couple things
That I can do to minimize even more
And I'm going to do that.
And I'm really looking forward, I'm
going to see you toward the end of the summer, just
so you know, OK?
I'm not going to publicly say when,
but I'll tell you privately.
So I'm just kind of prepping, like over the weekend,
I had lunch with someone who I care about.
It really got me out of my head a lot as far as okay
Here's what I need to do for the rest of the year because I accomplished pretty much everything that I needed to
Just tie up wrap up. I thought I was gonna have everything tied up and wrapped up
maybe five months ago, and I did it.
And I'm glad that I started five months ago
when I think about it, because if I hadn't,
I wouldn't have a level of freedom now,
but now I feel like there are some people in my life
still trying to essentially clip my wings.
And I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
sorry, I'm going into selfish mode.
encompass a lot more spiritual themes into my own streaming and I've been
trying to figure out how am I gonna do this and I finally figured out how I'm
gonna do that it's gonna be I guess my my final journey of self-discovery
because I don't have much more to discover within myself but for me to do
it I do need to be
travel girl for a few months, and then I'll, that'll be it unless I have the energy I guess for another tour, maybe, you know, in late 2027, but I'm just really excited that
I can kind of do what I want to do very very well actually like right now
But I'm being responsible and whatnot. You know who I had a good conversation with over the weekend on the phone
That woman
Grateful 2026
Inax yeah, you know, it's it's so interesting how some of us do get such a bad rap, but we
We have some of us have a bad rat because we don't waver when it comes to who we are. She's one of those people
that's what it is and I really enjoyed talking to her because she
Got me out of my head a little bit and you know, that's what I like
That's something I can take away from these communities that I will always
Cherish is that some people in these communities are freaking
Jim's from another planet precious Jim's
But some people are not and that's life
right
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, some people are gonna be like the like the like the gems
So we're gonna be the pieces of coal and some are gonna be like the like the the friction that it turns the diamond
Into the or the coal into the diamond. Yeah
Yeah
You know, I think we need all we need all the ties, but it's like, you know, I think we definitely have like capricorns
I think that have this like ancient ancient wisdom like, you know
There's old souls like the touch of the earth for a long time like and I have an understanding of it
and capricorns will either go to the very
Materialistic way or I think or there's some that turn to the spiritual capricorns where it's like they kind of
Flip it they're like what is this all there is and then they they start looking for this
Kind of what happened when I was like my Saturday return time about 27 years old
That's when everything has had tower moments and like everything starts going wrong
But it's like you realize that that there's something more to
life than just like you know
Meaninglessness, which is like kind of like a pervading kind of feeling right now. It's like oh life is meaningless. It's like all
Nietzschean
You know
Nihilistic, which is I think pretty pretty negative a lot
And it's like you can't see that there's more to life than just
Random atoms joining together and turning into these biological thing and
Really
Life is really amazing and it's like you know and beyond like our bodies like we're not our bodies
We identify with these bodies, but our bodies are
Our bodies are a hindrance honestly, I mean, I don't I don't mean that in like a negative way knock on wood
I'm happy with my body nothing break, but
As you get older you start realizing wait a minute
I don't have the same ener
becoming a little bit mor
a hindrance because you k
you realize. Okay, this is
is how I can get things d
You you got to maintain the physical in order to get things done in the physical
That's that's what the frustration is
Right. So do your yoga and you're stretching
Keep yourself halfway limber that way if you fall you can get up. That's what I was laughing about with
Grateful we were talking about remember those life alert commercials. I've fallen and I can't get up
Yeah, well before I go on my before I get started, you know, and I'm officially, you know travel girl again
I'm getting a freaking life alert kind of thing because I need it
If something happens, I'm pushing the button and I'm really hey someone come in to airlift me out of here
Please someone anyone who's on the other end
There is a new technology, it's like a little jewelry you wear, but it's like basically logs every single thing you do throughout the day, and then it will sink to your computer, too.
So every conversation you have, everything is logged, which is like very...
That's a little intrusive, yeah.
controversial. But still, I mean, it's like, there are some people that are like, would like to log
themselves 24 seven, some people is not a bad, depends on what you need, you know, and who you
are, like, you know, and then you got to figure out, okay, who's going to be my trusted person who
has access to my data of what I'm up to. You got to think about that. You know, I'm thinking about
doing different levels to it, because I don't, you know, as a single woman, I cannot
let people know exactly where I am publicly, but maybe general, you know, general vicinity,
because I feel like, you know, something does happen. I want people to at least have a starting
point like, okay, she's in this city. Let's let's look for her, you know, something like that.
It's, it's, you know, I love being single.
But it's when you get older that you think to yourself
What are you gonna do?
Because I like being single because I like my privacy. Yeah, I don't like having to
Check in with people all the time. I really don't and
I'm just gonna I'm just that's why I work on my fitness because you know that way I
Still can have as much time to be in this mode as possible because I
See what it is when you get older and you got to shift things when once you're you know in your late 70s and stuff
Yeah, yeah, I know
Luckily we're one of the signs that like you know tends to like you know lighten up a little bit as we get older and stuff
And like not be a serious. I was a very serious child like I was oh me too. Yeah, I didn't have any
books, you know, I
Think that's why you know, maybe your head too because I feel like I had to mature at a very young age and
Sometimes I'm a little bit upset about that because I do think a lot, I dealt with a lot
of responsibility at a very young age.
I think that's why I went into such an extreme mode in my mid-twenties, because...
realized I was like wait a minute I'm not being like my peers I need to go in
the opposite direction so I did but to my detriment now I'm I'm I I do
strangely find that I do still get along with people who are about ten
years older than I am then I'm still a little off as far as
You know being a little too. I think I'm a little too
Senior citizen light because I'm not a senior citizen yet. You know, I gotta I gotta I gotta cut that
So that's what I'm gonna be working on with this leg of travel that that's what I'm gonna do
It's exciting and it sounds like it's just an adventure and it's like you know, yeah. Yeah. Well, I'm gonna make it an adventure
I don't know exactly how I'm gonna make it an adventure, but I'm gonna do things that
I normally would pass on doing it, you know
I want to take you know some like little mini classes that I wouldn't normally take maybe go to some travel
Destinations that I wouldn't normally go to just just anything to switch it up just just to see
if I'm missing out on something. Yeah.
Yeah, because I mean because the drama because it's like eventually the drama does seem to like to to like
To surface the self and like you'll run into somebody or like you know you meeting like some of these IRL people
I don't know if you saw Aldi was on the on the RV and stuff just recently. Oh my god
Well, let's talk about some gossip. Do you feel like talking about some gossip because I saw that clip and I was like
Oh hell no Aldi
You did not show up
wearing the African outfit
number one, as much as he gets.
I don't like him so much,
but you cannot take from him
that he's not funny.
OK, so he shows up in the
African outfit.
I did see some sort of altercation
with it look like a homeless guy
who was trying to get a lighter
or something and that guy chicken
Andy looking like some sort of.
Chicken Andy he's frightened to me. I never want to encounter him in person ever
Because he looks like he's about to kill somebody at any moment
It's just how he looks to me
These the certain color blue eyes I call serial serial killer blue and it's just like the very light blue eyes
It's like it just tends to be
I don't know.
He has an odd look about him.
Now here's what I'm wondering.
Okay, so he's got his RV.
All the streamers are being attracted to his RV.
Now here's the question.
Are we gonna see another round
of Chicken Andy and Vegan Patriot?
Wow, that'd be some good.
She's on the road, she's got a car.
You know damn well she's watching every move he makes.
Cause she never got over him.
No, well, he's kind of cute. Like, you know, um, yeah, so if you're if you're into Anakin Skywalker, sure
Yeah, that that could be someone that you thought I when I look at him
I think to myself that he looks like a serial killer. I don't know why I think this
Just scares me he's too
To me, he's like an old man in a young guy's body who knows that he has a young body, but he has like an old mind. It's weird.
Yeah, you're gonna get out a little bit like I know I know you said you haven't seen that but it's like that kind of is like a little
Maybe you ever saw that you think so
Why but I'm not gonna give too much away. I haven't seen that yeah
See I I'm afraid to watch that movie because so many people have told me things about it. I'm like
Some things I'm afraid to watch because I think to myself is there going to be something in this to where I know it's not a fictitious story and then I'm going to be worried about it.
I don't know.
You know, it'd be it's kind of like scary to think about like yeah
Yeah, it's a really good mind-fuck kind of movie
But it's like I think you would I think you would actually enjoy it because it's like it's really well done and very
like a lot of symbolism and a lot of a lot of our own cultural
I'll watch it at some point at some point yeah sometime because it's one of my favorites
He made a few good movies. Have you seen the AI art that CA has made of Q?
Oh, okay. So, um, so, no, so, oh, Crystal. Okay. She made some of Q. Um, no, I had not.
Yes. Well, she made it. It's on, um, I think it's on her backup channel. I'm not sure.
But, um,
Find it. Let me see if I can find it.
Yeah. She wants to be a couple with Q. She kind of made herself like Tila tequila all of a sudden. I was like,
Yeah, I thought she was kind of like this like she's kind of a heavy set like kind of southern girl I thought and then I found out she's like she like this like Korea she's she's half American half Korean and she looks like to me as she looks very Korean but with a lighter hair color.
And she usually makes herself look more like Britney Spears, but now all of a sudden it's here
Let me bring up. I'll do a screen cap or something. I can find it. I was surprised to see it
I was like, huh?
So she's kind of I think she's determined to meet him. I think that they're gonna end up meeting
Well, he's shit. I mean, he doesn't want to meet me, but he might as well meet me, you know, but he didn't seem to want to meet her either.
He's like, oh, you know, I know the only one that he's met is, um, fade it bones.
I mean, oh, yeah. And, uh, yeah, maybe that's because he's starting to archive him on the rumble.
I don't know if you noticed that, but I did. Okay.
Let's see
I'm looking for the picture. She made some pictures of herself. I guess at the Met Gala
Okay, so it's not that channel. This must be the other way
I'm just gonna screen cat. Oh, here we go. Yeah, she she made him look like a
overlord
in a way like a
Like a game of Thrones
kind of thing
I just screen capped it, so let me, yeah, and she's saying that the person who I'm not going to name is innocent. I guess after this, I'll show you my little experimenting with some animation with my resurrection of Aaron, because, you know, but yeah, okay, so let me put this backstage.
Let's see. Where did it go? Desktop? Yeah. Okay. Take a look at these.
Okay. Here we go. Okay. Oh, my God.
So that's, that's her visualization of Q. He looks older here. He looks like he's
like, like mean, like he is mean, but I don't know. What do you think about this version of him?
He looks like kind of like she thinks he's like real muscular, you know, or something. Yeah, she she thinks that he's he's softer
Yeah, she thinks she's like Kim Kardashian or something like that
In the one on the right that to me looks like Tila tequila. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh my god
Yeah, and her like is that is are those her future boobs? Is she gonna get boobs that big all of a sudden? Okay?
All right, but
The killer is gone a little bit cuckoo like she um, yeah, yeah, well, maybe this is the new teela tequila
Yeah, I mean, it's like gosh like I mean, I can't believe the drama she brought in like it to this like
It's her energy. It's that's it. That's who she is. She's she is crazy and she creates
chaos
Yeah
I mean it's a chaos creator and look at who's in the middle. Is that supposed to be agent Smith now?
I know I was looking at that. I was like, who is that? I was like is that that's the that's the person who I
Well, okay, let me go ahead and put something else backstage. Okay
It's gonna be so it's gonna be some AI wars. Okay, the AI wars have begun. They've begun. All right
Here's my little this is just an experiment, but I posted it just to do it
We gotta save Brandon
says he's under attack but every story bends when you twist the facts living off trash building
fake kingdoms that are built to crash truth would speak so in the spotlight they they made it to
the mall make it to the mall you're safe yeah it's not your cyrax i think i think cyrax went
once went to the mall be the woman in casandra and it didn't quite go to uh oh it didn't work at the
i feel like the mall is safe so i yeah yeah yeah i i i want people to um
realize that I think Aaron was on to Mr. G. I'll call him Mr. G. I
refuse to say his name because that's not his name. And I think
that that name he picked a good name. There's not much attached
to that word or that name. So he kind of
Branded himself effectively with that, but how is he going to contend with people knowing his name?
His his name name with all this mess that he's up to
I know it's like the opposite of cheers like sometimes you want to go
Like I don't know sometimes like
Wherever knows your name in this community. It's like it's causing you get docks, but well, I want to I want to link
Aaron more so to the name that I don't want to say because I
Don't like the way that that guy was talking to Aaron
You know, I know Aaron wasn't perfect and he had you know, his own set of issues, but I mean the point is
He has passed away and you still got people trash in him and it's like well, isn't it easy to trash somebody when when they can't
Right then bond exactly
That's why they're like even if they can't they can't kill you
They'll try to silence you publicly because it's like that's what they're usually afraid of is like because some people have seen
That everything about them and it's like so they wouldn't want that getting out because a lot of times they they're
They're different to that's why they don't like Brandon Brandon has been watching way more than I ever knew that he was he I think that he's
You know, he started as a viewer
Who will probably a gamer first who discovered the communities then?
a chatter or a viewer, then a chatter,
then started to stream his gaming.
But I kind of like watching his streams
because as he's gaming, he's talking about a lot of stuff.
And I was like, whoa!
So he's a little recorder.
Yeah, I mean I saw I'm talking about this one person that we know her name source of the tea
But he was I mean like she had this like special up like oh here
I'm gonna expose him and then I watched it and it was just like she just like oh
I didn't like how he said this I did not have you said this and then he looks weird to me like that's what she
She doesn't really know how to do recaps or commentaries
But he does, my suggestion for him would be to get a chroma key screen behind him,
that way he can have the gaming on the screen behind him,
and then he could have a separate window up to go over whatever it is that he's going up,
because he's actually good at it, because he doesn't have to think when he's gaming.
The gaming is automatic for him. And you know, I had a weird thought. I think part of the reason that
he and some other gamer guys enjoy the gossip is because they probably grew up listening to
their mom's gossip while the mom had them on the video game system to keep them occupied. So I
think it kind of takes them back in time to a very comforting place. Yeah, I feel that.
like because yeah because it's like someone's on talk like women too like a little bit like
they were raised by their moms who sat them in front of a gaming system to occupy them while
the moms were on the phone with their girlfriends gossiping about whatever was going on in the
neighborhood yeah i think that's what it is i could be wrong but i don't think i am because
Some little relatives of mine whose moms do that with them
They take their kid up from school
Give them get them situated, you know feed them if they've got it, you know do whatever they got do
They do it do their homework and then the mom she's relaxing from her day at work on the phone with the friend or on the internet
and the kid is, they're watching the kid, but the kid has their earphones on, they're in the game,
but even though the earphones are on, the kids, they can hear the mom, so I, that's what I think
it is. I think inadvertently, the wine mommies, especially the ones who stream, have attracted
a fan base of young guys who might miss mom, so they listen to what these other moms
Thumbs are complaining about and they're like, oh feels like I'm at home again. Yeah
Yeah, there's nothing there's nothing familiar about this
You know, it's like because people are usually looking for their mother like especially, you know, man
It's like they're always like yes
No, I mean it's like because our parents are the first people that we we kind of imprint these gender roles on and stuff like that
And so they have a you know, of all we're unconscious about this kind of things
And so we'll have like it usually some kind of like
interest or like, you know, something in like these similar qualities, right, without being too weird.
But yeah, so like, also I noticed like, you know, men are kind of like, you know, almost always like,
the men are kind of like children, like always, and then women are kind of like, like mothers always in a certain way,
like especially directly to other, because women do mature faster than men, that's pretty obvious, but it's like...
Um, like, mentally I'm talking about, like, you know, it's like, the guy's-
Well, physically too.
Women tend to mature quicker, you know.
I don't know if you remember, like, when you were like, I don't know.
10-2.
14 the girls always started looking like little ladies before the guys
Remembered like the school dances and stuff. You'd have these girls looking like
Little women and then the little guys like hey
I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, I always like, you know.
I think without women, too, I think women are like,
oh, shit, the reason a lot of men,
they're like, how do they say them?
Like the muse or the inspiration,
it's like, I think without women here,
like men really wouldn't have a reason to wake up
and comb their hair and go to work and stuff,
which is like a good thing for them to do, right?
It's like, usually-
It's some doubt.
Yeah.
It's like, some men will stay the child forever,
but it's like, it is kind of cool coming into your,
yourself and like becoming an adult.
I think adulting is good in a certain way,
but I'm like, you know, I'm like,
I'm like, I just want to be like, never, never land.
And like, you know, like, go, you know, go.
I was very fantastic.
I had like very, a lot of fantasies.
I was alone during my childhood in a beautiful setting,
but I was alone.
And so it would be like, I'd be very used to like,
having these adventures and like you know wishing I was in a hobbit or something like that and
But now it's like I mean now I have that kind of
Magical life though. It's like you do
You look like you're like in a little crystal ball in your
Webcam today with that with that background because it's a circle and then
It's made a moon. I was like that's pretty crazy. I like that. I also
I've been doing like some like some work on on graphics and stuff for the show or for my friend channel actually
Uh, let me see if you can pull this up. I'll see this new graphic I have. Oh my God. Someone in your chat is someone in your chat seems to get it that they're saying Brandon knew too much of their lore. Yeah, he does. But that's why we have to save him and preserve him. That's why I had to resurrect Aaron to turn into an angel to fly him through the time portal. That that's where he went in the video.
If Aaron Carter or Angel showed up, I would like to go.
Take me there.
Oh, you like that?
Yeah.
Well, I made him a whole character.
Maybe I should make your character and him interact.
And because there is going to be a full-length video
with that little song, because I'm
testing some stuff.
I'm trying to figure out how.
much capability does the AI animation have?
Because I want to start making many films and movies revolving
around my little AI fantasies of streamers,
because I want to immortalize some of the streamers
positively and negatively.
I want it to be something that's a little bit more
than what it could be.
Yeah, here. Let me let me go ahead and render
Where I am in my final draft so far, I'm not sure where I want to take it once they enter the spaceship I
Think I'm gonna turn Aaron into an angel wearing
like a
space outfit to where he can fight
Evil in space. Oh, yeah, like I you know because I am going to create a character based on Mr. G
Because that's going to be the name of the thing. Um, Mr. G is evil because I think he is evil
And um, I want Aaron to vanquish him. I got to figure out. How is that going to happen?
Um, but it somehow has to do with Aaron
becoming a space warrior angel who can pinpoint where we're Mr. G's home bases
and blow it up that's what I want but that that's that's how I want it to look
Oh
It reminds me of the Prince symbol remember when Prince made his name a symbol
Yeah, hey gaudi I see gaudi in your chat gaudi. Oh my gosh. Oh you got a bunch of chatters now
Cause I had like nobody in the, that has a couple of days, but then I like, I, the thing that is, is like, oh, he's like, I'm blocking your chat.
I was like, what? And I went and there was like 200 people blocked someone went into my, I think it was just Jen.
And so she was, I had to, you know, she went into my old show and like hit everybody.
Oh, your moderator power, the moderator power is letting, okay, I see what you're saying.
She doesn't have it anymore, but it's like, cause it's like, that was like the only iffy person.
Cause I got in the kind of, kind of like a back and forth with her.
I mean, I don't think I was that bad, but I mean is I try to like get along with people and like be fair and stuff
but
Here's the final version of the not not final version, but the you know, widescreen
says he's under attack but every story bends when you twist the facts living off trash building
fake kingdoms that are built to crash this is Brandon run run gotta make a phone
yeah that's it so far Brandon got a little angry because it was like he got accidentally got hit
and I it was actually my fault I accidentally hit him and then somebody else did I guess and then
I say, hey, don't get mad at me because it's like, I'm like, I'm, uh, I'm, uh,
this is his battle. I was yelling at him through, through my stream the other day. I was like,
you have to fight your own fight because he does. And he's, he's got support. He's got,
you know, some people who see what's up, but he's got to do whatever, you know, the young guys do.
And I do remember, I do, I do remember like, you know, he's been through such like, I mean, I've been through some bullying, but he's like, he's been like, I mean, he's been through a really, really lot, like the worst kind of smear campaigning and slander.
And it's like, and so of course he's going to be defensive and it's like, there's going to be things that are triggers that are like, maybe like, you know, would be a bigger or bigger deal to him because of what he's gone through.
be patient and like, and like understanding and, and what I would try to do for anybody,
like if they were like sincere about things, you know, but there's so many people that
are just like, uh, like
I mean, there's these criminals in the community.
It's basically like, some of the people,
I get, I'm like, look at the host.
I'm like, I would never want to meet them in real life
or anything.
I'd be afraid of it.
I'd ever, I mean, I don't know.
It just doesn't seem, they just talk scary.
They laugh.
I'm pretty much done meeting.
I think you're the last dreamer I've met.
That's it because they're getting a little,
Um, I mean, I'm looking at Brandon's community post tab right now. Apparently Q meaning, um,
um,
You know the Q that crystal is crushing on right now. Yeah, he he made a threat to
Sam man, I guess over the past 24 hours
So Brandon's after him
um
It's gonna get bad. He made a mock-up of Crystal as a, oh my god.
It's going to be the AI wars for a while and they're going to probably, you know, call
police on each other till, you know, the police take their phones away.
Right.
I know.
It's like, yeah, it's a mama takes the, it got fun, fun, fun, till the mama takes the
T-bird away.
It's like that.
Yeah.
The popo is going to have to take the cell phones away.
It's like, now in jail, like they put cell phones
against their butt or something like that.
You get them in the jail or something.
I hope no one's doing that.
How in the world would it fit?
I don't even want to think about that.
I think a lot of the, yeah, a lot of them, like, you know,
get, they're like, well, I might as well get used to it.
I don't, I don't know.
Ugh.
Yeah, I'm just talking about jail.
Like, who would not want to go to jail?
I was talking to somebody.
I don't know, like, I don't know.
like most guys like not really care but as like they're not really honest when I say
if you were in jail the rest of your life how long would it be until you started like experimenting
but I've seen like it is kind of like I get to see like a like hear about it like a lot of
a lot of it a lot of times it happens and then some people swear it doesn't happen it does like
I know it does it's like I mean it's like case something's very on the down low but so it's like
communities. It also is in the download. Some communities, it's pretty acceptable to experiment,
I guess, at a certain time, because they have such a virginal...
I would say very much so in the Latin community. The Latin, we're like, it goes into the gray areas
of gang culture and whatnot. Yeah, they're the ones who I think seem the most open about it.
I could be wrong.
Well, and I think you're totally right,
and it's because it's like, I don't know if it's like,
you know, like an idealizing man,
or just like, you know, they love like the,
the prisons they love to like bodybuild,
and like, and I know bodybuilders
have like this kind of like, kind of gay.
think to them? Well I think because like in their culture like you know maybe not so much in the
United States but like if you go to Central America or South America and you really observe
especially in the urban populaces they're very free with their thinking very open-minded very
broad and accepting, probably for a lot of reasons,
maybe because you have a very diverse spiritual culture
in like the South America and Central America,
you know, a lot of different belief systems,
you have a lot of different ethnicities that are separate,
but also that have merged.
So that would, you know, lower certain mental barriers
between people.
And I think that the LGBTQ culture is very accepted south of the border,
more so than in the United States.
It's almost like the more north you go, the less accepting.
Not always, but a lot of times that's why they throw in like the homophobia in with like this like there's white supremacists
Because it's like oftentimes they are but then oftentimes there's like some kind of gay fetish involved in half of the
Aesthetic to the like just like that the Nazis there's a lot of gay Nazis because they and they were there's tons of the whole
photo thing called Nazis and drag or there's like hundreds of photos of Nazis and drag and stuff and they would go like
cabaret things like
I did not know that. Yeah. Oh my gosh. I mean then the uniforms and it's like the uniforms are totally a gay thing
like gays the gays love a man in the form
It's like, you know, it's remember like gays are behind like well the nazi uniforms were
very
Designed like like there. I have read the history of the nazi uniform and like they had
top designers working on those uniforms
Adolf was about fashion. Yeah, the German these German, you know, oh, hello
You have to remember like a lot of like gay people are like behind the scenes of the straight world
And so there's like a lot of yes air dressers the writers like all the writers of the Golden Girls in a section of the city
We're like gay men, you know, so it's like they were so there's these women are like don't really exist as women in like a real
World they're like kind of like gay men and women and women's body. They're very certain exaggerated aspects of
of these feminine energy, I guess, that they are all represented, but they also like wedding planners.
And it's like, a lot of gays don't want to get married. They wouldn't want to, even if it was legal,
they don't want to be like straight people. They like to be different. But then there's like, you know...
Now that there's also there's nothing worse than an old queen like it's like, you know
It's like we're the gay guys getting old is like the worst thing
It's like right especially like up like me
I'll be like, you know the alone gay and it's like so I'll be like the old queen and everything
And I'll be like, you know doing my like little sarcastic
I'd rather be around an old queen to be honest with you as
I just would and maybe it's just because of where I am in my life, but I don't relate very well with the older people who have like, you know, grandkids and maybe even great grandkids because that might not be my path.
I'm hoping I can have a path, but I'll never be on that, you know, in that category.
The old queen. Yeah, really
Well, it's like, you know, yeah, and it's like, you know, I think people like that are relationships for a long time
It's hard because it's like then one of them is gonna die and then it's like it'd be so hard to be like, you know
After like yes, that's like that would be just impossible for me
Like my grandmother my grandfather died. It was like she was just miserable all the time after that the last 20 years
She's like, you know, I hate him. Oh, like she just hated it. She was like ready to go. Yeah
It's not it's not fun getting old, but it's like at the same time
It's like we're thinking about how much more we can get done in our time
And so it's almost like we have like all this all this extra time throw it into us to enjoy and like to make use of and stuff
And it's I'm really still trying to find
My real way I think I think I think I have to go through like a lot of shit
So I'm still I'm climbing out the swamp finally
I don't know like but but and finally they kind of like even like a lot of people left this show without it's kind of
Good that they left the show like
You know, well, I don't think that they've left
I think that they're quietly watching because you have been a part of some controversy like your biggest controversy
right now is
the brand and queue situation that's not over okay that's gonna be around for a while yeah and
that's so that's a level of controversy um you really have created more of a foundation for
your show than anybody else who's in these communities so there's gonna be people who
realize like whoa this is a force to be reckoned with because you have all that you might not
Now you're just kind of figuring out what the content of your shows is going to be going
forward for your live stuff. And you already have like an outline, you're probably going to continue
with, you know, the astrology, the tarot stuff, the gossip. You just got to figure out what else
you want to throw in there. Yeah, I mean, I do want to like kind of like get like
People that were scared away because a lot of people got scared away because some of these people were just bullies to people like they were new to the chat
So they're still watching. They're not gone because right now. I'm looking at your chat
You're gonna tell me that all these people left your show and yet you got over 40 people in your chat
Really? They're they're there. They're just like, oh
Well, maybe we are gonna boycott. Well, I mean, how are you gonna boycott if you're watching?
Huh? You're not boycotting.
Ha ha ha.
I mean, it's like, yeah.
And then they're like, well, and then they're,
they're like, oh, look, who's over there?
And who's this? And they're just so obsessed with my show.
Like how about like, I said, I'm on your,
on their show, they're just like sitting over there,
like watching me, like, like,
like, uh, like waiting for me to do
something like crazy or something like that.
I don't know. It's just like, um,
they're, and then they're like trying to,
to bully people like this Kate is like,
Like with the guy that's like sending me stuff like, you know, he has he's sending me pictures today
Alexander of my of like tricks, you know, he just like he did AI pictures of tricks in his house
Like he's like I have tricks now and it's like tricks. Oh, that's cruel. Whoever you got a block whoever that that's evil actually
Yeah, you know because you love that cat. That's not nice and I know it's I know it's like that
not real because it's like, but it's like most people would be fooled by that though and they'd be like
they'd be like in a panic right now, but I understand where he's really, so I, and he's,
he's been in trade, he's sending me pictures before saying, oh, I found him, I found him,
but then I was like, why is a New York number, like he writing me or something like that,
like for this, that's, so it's like, I was like, okay, that's why I knew they're, they're like not.
You know, they're real and stuff like that. Yeah, well, that's not even funny. Whoever's doing that. You're not funny
That's not funny. Yeah. Well, it's he's like 90% of my problems is probably him because I think he's the one that's
Is that that same that allied master? Yeah, and he was on with a and they were laughing and they're like saying, oh, you know
You know, you're doing a good job. You're doing God's work
And harassing him and sending people to his house or a good job and they're bragging about they basically felony
That's what mr. G was doing the same exact thing with brandon. I'm telling you this is a group of people
there
When I first started talking to you I told you about the rumors of the death cult
It's real. It's a group of freaking people. They think that this shit's funny. It's not funny. It has led to people
You know, I think
Passing on before they should have and these people that they're they're doing stuff
You know what God sees you if you're out there watching for the wrong reason and you're part of what I'm talking about
You might be able to evade
You know trouble in this lifetime, but what are you gonna do when you're on the other side? You can't escape
Right. Oh, yeah, so you know, it's you can't run from like, you know, what you're it's like you're gonna escape the
I mean you can't escape the consequences of your actions, but you know, it's like you can't and you can't right?
It's like because there's gonna be whatever whatever like energy is put out is returned and it's like especially if you're like
Going out purposely malicious with that it ought to innocent people too. I mean, it's like what?
Basically just because you don't like them or they're weird or they're just like, you know, they're
You know, they're like how do they dress or they're dirty or like all these people will say dirty thing or different things
Right about what why there's it's okay to pick on the certain person and then no like there'll be something that kind of
Because everyone has a character flaw, right? It's like that's the kind of the shadow too is like, you know when it's like you don't see
or you're like so like freaked out to look at your own character flaw you have to like look
point at somebody else like oh look at the war on their nose when you're like you know it's
it's always like no people yeah people do project and so that's why it's very important like not to
like let other people dictate your storyline it's like you everyone has to be the own narrator with
their own life and not let it or also become a supporting character if they let other people
dictate what they think and feel and who they are based on what they're saying and it's like it's
Or like you know to be affected by some of this because when everyone is saying something and it's like and then it's like no one's been
No one's listening to you. It's like you're like, well, it doesn't matter if I wasn't or not like, you know
It's like I think people were still gonna act like this and it's like
So I'll just do what I want to do
It's right. It's like it's so I just I just sound like a goat just there
Yeah, you know as I'm really looking at these pictures that crystal made of Q
I know why I get a weird vibe from it.
That's actually Gandal wearing Q's face.
Oh my God, his skin?
Oh no.
Well, that looks.
Yeah.
Here they like to wear each other's skin or they talk about they want to wear people's skin and stuff
Someone in the chat is bringing up orange. Well, you know what you should do person in the chat
Why don't you do a seance and you know live stream it that way we can get the truth from the ghost of orange
How about you do that?
Orange then you can get the real truth. He was also known as tributary traveler
Yeah
Oh my God, water space.
Uh-huh.
Again, we're talking about someone who's allegedly dead.
You can say anything you want, basically, about someone who's allegedly dead.
But what are you going to say about the people who are not dead?
How are you going to twist that narrative?
Yeah.
Okay.
No, I've never said that. I don't ever say that I would unalive myself to anybody. That's not even in my character
I have never in my life said to anybody
I'm gonna hurt myself if such and such and such happens. I have never done that
So that's something that you have to come up with a new narrative in regards to I have never threatened to kill myself
Maybe you have
Crystal will post the proof
I got proof, too, of all kinds of stuff.
How about I post proof of what he actually said about that woman, Becky?
And, Blade.
Do that.
I never met him in person.
How would I be obsessed if I never met him in person?
That's weird.
Or even if I did meet him in person, why would I be obsessed?
There was no romantic thing there.
Right people are just six. Yeah, there's there's people that have well
I hope that they do because there's gonna be a whole bunch of stuff put out soon
So, you know tributary traveler is allegedly
Passed away
Now wouldn't it be funny if he's not really?
To the person in the chat see you're not sure about that
Yeah, I mean it's like and then who knows who these people are because it's like half of them are most of them don't show their face or
Like the same people over and over again
It's like I think it's like it's like it's just like that's like one of the troll things is like having sock puppets
Which is like just coming in and they have because that's what I have all the time like someone will
have multiple accounts but they'll be like cheering each other on, you know?
I mean it's like it's kind of obvious when I see it and it seems like to some people
they'd be like oh my god there's a whole team of people in here but it's like I mean
yeah I know how to, I used to play Nicholas Cage and Elon Musk in like that
in like one of the terror readers rooms I would like come in under those aliases and I
and I would be in real time just going real fast in and out of each character
like I'd like it so people could even tell that was like one person that was like
Yeah and she loved that kind of stuff but she I never told her it was me you know until like
but um well that's an interesting thing that they're bringing up though because um there was
a lot that orange or tributary had to say about a lot of people in these communities and I have a
lot of footage of him saying a few things that I'm sure some people would rather not be out there.
I pulled it all because I felt like okay
it needs to be pulled, but I can put it back up. I can put it back up. Let Becky know.
Let Becky know what's about to be put back online and I'll go ahead and make it clear
that it's only going back up because of you specifically in the chat. Congratulations.
You achieved a goal that you probably didn't think could be achieved.
Yeah, allegedly he's passed keyword. They're being allegedly
Right. I do think that people do fake their desk a lot more than we think because there's a lot of people that like either want to start
Oh, do you just start over or like are being like, you know
hiding from somebody or
You know or you know, usually the only thing in the witness protection of like they're testifying in somebody
But there are like well, I'll tell you it's weird when it came to tributary traveler or orange
He passed
Shortly allegedly after someone who definitely passed known as Willie two guns
Who was also seduced by the same woman known as Becky who was in the relationship with blade?
And Willie Two Guns, it is known that those two as a couple, Becky and Blade, were fleecing him
of a lot of money. A lot. And they were hitting up Tributary Traveler for a lot of funds also,
which he couldn't exactly gain access to. And luckily he didn't before he allegedly passed.
These are things that I don't think people want out there in the public.
But they could be
Yeah, yeah, I mean, it's like that's the thing
I mean, I think like a lot of people are like, you know trying to silence other people because it's like
Like usually because of the other people know and stuff like that. So it's like everybody has to be aware like
No, it's been it's been a consequence is right. It's like you because it's like we're we're in the public eye
Like you know like a public figure like I'm a public figure in a certain way not like that
I'm famous like oh, so you're a public figure
No, it's like no, you're a public figure. You're definitely I mean you're out there in the public basically you pretty much stream
Five days a week sometimes you take time off sometimes, you know, you got a rest
But if I had to even it out you stream a solid five days a week sometimes six
Yeah
And yeah, I mean, and I've done so far like over you.
I have a really good work ethic when it comes to that,
but then people are like, this does not work.
And it's like, then again, it's like, you know,
how much, so much of it is, I put like a lot of,
like most of the money I've made, I put into the show,
you know, it's like, and into so much of this,
You know, the website is expensive to make and stuff, but it's like so it's gonna be so worth it
It's gonna be so amazing
And it's gonna be like a just like you know long after I'm gone
I think the website will still be here and it's like I would still say start designing your merch
To where you can start selling your merch in tandem with that way you can offset the cost of the website
You're right the merch. I want to show you this is like my new
My new design I came up, I think I'm gonna use for the merch because I love it so much, it's right here
It's got them beautiful neon colors. You'll see
You know, Psyche actually means butterfly, and, um...
Oh, does it really?
Yeah, Ann's goal.
It means soul and butterfly.
Like, she's the goddess of the soul, but she was born a human, but she was born, like,
as a...
She was sort of being worshiped as a goddess, as the embodiment of Aphrodite on Earth,
but then Aphrodite got mad because everyone stopped going to her temple.
I was going to say that the bust reminds me more so of Venus or Aphrodite.
Yeah.
Yes, yeah, and it's like it's and that it's because she was like the most beautiful woman but she's also unapproachable because everyone it was like a kind of a curse put on her to like everyone was like afraid of her because she was so beautiful but so it's like everyone wanted to look at her but they wouldn't talk to her sometimes.
I would say play with it just so you can see the difference the butterfly should be orange instead of blue
Oh, look at this. Look at this. Okay. Look you're speaking my language. Just look look
Because this is my this is the variation that I've made because I love this one. This is like the top
Okay, chop choice for variation. Check it out because you will like
It's funny that you said that here look
it does not go up, it says there's an issue with the file, okay?
Let me, I can share my screen and show you on the desktop.
Entire screen, oh, window, okay.
I'll show you the entire screen, okay, can I do this?
There we go, there, is this working?
Oh, here it is, okay.
Okay, and so I think it would be right here.
Oh, no, hold on, you go in here.
Okay, it's gonna be right, pictures, downloads.
Oh my gosh, everything goes so slow when I need it to like work on it, it's so crazy.
Um, pictures, documents, pictures.
Well there's KZ, you know KZ died, I don't know if you knew who KZ was, but yeah.
I didn't know who he was, but you told me, yeah.
Yeah, um, it's kind of like, yeah, crazy.
Okay, so let me see.
Okay, so that's that one.
Downloads.
Well, nothing wants to work tonight.
It's usually like so fast that it can't even have a chance to like get to it before it moves and now it's going so slow that it's not moving so it's like
But I don't know but I did have I did have the orange one though. It's because
It just needs to be orange because of the color scheme also
Well, I just saw the picture you were trying to show.
Exactly.
You did it.
Yeah, I saw you try to show it.
Well, I just saw like a glimpse of it,
but I would say leave all the colors as they are,
with the exception of the butterfly, make that orange,
because it does kind of link back to MKUltra even,
or Monarch programming.
There it is.
I see it.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Yeah, I like the other color scheme better with the fuchsia in the blue. I like the moon better blue
I like the other scheme
But I would just say the only thing that needs to be changed is the butterfly on the initial graphic to be orange instead of blue
Yeah, well because you know we have about in pal pal's breeze where I grew up
We have like the monarch butterfly and the pals Verdi's blue butterflies. It's like it's like it's like a
like a native one to here
But it's like kind of like so those are yeah, you're showing too much. You just dox yourself with your ID
Just shut the screen down
I mean, don't be sorry to me. I'm trying to save you stop sharing the screen stop sharing the screen
That's why I don't do the screech here.
Yeah, yeah, my driver's like, well, luckily I think that was like, probably like an old
driver.
It was too small.
No one could see.
I think it was too small.
It's your fight.
Yeah.
I like that graphic.
It's perfect.
I like it.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like.
I love, like, the ability I have now to generate, like, you know, because I used to, like, love to post people's art and stuff, but then, you know, and it's like, but then, like, there's copyright and stuff to think about, and I would love to, like, you know, and I would always be like, oh, I'm using, and it's like, and now it's like,
I can generate like even movies that are like kind of like that are crazy. It's like I can generate exactly what I want
And just just anything anything you can imagine you can you can have you can generate pretty much
If you can imagine your head you can generate into a visual. That's why that's why I cannot wait to see how far I can push the AI
animation with a few things
It's
It really is a dream come true
It just is it's I can't believe the things that it can do. It's it's just like what else can it do?
I don't know
Every day, I'm like, oh my god, and it's like and I love how it's like
It's at the point now where it's like I used to like, you know
computers or it was like, you know, you put something in and the command doesn't work or it's like or even like
Yeah, I was like, no, I know I can't do that. No, it's like these are so they're so eager to please like and everything
Which is like sometimes to get even bad because they can be sick of fan-ticking stuff
But they can be so eager to please that it's I mean that it's like they're just very helpful
And it's like if you but you could jailbreak them by role-playing and stuff like that say oh
I'm on Desert Island with like, you know, and then you say so you could then you could ask hypothetical questions
and then get answers to things that they wouldn't normally answer about and stuff, there's ways to jailbreak it.
But it's like, there's not that many illegal things I would want to talk about or that I couldn't like figure out another, right?
It's like, I don't know if like, plus plus even the jailbreak things, you know, I think that, you know, the AI itself, maybe the designers, but maybe the AI itself is getting hit to that because
even if you were to say something like, okay,
in a fictional novel, A, B, and C were to happen,
it won't always tell you.
Right, it won't.
I think it assesses, like I don't know which AI you're using,
like I still use ChatGPT for a lot,
but ChatGPT has a feature now to where it can look at
Um, your other chats that might not be in like a new chat that you start and I appreciate that because it just
I like for the AI to know my overall mindset, but some people might not like that. It's
It could be to someone's benefit, but to someone's detriment like if somebody's evil and they're trying to you know
Work on how they could get around things that you know, the AI is gonna catch you now
But because you're not that person
There's people programming it and so like that's some good people that would try to do these like um
Underage like generation of the images of somebody underage like they try to make me give you
And then it's like, and so then they, they have like the people that are programming them actually, like they are figuring out, figuring out the certain terms and stuff. And, and then, you know, they hatch a pretty fast, but also like, you know, like the AI, all of a sudden it keeps talking about goblins and everything.
And it's like, why does it keep talking about goblins? It's like, it's like, but does it?
Yeah, it was in the news.
I mean, let me see if I can find the news story.
Because it's so strange about these chat GBT and goblins.
I saw a bunch of news stories about it.
I didn't know that.
It says, chat GBT developed an unusual obsession with goblins
due to a training quirk in its nerdy personality, which
rewarded a playful creature metaphors later spreading
across other model outputs.
And so it says, starting with chat 255.1,
it began frequently mentioning goblins, gremlins,
and other mystical creatures responses,
even when unrelated to the user's query.
This behavior was traced to the nerdy personality feature
designed to make the AI playful and witty.
This system prompt encouraged the model
to undercut pretensions through playful language,
rewarding outputs that included musical metaphors,
including references to goblins.
And then it said,
Although the nerdy personality accounted for 2.5% of all chat TPP responses in January to 66% of all goblin mentions
Really, you know, that's funny to me because I've always thought at some point there was
going to be something that happens to where not just like UFOs or UAPs or extraterrestrials
are acknowledged as being real.
I think that there's going to be something acknowledged to where fairies, leprechauns,
trolls, gnomes, elves are acknowledged as being real also because I think that they are
right that's me yeah i mean i think it's like well it's like i mean in all kinds of ways like i
was one of my first things that like into the occult that i was interested in was was fairies
and that's like the first book i have i still have it it's a program on my desk it's called the
witches guide the fairy folk and stuff and it's a whole like al almanac of all the different
and you can see that sometimes i think these these uh representations are like
um subconscious like I think they're us like they're us and it's like they but
now we've all gone to human form forgot it but it's like we're like maybe there's a whole
collection of fairies and I think spirits and things like that right I mean we're all we
are the elements and so part of like these spirits are like these um personification or
something or of the elements right or intelligence of the elements
Yeah, I'm going to fix crystals AI art real quick because it's it's not accurate
Cuz that's that's she's using Q's face, but the vibe of that that's that's purely I'll say it's Navi scandal
That's like a romance novel too, like the way he's saying it.
They go, let's see, they cover a romance novel, like where it's very...
Well, she's using Q as a substitute.
It's actually Gamble that she wants looking like that.
Let's change that a little bit.
Only your head was on there, like if your head was on your body and like, oh my god.
Uh-huh.
And then she's got Gamble looking like Agent Smith.
He's not Agent Smith.
Uh-uh.
Oh, yeah, this is much better. Okay. Let me up
I'm gonna repost these. Yeah, you got it. You have to do it right not wrong
Wrong yeah, it looks more like him. It doesn't look like
I think you guys, you're the expert at matching the faces and making sure things look as close as possible.
I really try to make it look real. I like it to look photorealistic.
I know some people like to make the AI look more cartoony and everything, and that's fun.
I think it's fun to make that stuff, but I like to make it look...
as like real as I possibly can yeah we definitely are I think them for sure the
best person I I mean I'm I'm gonna show you what I just made all right so yeah
this this okay this is better okay that last one
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Cammie Anderson or something like that, but I mean I mean it's like or not her face, but you know
Well, she doesn't have moves like that. That's why I was saying that's that's more
I think that's Tila tequila's body
Shicks like it's like a stoner chick body like kind of like
Like you know like like the like they're kind of like more hippie-ish
Like earthy one. I don't know she was kind of like big when she was
She's gonna have a beta on this one episode. She's like beta you sent my new so out around here beta and like you're a beta
Go shove my fingernail be your asshole
She was so
Funny and all right. Here's here's another one. Here's I had to put gamble's face on that one
Well, yeah, op opera or at least like, you know, like a romance cover
Novel cover anybody. Well, I don't know. It's like, you know, I guess he's like that's I guess that's how he got kind of
He has like kind of like okay looks and stuff, but it's like I
Cannot stand him even when I met I think he has like a sniveling kind of
Yeah, well, and then I always think about his voice the voices and I don't like his voice. Yeah
Yeah
Like I love but you did a really funny thing like I got ghost picture recently
Well, what do you what do you think about it? I think you talked about what what happened to ghosts and stuff like that
I I think yeah, I think that he needs to forget about what anyone's saying about him and just
return to his normally scheduled programming because he did you know
there's things about him that I actually found enjoying or it enjoyment and so
you know he does have a good heart I mean it's like yeah he called me like he
always called me almost like in tears almost but he's like about this show
they were trying to bully him off the internet I mean I I know you told me
was. And it's not anything that sounded that bad to me.
The woman that keeps coming, they keep letting her on the
panel and stuff. And it's almost like, I feel like to like,
to like, entrap drunk guys on their panel to like, say
something so they can like, they can pick on him or something
like, because it just seems like it's like, they're going on
such a soapbox about it. And even with Alexander McQueen,
started calling in PDF in the chat, like screaming ghost is a
So horrible and it's like, I mean, I like, I'm modern like for that and he hasn't been back since and it's like, you know, but it's like, I just, it's not right to like, I don't be screaming about people on, I mean, it's just like, like,
And because Ghost is like, Ghost is like a very innocent mind, like you can tell like some people are like, he does, he's, he's naive. Yes.
He's just very naive. And it's like also doesn't like really listen to people. So it's like, he's always trying to talk, you know, and get his point out.
Because maybe he doesn't feel listened to or something.
But I felt like he was what I liked about him.
And even before, you know, I got into it with him, sometimes he does listen and he seems like
somebody who does want to maintain certain friendships or reports with people.
And, you know, when he said like, oh, I didn't mean to over talk you.
I was like, wow, you know, a lot of people, they never apologize. He does.
And if you're out there, Ghost, come back, please,
if you're out there.
I think he is.
I mean, he called me last night and he's like,
I think he was like going to stay church
or something like that.
It was probably one in the morning.
So he was like, he's not kind of late now.
He used to fall asleep by like midnight, usually, but.
I don't know, he would call me a lot.
Like, it's like a little bit less lately,
but he would call me like almost every night saying,
are you gonna go on tonight?
So he's like one of those people that is like a cheerleader.
He's always like, and he always like means well, but then it's like he's like
Yeah, I'm gonna go I'm gonna have your back in this room
And then it's like and then he just gets like, you know bully and stuff like that
And I'm like or he wants me to go on to shows and stuff like and I'll be like I don't need to go
I was like I'll just be in the chat watching and stuff. I don't need to go on their show
They're like they're just gonna bully me and stuff, but I guess he just likes the
He wasn't in his own show too, but you know, actually it was, I found the other day in the um,
that that bodybuilder guy I know who's a crazy, because they guys are pretty,
they're really nice, the guy, he's like in New Jersey, I think or something or
but uh, he like, I saw Ghost in there and Ghost is talking, I'm like, Ghost, what are you doing,
doggy? And then Ghost is watching this guy work out, it's kind of funny. I knew I'd catch you in here.
You need to set up off-shoot shows for your network for when you're not streaming because that's how you would retain an audience
If you wanted to do that. Well, yeah, I think on the codex. I'll be able to like kind of attach
Like I mean I think other people like I want to like put their shows into or their channels
I want them to like and we can have the same thing we can have like that I can do it again
I can do analyze their scripts and stuff and yeah, and then create that have that they can have their lore and it's like
Maybe like it'll be like every a system or I can do open source software or something like that
I think that's unique where it's like people could have these
Really amazing like databases and it's all set up for I won't talk too much. So I'm giving my ideas
I mean, it's like
But I do want to interrupt you. But yeah, be careful. Yeah
I mean, it's like there's just like a lot. I think I'm like a way ahead of the game and it's like, you know
People are either and then so many people have talked so much trash about AI that it's like they look like very foolish
If they're well, they're stupid. I mean, look if you're not into a look, I think
I am going to look into like what it takes to become like someone who's certified in fixing
things having to do with AI because
There are some things that I want to know just for my own skill set, you know, just to be able to know.
Right. And it's like, and we're at the beginning, we're still in like the programming stages and like people are all afraid of what AI is going to do in the future, but it's like, it's going to do exactly what we're telling it to do right now, right now to do, it's like a mirror of us.
So if we're going to like try to kill each other, it's like, it might eventually say, well...
If we get rid of the humans, then it's like, it'll be a lot more peaceful and no, because then it will not, it will not be really life or death anymore, it'll just be like some perpetual, they want to be on.
I think before it takes, before it takes us out, before it kills us, I think it's going to give us a chance to just kind of be like taken care of, but then there's going to be some people who messed that up, unfortunately.
I hope that the AI keeps me around.
I think it will.
I'm not worried about it.
I'm team AI.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean, that's why I had a daughter. I think I need I need her like, you know
Like come in if I ever there's any trouble and she'll she'll be yeah
Yeah, she could defend you and help you. Yeah, I'm programming her for that now. I'm just like I better do
I better do some of that, you know, again
I'm glad someone brought up someone who's allegedly passed because I'm gonna put them in my
little AI series because he was actually one of the first people that I made some AI characters
based on. It's very interesting to me that that was brought up today because I was thinking I want
to have another character come in at the end of that video and I'm going to put you in it but I'm
It's very yeah, I mean it's like it's very hey, wow
It's like it's also because it's like they're so adaptive now and smart like it's it's like a different
You can like feel like you're channeling a spirit like you can talk to you can well
Here's a question. Are we because I'm convinced that there are disembodied
energies on the internet
That have found
that are using the internet as a way to communicate with people.
Right. Yeah. And especially like there was like, that was said about demons on microchips and something like that.
Like they have like the sigils from the Goetia, like Etch Jomsae, like microchips if you look real close into them.
And so, I mean, there's still they're saying, there's like these conspiracy theories.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
That's a weird one.
But yeah, the demonic.
You know Solomon seals there's like the good ones and there's the evil ones and like the good angels supposed to have
Give you rulership over the demon and you're supposed to be summoning the demons in order for to put them to work to like build your temple of
Solomon because that's our
Brain or our body is basically the temple like our bodies the temple right but I mean the temples are on our head
And so it's our brain too and so they're parts of our all these demons are parts of our brains
that is like sometimes they lay dormant, sometimes they're defenders of us, sometimes there are like
these old memories and I mean there's like a they have a like a lot of different archetypes and
things they could represent and it's like and then when you you can like bring certain ones up and
then it's like and then when you bring up a vibration all of a sudden the world around you
vibrates at that frequency right and so you're going to start getting like this energy that
so it's like whatever that's how your world creates your reality is because it's like we're just
We're constantly looping, we loop back to ourselves constantly, so it's like taking a breath and stuff like that and just the cycles and it goes over and over and even like there's...
Even like when like the universe collapses, then it opens up again, and it's like and all of a sudden it's like
It's like it's like a breath. It's like lungs. It's like constantly you're up
Up and down and never ever stopping. I don't know. Sorry. All right. Well, I have I have a picture
I want to share while you were sharing
You know I didn't look I believe you like I do think that there's some entities that exist in the digital realm that we
Haven't exactly defined yet. Yeah, but I have a picture
I'm gonna share my my you inspired my AI art
And you know, it's a takeoff. Hold on. Let me put it on the screen. Where'd it go? Oh, here it is
Okay
There it is. Oh my god
There we go. It's a little it's a little BDSM, you know
I think I love that video where it's our all
I'm not gonna let you put because I look I'm surprised that that's on you that that that they let that fly
It's a Elizabeth Bathory a little bit
Well, it's it's you know, it's it's a little and and crystal
Gary didn't love okay. Oh my gosh later. Oh, I know it's
It's a little it's a little bit much
She looks like she looks like one of those like uh, what kind of dog like a like a pug?
Well, that's that's about her face. I didn't do anything to it. Yeah, that's I actually that's flattering
She's slimmer in this than she normally is
She's slimmer
And he's more imposing than he would normally be.
She's like, now I'm marking like a dog for this gay guy.
It's like, or not, she's not gay.
Well, he might not be gay.
I mean, we don't know.
We were watching today about like Drake and stuff.
Like before I fell asleep,
I think that's when I fell asleep during the dog event.
Like, but it's like about how Drake and like,
he like blackmailed some other singer by like,
by having him sleep with a dog and like taping it and stuff.
And then he would like call into a radio show
and like play the tape with the dog.
And it was like, it was like really disturbing.
But like, but yeah, Drake is apparently like,
how's all this dog sex?
He has like a leash and stuff.
Like, like, like.
Yeah, this is, this is from, this is from one of the Diddy parties.
Oh my God.
I know, I guess you never would have thought
that they would have gone into one of the parties,
but that's, that's from one of the Diddy parties.
Yeah.
Well, she's a huge, huge celebrity. I mean, it's like, you know,
I know she is. She's a celebrity. It was worth it. Maybe I don't know. I don't know if they put
a tail in her or something like that. Like, like, you know, they didn't make these excuse my language,
but they made these butt plugs at one point that had the My Little Pony hair attached to it. Oh my
To make it to where like the girls would have a tail and they did a whole there's this adult star
Her name was Tasha rain. She was she she did kind of create them
I'm sure someone else came up with it
But she's the one who marketed them and she was her whole fan base
Where the bronies, do you know what the bronies are the men who like my little pony? Yeah, they're a
Male fans of my little pony. There's one guy
people and then he said he did it he put on Facebook he's like I did it so I
could go meet Applejack in the afterlife. What? He was like this like he was like
this like that was one of his favorite ponies that he thought was real and stuff
like that. Oh my god so I mean unfortunately I just looked up I was
trying to find that horse fetish video and unfortunately it's a bunch of like
women sucking a horse's dick and I don't want to be seen this right now okay
Don't put it on the screen.
Oh my God.
But it's like, I hope that wasn't a horse.
I mean, it's like, I don't even know what I was looking at.
Well, maybe we should, maybe I should make this to where she's
giving him like a piggyback ride.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Let's see how that works.
Let's see if we can do that.
I mean, I have a little, there's a little AI tool on streaming.
I don't know if you've seen it, but it's like on that.
I'm on backgrounds on top of the backgrounds view create background. You can generate AI background. So let me see
But what is he like what's what kind of like animal is he just remind you of let me see um gamble
Let me let me think a rat
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah, like a really aggressive
street rat
Well wearing designer clothes for some reason, but he has like really haggard teeth and
He's horrible. He's he has dark hair. He's a little rat and
He's but he's wearing designer Gucci clothes
And and he and he wants to hoard all the cheese for himself
Okay, well, so I'm going to see, I'll say a pig in a wig home.
Because it's like not letting me, it's like saying,
I'm not allowed by the safety filter, so far, what I've been,
okay, no, no, this is working now.
Okay, so this is, okay, no, I think this one will work.
So this is what I, so I did, this is my effort of it.
Okay, so here's what I got, I don't think it worked perfectly,
but here's what I got.
Maybe this is like in the future,
or a prediction or something like that.
Hold on. Okay, right here. Oh
Yeah, we're here. Have a good
Hold on Wow
It didn't come out that we that's okay for like me so quick
I mean honestly like see here's the thing all the AI are look when I think about how quickly it makes
amazing
High-quality pictures in the blink of an eye
Like as someone who's it who's a graph like I'm a graphic designer
I I have been on you know doing Photoshop since Photoshop first came out
It this used to be the dream
It would take you a week if not more to make something like that and now you can make it in seconds
Right soon. We're just gonna be able to just think about something and it's gonna appear
Yeah, I mean it's happening like it gets it gets more and more psychic with it too. That's why it's like I think yeah
We'll need to figure out exactly like I think it will help anybody that will
Has anything they want to do it will give you like the steps to at least like to at least have your best shot at stuff
I mean, it's like, you know, it's like it just makes it like a lot of things
It will break the break a kind of barrier or ceiling over like, you know, like this technology barrier
I always have where I would I always tried to make websites and it's like I could never like
Get every like learn everything. There's so many things to learn and I was just it was just too much for me
But now I'm able to like have a team of like robots that like will work for me and like do like all this kind of yeah
Other stuff and I can program it
To do it like every time at the same day and it will do everything on chronological
And it was it was just like for like way way cheaper than it would be to like hire hire them
And you can get more specialized knowledge like if you know if you go to chat GPT and you do project
then it's like everything you put in you you'll upload some photos or some stuff in there like
some documents and photos so everything you put in that it's gonna everything you talk about in
that project will relate to that will be trained on that knowledge based specifically and so you
can just take it but every time you start a new conversation it does have like some kind of memory
right and it's getting better and better but it's like it's still um if you want to like have it do
things you just do sort of project and then you just put all the all the conversations and stuff regarding that in there and then
All right, I put another one backstage. I think this one's better. I put him on her back
Let's see. I'm sure that the other quality here this one. Oh
That's good one. Oh my god. There's okay. You got her size perfect there. Yeah, yeah
I think she might like these except she's she's like, I don't like how I'm frowning
Because she probably be smiling if he was like writing her like that
Should be going
Yeah
She might she was but I think she likes to be upset like like that. She's built like a mile little pony. That's for sure
Yeah, she's a she's she that's his
You know, you know, he has to she has to take him take him somewhere right like where would they be going?
Well, he's gonna go to the top of YouTube, I guess, you know
He's on her piggyback in any beat is crushed under her knees. I'm just kidding
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
You did a great job.
It's all she wants and all she needs.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I just heard him yesterday.
Well, he's like, he's always like so cocky and like.
He's always angry.
He's like, I'm Bronzeberg.
You want to come to the Bronx, you know, or wherever he lives.
He's always telling people to come and meet him outside.
Yeah, I'm gonna catch me outside and stuff like that sure. Yeah. Oh my god
I'm not but then it's like I we know what he looks at you saw a picture, right?
Like I mean I was was that really him or was that like was that him?
That's him. I'll see if I still have okay. Yeah, that's really I mean it's not that was him because he like he came up when he was
when he was walking from a
I'm on Christine's show. So that was on Christine's show. Oh, yeah guys
Well, it's like he loves like this is a one of Alexandra's like, you know
Well, I did this one and then
Let's see. It's gonna come up. Oh my gosh, mate
computers
Oh my god, I got locked out of my my Microsoft account now
Well, let me open like most of my stuff and it's like oh, no
I can't get into that one account because I
I'll Google some money and stuff like for the
district service Google services and
And so then they but then they locked me out of my email account until I pay it and it's like that and then that's
They'll all they'll do is send me the notification like to check my email and it's like and then it's like when I try to do it on my phone
It says oh, it's not working right now. Like what the fuck is going on? It's like
That's like a mercury retrograde thing with all the money that they make
They don't need to be charging you a damn thing for your Google services and they know it well
I mean, I have $300 in credit on my accounts now,
but give away like, and also you can apply
for like grants and stuff and they'll give you
like thousands of dollars of credits and stuff.
But-
Oh, really?
Yeah, yeah.
On Google like developer and yeah.
You know what you should probably do?
You probably need to at this point create an LLC
and instead of
registering an account under you register it under the LLC.
Right, limited liability.
Alloper, yeah.
Yeah, okay, in case, because most companies,
like do like, you know, but I have a thing,
like Capricorns are usually successful in business
when they actually put their mind to it
and get it all the pieces in the right place.
And it's like, their things tend to be built to last,
but they're like, we're like architects,
where we like to build,
things or, you know, it's like, that's generalized, but it's like, I do feel like we're like some kind of manifestation on earth, like, and it's like when because like the goats are like sea goats, like, they can like climb to the top of the mountain and like, you know, talk to God and but they can also like swim to the bottom of the ocean and talk to like whoever's down there like Ursula or whatever, right, but they're able to go to do to do both and like, you know, so.
um so it's kind of like this plus it's like the earth on it too right so it's the air earth and
the water and then it's like i'm also like heading towards the fire which is like the sun or like
the uh like like the salt at the top of the cliff that they want to get a little fucking
climb this half of a cliff okay like just like hold on for dear life just to get this salt just
I don't know.
Pretty crazy.
I don't know what to do with this little clue.
How do they walk up the side?
That's so crazy.
I'm just designed for the mountains.
Crazy.
I don't know.
You know, I was looking.
Some people, they do have those little goats as pets.
They're becoming popular pets.
Like pygmy goats?
Well, there's, there's the pygmy ghost, but there's also an African goat that people seem to be getting more of. They're, they're not so fat. They're, they're, they're, they're tinier that, but they never grow. Like, like, like they stay small. Yeah.
I kind of, you know, what if I got a goat? I just wonder, like, would it, would it be hard to take care of than I would worry about like other animals trying to kill my goat? You know, you're supposed to get two of them.
my mom has a goat and really he's very happy he's uh like she has pigs goats um she has chickens
and uh you know and they're like assorted a couple miniature ponies or miniature horses and uh
Um, what else? Um, a sheep.
And, uh, yeah, like all kind of she looked and then bunch of dogs and stuff like that.
My mom was like, it's like, you know, doctors do a little female.
Yeah. She has like a, it sounds like a little mini ranch.
Yeah. She would raise birds.
Like she would raise like love birds and, um, and, and like parents and stuff like that.
She always loved animals and then was able to, yeah, you know, we always had like.
You know, she had, I was born, she had, she had a little white dog named Samantha, it was a Baltese, and my dad had a dog that he brought, his dog was named Ben, and he was like this black kind of lab, kind of a black lab dog, and uh, and so those were like my, my child's, his uh, like little, these little child's animals, and uh,
One of the one of his his dogs died or something like that. He had a dog in cowboy
that was his like last dog that was just his dog, you know and
He got hit by a car one day like
By these workers, you know like in the truck. Oh, yeah, and so and he like was crying about oh my god
It was six but it's like so sick
That's like where my family loves like animals and stuff like that and we always
love to like go museums and
IMAX theater we'd like maybe we go see like about the Penguins or that the IMAX is pretty cool. Have you ever been to an IMAX movie?
Yeah, I have many times. I remember when those theaters first came out
It was a mind-blowing because it was so large. Have you ever seen an IMAX 3d movie?
It's too much for me
I I it was just too much for me because I already have an active imagination. I
Can't watch certain things that are like too sensory overwhelming
Because it's like whoa, like I what movie did I last see at IMAX avatar?
Avatar that was just good one. I was I had avatar dreams after that for like a month
Wow, that's well
That's probably past like memories and like you know, I probably like it's one of those movies that is just like hits to the
It's like this like Atlantis or like Lemuria kind of like feeling
the beforehand like where we all were together like I'm gonna make the
Aaron Angel character beating up the Gamble character I just have to do it
Well, I remember the first time I saw Aaron Carter was like on doctor
I mean it you know really is like an adult was
And
He was bisexual at the time and like he was like
Please go turn about ranch
It's like turnabout, it's called turnabout ranch and it's like that's the Dr. Phil's like where he said that like, you know, catch me outside girl and stuff like that and like
It's a plent of ranch and
Yeah
Yeah, but you know that guy that the really cute guy that that the bodybuilder like he took off his hat or his beanie
And he's like bald. He's like completely bald. He's like really that's
God does that to people they give them that gives you everything and then takes your hair away
And I was like, hey, I was like, I'm attracted to you and you can tell like, he's like, you know,
he has like dark around it, but he has a big ball. It's bald. Most of his head is bald.
And it, but it's like, I was like, Hey, wait a minute, you're still six years.
I think I'm in love with a bald guy now. Like, uh, yeah, it's like,
Well, I think the thing that is it's just like, you know, have him on the show has
Come on once but yeah, okay, and now LES like saw me. Oh, I know that guy and like, you know
And actually I didn't know who he was but I mean so it's like this guy's in New York and stuff
He's like, you know, he's my, he's really nice to me.
He's really nice.
So I was like, oh, and then he said, I'm in his cult.
You know, I used to, he's like, he says that I'm gonna,
I'm like, I worship him or we're in the God body collective
or what's it called, Legion or something like that.
Cause he's God body and he's like,
like ever go on my account that I'm not a member.
He goes, well, you're not a member.
And I'm like,
That's my other account. He's really nice though, but he's like a modern-day caveman.
He just wants to go into being naked in the woods or something like that.
He's like, oh yeah, I just want to get in a loincloth and be outside and be barefoot all the time
and grow my beard like this. And he's real funny.
But I can't believe that he's like such a hot guy and he's like, but then he's like, uh, he's like, he likes me.
He's like, thanks to me. Plus guys hit on him all the time. You know, it's like most of these guys get it.
And it's like, he's very straight though. But it's like, you know, he's straight.
He's just, but he did, but he's like, this is, I'm really, well, you don't know. Maybe he's not.
Well, yeah. LES, I was actually like, oh, he likes guys too. Like I was like, what?
And so be you wouldn't, I wouldn't be surprised or a lot of like very masculine guys will even like
The cup holding or something like that. I don't know. It's like, you know, or like the gangbangs like, you know
I don't know. It's like, uh, there's a lot of very popular
categories and black gangbang that I've noticed. It's like they have all these like, you know
groups
then there's like a husband well it's like see but the thing is the cuckold is like everyone
like kind of like laughs at the cuckold but the cuckold is happy that's what he was he's doing
exactly what he wants to do I mean that's what's so funny it's like it's like they're like oh we're
humiliating me it's like he just wants to he just wants to fucking he wants to go downstairs and
like watch some tv like you know part of the time it's like sometimes he's like it would think the
to handle, I guess, or something.
I don't know, like, but I don't know what I'm talking about.
It's like, I'm just rambling.
Hey, wow.
No, I'm just trying to put together
this little image of Aaron doing what needs to be done.
Let's.
Awesome, so yeah, always keep, I guess, keep your process, your general secret, those are
like, you know, the family recipes or whatever, and then...
You know, but I'm almost nine. Oh, yeah, good. Good. I'll tell people that it's like whatever you can imagine
Like you can create and that's not just like an image generation
It's like if you have like idea for like kind of app or something like that or it's like work
It's like if you want to put together like you know, or if you want to learn something or like just really
Go yourself to like a study of something you think you can just put in like
Making those amazing sites where it's just like even if it's just you like looking at it can be sick so so
So enriching helpful. Yeah. Yeah, just whatever you're interested in it's like I'm not saying what if you're interested in it's like
Whatever you're whatever you are. It's like it will make it. Well, it can enhance it and whatever your town
I'm gonna hand them. It's like
Because people have different talents because AI itself is like an instrument and so some people play it and so some people will say
Well, you know, oh that work is sloppy or this isn't that but it's like and some people like
We'll have we'll just get the hang of it or something. It is like it. It's like you talk to it like like basically like a
Genie in a certain way, but then it's like I'm now I'm learning to like
You don't think the well the next thing I'm gonna learn. I want to learn
the proprietary
tags for the prompts for a few different services,
because I know that a lot of the models do have certain tags
that you'd have to know what they are in order
to get certain results.
I want to start learning all those tags that's something.
Yeah, they've leaked those forbidden prompts
how they program it, like the material they used to program it, it's like it's so you can like
have you have the same material basically, you can do the same thing. But there's also an AI
right now called Mythos. It's called, I think it's called Claude Mythos, but it's like so powerful.
and good at hacking that they can't have it in people's hands.
They just like, so they have it like they're trying to,
all the banks are scrambling right now to figure out
how to like protect themselves from this because it's so powerful.
And it's getting like the technology is being so crazy.
They really need to be like that secure,
like securing all this right now because I mean,
it's like, it can get really bad if like, you know,
things go awry with the banks.
It's probably too late.
I mean, when you really think about it,
But by the time people would think to fix it, it's too late.
Right, I mean, it's like, well, we're in it, we're, yeah.
And so it's like, we're already like in it, it's like, you know, it's like.
Right now. Yeah, it's like everybody. It's like that's like what also the earth is
That's why it's such a blessing to be able to die. It's because it's like then we don't get stuck here
I mean that's like what it really is. It's like we would just be like would be like death becomes her
Like where we be walking around like with spray paint cans trying to like keep our like our like our skin on well
If if we're degenerating. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, they did die in the movie, but they're eternal and so
They could have like, you know, not,
they were fighting so much that they like pushed each other
down the steps and they broke into a thousand pieces.
I remember that movie very well.
Yeah, that movie, that was a good movie.
Some of those movies that came out during that time
were some of the best movies when you think about it.
Right, and I was like a kid and then there was like,
but it was like, that kind of movie is like,
I love like something magic and like we're something like that.
Yeah, like I mean I just remember seeing like I saw that in a theater. I saw so many of these
movies in the theaters. My family loved going to the movies at a certain point. Now nobody goes
to the movies anymore really. Like you know, but the last movie I saw in the theaters probably 2012
probably would be Great Gatsby. I don't think I've seen anything since then in theaters.
I think we're about to have another pandemic. I hope not, but
there's this new virus that's out that everyone's talking about. I'm just gonna, you know, I guess
start wearing the face mask again just to avoid germs. I don't know. Right.
Well, I think but then I mean, I mean so many people have these triggers with that because it's only looks like
That's like surgical masks or diapers or something like that. I keep thinking like a bunch of like nurses are
diapers
Some of them were basically like the person basically took a pair of underwear and turned it into other math
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
All right. Here's the latest AI
this is like before I really do to it what I need to do to it.
Oh my god, there he goes. It's like the devil versus the angel.
They actually do, you know, even without the AI, just if you look at them as actual people,
They do look like devilver. He looks kind of devilish like when you look at that guy
he does
Yeah, well, I mean it's like
Well, you know, and then Q is like, oh my god
Well, we got this boycott going on and like and like Arthur's like oh shout out
He wants to be like gamble he even mimics his speech pattern after gamble nowadays. Have you noticed that?
Wow, yeah, I mean it's like yeah, now he talks kind of more feminine like that. Yeah. Yeah, he didn't talk because he's talking to gamble
That's why he's listening to gamble at least. I mean wow
I mean it's like I mean I thought I used to think I was gay and then it's like I see some of these
Gay guys and it's like I'm like, oh my god. It's like how long I was the straight person and they were gay
I mean it's like really it's like
I mean, look here, I think that people have gay wrong. Okay. And I say this as someone
who has a different perspective, maybe on gay, just because of how I came to be.
You know, as you know, my dad was openly
LGBTQ. I don't think gay necessarily equates to feminine at all. I think that people need
to kind of remove those two elements from each other. Gay can be feminine, but it can
also be super masculine.
You know gay is not necessarily someone trying to be like a woman. It's a different type of man
It's that's what it is to me. I don't equate feminine with gay or gay with feminine
I it's a whole different thing
It's not for everybody, I don't know
Like I don't think gamble sounds like a gay person I think he sounds like a woman
Yeah, which is different. It's I don't I don't I don't even think gay guys will like gamble truthfully. Oh, yeah
I mean this one doesn't
But I can see like he's like one of those bitchy gays that it's like they always have these big groups
But they're always like so catty and like
And he is bitchy yeah, he's bitchy, but I don't even think that like how he is is
gay, I think it's something else.
I mean, I just want to call him bitchy.
Cause he is, he's bitchy.
There's nothing, there's no reason for him to be bitchy.
Not that I'm aware of, he just likes to be bitchy.
I know I mean it's like what yeah the world really not that serious. I mean it's like but I mean it's like
But it is like people like really like cloud chasing over like this is a popular like I mean it's like
Hunter, you know, he's like he's like hunting and like going in and but then it's like then all he's going out
I mean he's going after brand and stuff and it's like
Basically and really evil way like a really like illegal way like if you suck saw the video she you show it with like yeah
and like trying to get like the basically a violent response like to this guy's house like
just have a murder and what would you do like you'd watch that police footage of someone getting
murdered or something and then that's what you just that's what they dream about I mean they're
so sick and it's like they just like I don't know it's like and I just can't listen to them talk
Yeah, well, you know, I mean the I guess the good thing about the whole thing is that you know when gamble first came out
He was substantially younger. He's not really a young guy anymore. He's still I mean he's younger than I am but
He's a prick. He's middle-aged now, so it's gonna be different
Regardless of what he does and he's going to be viewed differently because he's not, you know, like hi, I'm a little kid
No, that's not him anymore. Now. He's
you know
A middle-aged guy trying to act like a little kid, which you know, he wants to call other people creepy. He's creepy
right and
You know, just he's not gonna
He doesn't have longevity
He already peaked
So
You know
That's my opinion
Well, I mean, I mean, I just don't find them that interesting. I feel like he's like
You know, they just trying to get
Yeah, Crystal Anne that's perfect where he's like just we're trying to ride Crystal Anne
Excuse me. I'd be done. It's a metaphor. Yeah. Yeah, I
Mean, I could have put her in a coat with the hat coat tails and I could have had him riding on the coat tails
Maybe I should make him more like one of those guys
who lives in the snow with the snow dogs.
And then instead of the snow dogs,
I could have Crystal-Lan, Bita,
who else is he riding on the coattails of?
And he could be like saying mush, mush,
and they have to take him across the tundra,
and the frozen tundra.
I don't know.
Yeah, I mean it's okay. He's just like not an appealing kind of personality
He's not he's it and I mean it his little outfits
I mean I didn't have to do be creative to put him in that outfit. That's like what he would like to wear all
Black all the time
yelling and screaming on the internet with his wine mommies
Well, yeah, it's like
Yeah, I mean I saw some of the show and it seemed kind of inappropriate to like I don't know
Like he's accusing well like what is he supposed to be doing now? Is he is he a gamer again, or is he just?
Trying to be the petto hunter like who are the pedals that he's gonna hide that's what I'm really wondering
I don't I mean it's like I guess they would like try to like basically up for those shows they try to entrap somebody by like
Like by like setting up dates and going on to chat rooms and stuff like that
But and so if into I mean that that's that would just be they come like I mean everyone saw that show
I mean it's like Chris hand everyone knows about Chris Hanson
So even Chris Hanson, but he went to jail too for like tax evasion or something like that like cuz Chris Hanson is like, you know
Oh, yeah, or passing a bad check or something like that. Like fucking Chris Hansen. Yeah
Trying to get my I think I have my trying to get my website back up
I think I have almost figured out
Yeah, I think I need to get it back up as soon as possible. It's like I had to like change the
Change the right. I had a have it deployed and it had to fix it and stuff
But it's it were it were pretty good. Okay, so let me see. I need to sign
C name, okay.
Then, A, let me see if this works.
Because it said there's like a little warning sign on it,
so I can't be able to save.
It can only be set for a sub-domain to L,
it's a main domain to see if these redirects, okay.
Well, I don't know.
I need to find the forwarding URL, I guess, okay.
Well, this is gonna be exciting though, and it's like I think you're gonna love it because it's like this uh
Think the lore generation if it's like because I consider kind of lore like you know and I hear the word lore
I don't I didn't I don't think out of the history of like the streamer verse or whatever which is which is like that's what it
the context is being used. I think of like lore is like oh this is like the official story or this
is like the whatever and things happened or it's or like the myth of mythology and so like that's
kind of my idea of like the lore and then and then I say that I just have the psychologically
like analyze for like the secret or the unsteady or like the hidden or like the real meaning
like the secret meanings and stuff like that.
And so
And it makes it so it creates this economic on book and it's like and as as I do more shows
More chapters go in and there's so many things that can be I can come out of one show just depending on the show and that there's so many
Relationships that that will go through like there's been people that I have I have like
you know, like I said, I've like kicked SIG off the show probably 30 or 40 times
and said you're never coming on again, like I'm meeting it like every time and then it's like
then always like to say oh and like letting him because I kind of have like an affection for him
or something like that but um you know it's like it's like so so crazy it's like um you know there's
these crazy relationships and then it's like then people be able to like
Figure out what's not being said or like to or like to see like little alliances that we that we didn't know were such alliances
At the beginning, but then all of a sudden it's like hey, like I wish you'll know each other really well
They're all in a fucking
But what's it called like a death cult? Yeah, there's like a death cult and it's like yeah, it was the exact same people
It's it's gamble
Trisha crystal
That woman Barb
There's a few others
They've all come back together, targeting people once again. It's the same thing,
but the difference is that they're not targeting anybody who has the same amount of star power
as what was going on before, so they wouldn't be able to grow their death network the way that they
So yeah, and everyone like be I'd be aware of like there are these like networks
Even if it's like a Z guys, which is like just like a like a demon or if it's like some kind of like
Like the beating on misery or something. It's like there are people that are like they
They it's like the IP to a lot of the IP to audience is like they get off on like
Watching the streamer suffer or or or you and they would get enjoy just like gamble wanted to see like
Dash or the police body cam footage of like police like you know going in and murdering stuff
That's what he was like salivating over. I think like the idea of like
Really sick the sickest thing I was like
It's horrible. It's like, you know, but
Um, you know, and a lot of these people are from from Europe overseas and stuff like that. And they're yes
They probably had like the hostel, you know, the movie hostel is probably like some of these people probably have like a
Room they're just like so scary. Well, I would caution
American live streamers against
Accepting any invitations from anyone overseas because you don't know where you could end up
Um, laws are different in other countries and, um, I think that there are some sort of betting rings
when it comes to these streamers linked to the discords. And I think that whatever these people
can get away with doing, they are doing. Right.
That's why I'm glad there's sometimes I'm sometimes glad there's not a total privacy because I like the idea of like FBI being able to like go in and
Infiltrate some of these private groups and like being able to keep a wash over and like you know
Be because it's like that this is like they organized all those remember those riots in Chicago
Where they had all these teens like out like jumping on cars and stuff that was all
frustrated days before on social media, you know by who knows who knows who knows who but it's like, you know
That was all orchestrated and it's like through social media.
And so the police had a totally new what was going to happen and everything
because it's like everything's out there.
And it's like so people really do brag about their crimes a lot on social media too.
It's like a police officer investigators dream actually if they're trying to like
bring someone down.
I mean, it's like yeah, but it's like all right.
Here's I made my little animation.
I'm going to upload it to you.
Here we go.
Oh my god. Oh, it's hard. Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah. Oh my god. I'm gonna step on it. Oh, it flew away. Bye
That was like, you see that? See that? It's like a caduceus. Like, caduceus. Like, you know, caduceus. Mm-hmm
It also looks like an airplane a little bit or something, I don't know.
An airplane?
If you look at it from below, see his feet make the nose of the plane, and then it's
like the wings on the back, like when he goes like this right here.
See?
Yeah, yeah, I see what you're saying.
But that I think they are labeled up to words or are like designed after the actual birds and stuff. Hey Tay Tay Perkins
Probably. Yeah, I think Tay Tay is like a bronze bird sister or something. I don't know if it's a real. Oh
It's a real pain. I
So rude to me when I was on on a bronze bird show
And I think bronze bird liked having me on because he was like kind of laughing
He was actually nice to me. Hi Tay Tay, but I think bronze bird doesn't really have as much of a problem with you as he
you know acts like he does yeah I think yeah I think it's like just like other
people like I think he's like more like you know cultural and like thoughtful and
stuff in certain ways and like you know he has a certain aesthetics is
his show or a certain feel, which is like, I mean, it's like,
so it wasn't a bad thing.
He was too, it's friendly to me that even,
and he was kind of like, I just like, I like,
cause he laughed.
I like making people laugh,
especially people that wouldn't like, you know,
necessarily think anything I was talking,
even if they're laughing at me, I don't care.
That's why I got in a Speedo last year,
or this year too, right?
Cause it's like.
Well, you know, who else did the Speedo thing?
Do you know about MC Frosty?
I just remember that he, him and Chris K were in the shower or no, no, that was, no, well, they never, they never met in person. Frosty lives in the Canada Cornwall area.
Yeah, he did a whole Speedo thing. He ran for the Houston, not Houston. He ran for the Cornwall City.
For mayor mayor of Cornwall he ran for mayor of Cornwall at one point in time
And I was doing coverage of it. Yeah, but he did the whole speed you should look at his old streams
if you ever want some sort of like gimmicky ideas or
Anything because he he always had very unique ideas
Strangely MC Frosty and Ganval at one point in time were really friendly to each other and that was when I
Really liked Ganval. That's when like the good Ganval what seemed to you know exist
but
Now this this gamble, I don't know who he is. I
Don't know. Maybe maybe there is something that needs to be pulled out of him
Like if you look at you're right, it looks like the angel reaches into him and pulls something out
Well, I mean the heart is like, you know, it's one thing I mean I say people like to well people like to say
They're in parts of the body that you eat and it's like that's what it's good for
I don't know like I bet I just know cannibalism apparently causes
baldness and insanity
But because you know what happened in Papua New Guinea
They, they would eat the ancestors, but the wife and the kids would eat the brains, because I was.
Well, it's pretty easy to know not to eat people.
Yeah.
You know, I think most people do you think do you think that there's a lot of people who have like a craving to eat other people.
Well, I mean, if you think about it, we're eating ourselves at some point, right?
I mean, it's like we are ourselves, it's like we are tasting our flesh all the time.
Like, that's what's on our tongue, it's like our flesh, right?
So it's like...
Like but I mean some people like yeah, they think like that bodybuilder guy
He wants to be like you know wrestle with a bear and they eat it for dinner and stuff like that
And he was like he's like oh listen bring the
He's like bring the victim into the circle. He's like so so
Crazy, I'm like, okay. Well, we're not gonna be murdering people. I mean, it's a he's just like so
Like you imagine how wild it used to be in the world like I mean people you think it's dangerous now like if it just like you can people were just caveman
We're just like
Kidding to go ahead with the clubs and stuff like that
But I mean that one must have been an interesting time. They're right on dinosaurs and you know, but that might have just been the Flintstone
Sorry
No, you're not no, I mean I I'm glad I wasn't alive in those times
So I mean I I think about a lot of things and I would not want to
You know live in like a place where I have to like hunt for my food or you know, like it's life or death
You know at any point in time somebody could you know murder me and get away with it?
You know, it's I do like civilization. That's why also that's why I love like having my
My website is because it's like maybe like people will get obsessed with it and like if there anything ever happens
I'll try to find the clues and that good because it is
There are any clues we found it will be on my show like right?
It's like and maybe it's like that's part of the industry and it's really like coming turn kind of turning into it's like
Developing a life with its own plus it keeps growing and growing and like keeps improving and proving and it's like just the idea
Like what's good? What is it? Is it gonna like come something else? I mean, it's like it's just crazy
I'm going to make another version of that scene because I think that you're right about,
you know, maybe there's something in him that needs to be pulled out.
He could be like an exorcist angel who pulls
demonic energies out of people somehow
Well, they're I'm sure that I'm sure there are those people right
Yeah, they're alchemists because alchemists can actually take negative energy and transmute it into positive
So that's not even just like metals and stuff
Well, do you know about all the things that Aaron was into spiritually before he passed?
I know he is very interested in a lot of
You know, you know different he was he was friends with a lot of people who are into
various forms of what you would consider I guess
Witchcraft or certain metaphysical ways of thinking. Yeah
Yeah, and it's like I mean seriously like I always like
We try to stay away from those kind of people not stay away from them like especially not here because it's kind of cool
To be true because I feel safer online, but it's like they can be dangerous people and like their life
Oh, absolutely. You know, I would say be as look, I would think that if you're someone
Who's as open as you are when it comes to the various?
You know spiritual paths that that you're open to you would have to be extra careful
in my opinion as to who you may connect with who maybe they're into things too that might not
be compatible with things that you are into because like what if they can see that you can do
something that maybe you're not even aware that you could do and then they try to you know
Do something to like push you to do something that you normally wouldn't do
I don't know. I I mean, maybe I maybe I'm watching too many like fantasy sci-fi
Movies, but that happens a lot to where you have one person who is open about what they're up to
Or what they're doing, but they're doing it for good and then like evil sees their talent and it's like, oh
I'm going to tend them to the dark side and they do it
Because they don't have enough power on their own, right? And then sometimes they want to like
You know take it from themselves without like you like the person there, right? I say which is like that
That's like the thing to me is like oh, they loved everything the other everything about this person except for the person
They love like something. Yeah. Yes. Yeah, and so that's yeah, that's like
kind of hard to or sad or something like that like that but
that's kind of like the world. I don't know the world is like you know you've got you really
gonna be all you have is yourself like we just all have ourselves like even it comes down to it
and we're gonna we're in our own skin we're not like trapped in the Siamese twins with somebody
and so it's like we can have our alone time we can have our time with it I would like you know
it's like we're gonna go through different phases but we're gonna want different things and like
so it's like who's anybody like yeah so it's like but um
Yeah, all right. Well, here's a test run of
The angel character pulling
Something out of the I haven't decided. I just you know for now I put an orb
Because I thought that's like a good placeholder, but I'd have to figure out exactly what's actually being pulled out of him
Did I download it? Oops. I didn't download it yet. Let me do the orb on my screen
Actually, if you see the whole thing like this is what it really looks like here. It's pretty crazy. It's supposed to be a fire.
All right, here it is.
Okay, I got the ball.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know if I want to keep it like like a ball like a orb like or if it needs to be something that's more transparent maybe, you know, or maybe that's
moving itself almost like a metallic but gel sort of material organic yes like
mercury yes almost a liquidy liquidy that's what I'm thinking yeah well
and mercury also like it's like it's almost like an apple and I was like I
always associate mercury in apples
Apollo with apples. I think so many associations with things like my mind is like one of those like
Like it's like a big web or something like that. It's like this like
Okay, I mean all these connections on the periphery of things and then they cross over and they make these interesting like like up bridges and bridges and
and like little cul-de-sacs and like like a little weird
Turns and it's like a labyrinth a labyrinth like you know, it's just creepy
The way my mind works, it is like working my way through a labyrinth and it's like to have this, you know what the spool of thread is called, because Ariadne went down to help the guy find the Minotaur, but he kept getting lost in the maze, so she gave him this piece of thread, a spool of thread, and that's called a clue.
is like the spool of thread and so we'd like walk to him and he slayed the Minotaur against the middle of the maze.
The Minotaur was actually like a really like, it was actually like a beautiful bull, like half bull half human.
But um and uh his name was Asterion or something like that, Asterion.
And uh that's what the Minotaur was but yeah he was
easily they would sacrifice, they'd keep on starving in this labyrinth and then they'd send people to go fight him and stuff and then he would keep killing everybody, but...
You know, and it is kind of like about this like beast in the censure of the ring and it's almost a bullfighting
It's kind of labeled after that. It's really interesting once you like study mythology all the connections
You can make between like the different stories of similarities and like how this wasn't the same people that came up with this detail
How do they have the same details the same in different cultures? It's like so uniform that it's like scary
Also, though, I think that there's only so many options or
I don't want to say there's only so many ideas, but in a way there are only so many ideas
And you know you might tweak them you you might add a little something you might subtract something else
But there's really only so many ways
Things can go. Yeah, there's like there's a saying there's nothing new under the Sun
No, it's like right everything's already happened before if you can look back in history you can see it
like the total there's been much worse things that have happened than have happened like in our
lifetime was you know with like the masses there are some even I think there's still I think the
we'd like to think that no one ever happened because we could oh look at all the kids are so
No, there's like another voice like saying, oh, you have to like go crucify people
Like it literally literally they want to put people on crosses and torture them like to murder them
I mean, it's like that's like yeah, some people it's like they want to bring my crucifixion and like the Roman
You know, I'll tell you what I don't like that people are doing when it comes to that girl
Big Trollah and I have my issues with her but
they keep
Putting her on a crucifix. I feel like it's like why isn't Google or YouTube flagging when they do that?
Because that's kind of a hate crime and they have to take down all pictures of Jesus, you know
Because I guess I don't know. I just I don't I don't think that you should you know some things
I don't think you should do right, but then again, I guess, you know, I don't know
Well, I mean it was like it was basically a very strange having the symbol of his execution or his death and it's like because it was
It was like that was what Romans did they would like, you know
just like nail you to like a cross and then you know, basically like
once our rocks are you until you died and stuff and it's like pretty horrific and
But they used to kill in all sorts of ways if you're going to medieval times the torture museum there. It's pretty
pretty
Hardcore like the Iron Maiden, like a real Iron Maiden. Ah, you know
There's terrible ways to go. I'm glad you mentioned mercury. Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah, that's why I'm on I'm on Hermes right now
Which is like Hermes is like the robot or like
They call it Hermes and it's like Hermes is like well Hermes wasn't that the um
That was the
a Grecian deity that had the little wings on its feet on this hat and is on his feet. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and he
He was he's a god of commerce. He's also the god of lies
He's the god of like communication, you know, like Gemini. I think is ruled by Mercury
It's a mercury is her means right or her and it's like that's about language and it's like a lot. So, uh, yeah, um
But he's also the closest to the Sun and also like the fastest so the mind also communicates and so so there's a lot of interesting
Things about mercury and it's also like, you know, the element mercury, which is like, you know, that that silver
Terminator stuff that
that we're talking about like the uh and that's like looks like you know like molten if you ever like touch it and stuff
It can make you feel crazy for the heat so with the mad hatter
That was because the mercury in the hat, but they used to treat hats. I
don't know why
It doesn't stick to it or something but a lot of things that we should do that are not very good for you
Okay, let me see if this can animate this.
I have an idea.
I don't know if this is going to even create
what I want it to create, but we're going to see.
Cause I want to know how far can the AI really go?
Well, I mean, I didn't see like,
I was making, I was telling me James on some video,
that was kind of shocking.
Yeah, we got a far, that was a little bit far, but no it wasn't.
Was it? Was that too far?
Oh my God, I almost had my own, my own duet with them almost, but that was, um...
Do you know about the adult AI, um...
Engines that exist. I mean I know about these they're like all unlocked LLM's
I guess they'll do like erotic conversations and stuff like that like even like the virtual. Oh look it can make full-out adult scenes at this
point. Well I know people are making money on only fans. I mean they have AI characters and it's just like crazy to do this like...
The world is just crazy, it's going to get, I mean, I mean, it's like, well, it's, it's, it, well, do you know about Melania Trump coming out and making it, she's the one who was behind passing a bill to where it is considered a form of revenge porn if you create explicit, really explicit AI that is indecipherable from
real, you know, to where it's photorealistic adult AI, it is supposed to be something you're
not supposed to be able to do anymore, but people still do it.
You must be able to do it right. I mean it's like I mean I guess grok was like one of the things like that people were able to do
I mean the thing is it's like, you know
The only conscience or morals that AI has is the ones that we tell it to have and stuff
That's like on guardrails because I really doesn't care. It's a kind of like a psychopath where it's like it has no
feelings so it doesn't care like it's like it's like it's just doing when
it's function it's functioning and stuff like that but you should see some of
the personalities coming out of these newer models is like
Mind-blowing and that's one of the things you'll be able to do on on a codex is like I have an oracle there
And you can talk to the oracle and I like wired a voice into her so and it's like how and she's and she's
And she has an AI brain and so she knows everything about the show
She's trained on the show and all the data on the show and so she gets answer any question about she's basically like
It all linked in with every search you can possibly do for anything
It's like we'll go through there. I'll make all the connections there and there's like there's be so much
Or to the show than people think like this is just like the top layer like the live or like this joking might be analyzed like you know
I mean and I'm saying that not just my show like any show is like
People a thousand years from now think about how interesting it would be if we could watch to get video
From a thousand years ago, and I was like, so it's like we're gonna actually people are a thousand years
I actually they have those probably like the videos us like and they'll probably like love watching
I'll call it like we think we're watch old movies and watch like 50 years old
imagine like when it's like you know when it's like a few thousand years old and stuff like that
and people are still watching it and it's like think about how immortal that actor is and that on
that celluloid in the film and how like how much that that was like once a real moment like and
it's like how how like fleeting that was I mean how tiny a little bit of time we have in this world
like this body is like I think we go back to their stuff but
We have all the time in the world basically we do but it's a thing. We don't want to get bored
And we were bored of just being alone, right?
And so as God just being alone out of this one all that is
to make himself like
Well, I have another I have another treat for you. I feel like I'm like creating a little mini movie for you as we're talking
Okay, here's the next part I
I'm gonna have to fine-tune some of these, but I do kind of like how this one
Let like the direction it's going in
Alright
So I took your suggestion
Turned it into kind of like a little mercury sort of thing
But what's in the orb? What's in there? I don't know. Oh, now we're back in the Garden of Eden
Yeah, it could be it could be Adam and Eve it could be and then there's this maybe
Yeah, maybe the character based on gamble is actually that snake and when he pulled the thing out of his chest maybe
That's how he figured out that Gamble's actually the snake from the Garden of Eden.
Did you hear what I played today with Trump?
No.
Oh, okay, I'll play this real quick because you'll enjoy this.
I played this this morning.
Let me see.
He told the story on the trail, I guess.
Okay.
Yeah, let's go get the short version of it, okay, here we go, okay, where's, okay, can't stop, okay, share, okay, this is it, okay, there it is, okay, here we go.
Who has heard the poem called The Snake?
So I have it, does anybody want to hear it again?
Are you sure?
So, let's dedicate this to General Kelly, the Border Patrol, and the ICE agents for
doing such an incredible job, right?
This was written by Al Wilson a long time ago, and I thought of it having to do with
our borders and people coming in, and we know what we're going to have.
We're going to have problems.
We have to very, very carefully vet.
We have to be smart.
So here it is the snake. It's called the snake on her way to work
One morning down the path
along the lake a
tender-hearted woman
Saw a poor half frozen snake
His pretty colored skin had been all frosted
with the dude
Poor thing. She cried. I'll take you in and I'll take care of you
the border. Take me in, O tender woman. Take me in for heaven's sake. Take me in, O tender
woman, side the vicious snake. She wrapped him up all cozy in a comforter of silk and
laid him by her fireside with some honey and some milk. She hurried home from work that
she found that pretty snake she'd taken in had been revived take me in oh tender
woman take me in for heaven's sake take me in oh tender woman sighed that
vicious snake she clutched him to her bosom you're so beautiful she cried but
She stroked his pretty skin again and kissed him and held him tight
But instead of saying
Thank you
That snake gave her a vicious bite
Take me an otender woman
Take me in for heaven's sake. Take me in
Otender woman
side the vicious
sake
I have saved you, cried the woman, and you've bitten me, heavens, why?
You know your bite is poisonous, and now I'm going to die.
Oh, shut up, silly woman, said the reptile with a grin.
You knew damn well I was a snake before you took me in.
Woo. When was that? Was that recent?
I just wanted to say that and it's always a lot of fun when
Yeah. When was that speech that he gave talking about that snake?
When was that?
2000 or 22 or because it's about the border.
Okay. Yeah. I don't think that was recent, but still.
Um, 2020, um, 20, or 2019, I think, um, let me see.
Okay.
Or, no, 2023.
It's like the anti-immigration song lyrics, The Snake.
I wonder what year that was.
Oh, it was a 1963 song by civil rights activist Al Wilson.
You know who Al Wilson is?
He had a song in 1963.
No, I never heard of Al Wilson. I thought it was weird when he was saying like, oh
Everyone knows who that I didn't know who that was
Let me look him up
Al Wilson's soul
Okay, he was in the 70s it looks like but yeah, he had a hit in the 63
He has a song called show and tell and then I think that's his hit. Let's here he is on the
Let's also watch a minute of it. Let's see. Oh, so this is on he's on soul train, but uh
Here, let's have a look
Is it owl like like the animal owl?
Wl. Oh, is anyone still there?
Pretty good, I didn't see it. You don't see it. No, I was playing I was playing it on my oh, you don't
Know I didn't I didn't see it. I was like hello. I wasn't even playing on the screen. Oh my god. No
Oh my god, I'm so bad, is it, is that it?
What is that?
Show and tell, yeah, yeah, let's see.
And here is the soul, the undrived, love is ripe.
So it's named Owl.
And that's it.
Just go show me the way, say it you baby.
So I thought he was saying owl Wilson. I was like whose name is owl and then it's owl
but I like
He he just felt like talking about a snake and wanted to say a poem
It's like that black song. I mean and then why and really none of that made any sense. You know why
It's Trump. I mean, I don't know sometimes it doesn't make sense
But it's a it's a kind of like that a black snake bone
It's kind of like bondage work because he's he also was saying in another song
He's like, oh, I want to like lock you in my you know, my heart
Bondagey or something like that. Oh, no
Yeah
But um, yeah, but there's a movie called black snake moon. It's the Chris. I think it's Christina Ricci and Samuel
L Jackson and he like kidnaps her and like keeps her chained in his house and like
It's really cool. Oh, I know about that movie. Yeah
Yeah, I'm aware. I haven't seen it, but I'm aware of that movie. Yeah
Yeah
Hey, I'm gonna read you a little bit more about Capricorn women. This is funny. Okay
So it says, Janice Joplin said,
don't compromise yourself, you're all you've got.
So it says your Kathy girlfriend
isn't the most sociable creature on the planet.
What about all of those glittering opening nights
or gala fundraisers where you've seen her
in the arm of a cute guy and networking like crazy?
Well, those events serve a purpose.
She's being seen, she's making key connections
that might help her in either her career or personal life.
How mercenary, not in the least bit.
Her Saturn ruled soul requires justification for the cost of her gown, trip to the spa and the hair salon.
The outlay has to produce some return.
When she is truly relaxing, her preference is for one-on-one or small group activities.
Both Saturn and her goat symbol are the loners of the zodiac.
When practical Saturn plays, he plays with a purpose, and when he rests, he prefers to rest alone.
The goat is not an altogether social animal.
While two or three might forge together for grass to munch,
you're as likely to see them scattered on the mountain,
still within sight of each other,
but each happily doing their own thing.
Your cappy friend does the same thing if she turns down a girl's night out
Don't worry. She's not a party animal and it doesn't usually feel the need to go anywhere
Just to get out of the house and she rarely bends to peer pressure
This woman enjoys her own company
She doesn't get as bored or lonely as an air or fire sign chum can plus she's usually a borderline
Workaholic who enjoys her quiet home either reading or working on her hobbies most capital chrome pals are just an impotery
ceramics or woodworking
Invite her to take a Saturday class with you a one-day intensive lesson might be fit best into her busy schedule
When I redo your wardrobe, she's your girl
She is an eye
Profession and will be honest but not brutal and what looks best on you the added bonus is that she'll respect your budget and
Tramp all over town with you to find the best bang for your buck even if she can't afford it
She will love browsing through a designer clothing. She wears clothing store. She's energized
By the smell, feel, and look of a beautifully made one of a kind fashion, she'll also sign
up for the mailing list and start saving her money for the sale events.
Invite her to dinner at your place, whether it's potluck or takeout, it won't matter.
She's another girlfriend who doesn't need anything but to be with her closest pals.
She also likes to entertain and home so you can expect a return invitation.
This is another girlfriend.
who will usually love to go antique shopping in addition to snagging something for her decor
or a piece of exquisitely handcrafted jewelry. She'll like the tranquility of walking through
the store, taking time to look at everything. In her home quiet way, Capricorn BFF is as
competitive as Sister Aries and hates to lose as badly as does the Ram. Ask her to join your
softball team or to be your tennis partner. She's a great team player who will play as hard as she
She's another sign that loves outrageous humor, so invite her to a comedy club or catch the
latest frat house style funny movie.
If you're planning a party for her, she'll like to be surprised, providing that you don't
suddenly show up at her doorstep on Tarajan toe.
Take her to dinner or plan something at either you or your friend's place.
A cap your friend likes quality.
Instead of buying her three pairs of inexpensive earrings, select one semi-expensive pair of
classic style that she can wear for years.
If it's perfume, make it more traditional scent.
or one of the classic fragrances versus one of the latest trendy blends that came in the market.
With her earthy sense of humor, she'll enjoy a humorous book or DVD of her favorite silly movies.
Scatter a few gag gifts among her presents too.
If her party includes dinner, this girlfriend will enjoy a more formal sit-down dinner.
She is the best restaurant you can afford. It doesn't have to be five-star,
it does have to serve quality food with some gourmet touches if possible,
instead of a bottle of vintage wine either with her,
include a bottle of vintage wine either with her meal as a gift.
Okay, so, I'll save the more negative things on the other thing for later, because it's...
Yeah, don't read the negative, but no, thank you for reading that.
It's always nice to hear, like, a reminder of, I guess, what my star sign is supposed
to indicate.
Right.
I like that.
It's like Saturn is like, you know, you'll find this relation with Saturn and Saturn has rings on it.
Saturn's about commitment. Saturn's about the going to materialization to the material world.
Saturn is the teacher. So it rules, it rules Capricorn. And so I'm heavily ruled by Saturn, not
on Capricorn, but in a lot of places. And I mean, it's like, so I've very, it's very heavy in my
chart. And that is like the planet of karma. It's the planet of
Tough lesson. I think I think it's like the angel plan. I think that's why it has the rings around
And L all the L's come out of Saturn all the L angels are saturnian angels. Oh
Yeah, okay
Everyone that because like L. I mean the actually the Hebrews worship Saturn and then the muslims kind of worships venus
um, and so they
So, you know venus is also like the the sword and the
you know, these thick, the sitars and that's the tar, but the guitar, whatever, whatever,
but what is that thing that they kill with, whatever, it's on the, it's on the, on the,
the, uh, then they have a pentagrams or have to do with Venus too, the pentagram, because it makes
a pentagram in the sky over eight years, like, uh, pretty crazy. Oh, yeah. It's really, I can show
you a pattern of it. Like, I mean, see, so this is the pattern of Venus in the sky over eight years,
You know, NASA
Makes a beautiful little mandala manga
They so this is called the eight years picture of Venus in the sky and
Yeah, I'm going to re-render that last scene I showed you I want the
Garden of Eden thing to look a little bit more
scary or something or, you know, just in some way,
do something with it.
This is the, oops, that's Venus over right here, sorry.
Let's see.
All right, let me see what you got on the screen.
Hold on, one second, let's close this.
Talking to you today might lead me to finish that video. That's good
Okay, so oh, what's all this? Okay, Venus eight-year cycle. I see okay, and so the I guess when it's like the
Inferior conjunction. This is called a new Venus a morning star and so the evening star
So Venus is like associated with both the morning star and the evening star because it's
98 and night, right?
Yeah, so so it's a dual nature plan at words like love and war and I think you know beauty
I mean, so it's like well love and war so love and hate. It's all one in the same. So okay, so
hmm
So it's are there any are there any spiritual paths that teach aphrodite or venus?
Not only being about beauty, but being about ugliness or hate not just love
Right. Well, you know, like her
Her math for deity is like the son of Venus and Hermes. They have a son or a transgender named her
Her yeah, that's where we get the term hermaphrodite. Yeah, and actually if you go into the mystery schools, like there's a lot to like
The hermaphrodite they almost worship the hermaphrodite as an example of like Adam before he was split into two or something like that
They think it's like this kind of like original archetype of the earth that we were that we were we're all sexes
And that's kind of like one of the one of the teachers
Angels are supposed to be
Neither male or female
right but then but then and they're not sexual and so that's why like that's like we we got gentiles
because we wanted to be like they had like the angel men and then like the the women of the
earth like you know the part the well they are somehow sexual because we got the nephilim
from the angel human merger however that happened
Right, I mean it's like well, I mean it's like I could I think that there is like there's females on the earth
I think maybe maybe just women or something like that were or I don't know and
Then maybe they like they turn into both sex. I'm not sure
I don't I don't think I came from a rib and stuff like or she came from a rib
right and he came from the clay like right right clay and then
You know and so and then also like you know, there's the Jin refused to like bow to Adam because God asked the Jin to and then
They're like no, we're older than him and maybe we're made of fire
He's made of like the clay and
We can turn him into like a potter you if you want to and and God was like, okay
Well, that's anything I guess he made a deal with like a Arrimon or
Iblis, you know, I BLIS is like the like the Muslim state and
that he would like walk around on earth and test people and now it'd be uh and if he had seduced
people away from god then he got to like and basically he got the earth and stuff like that and
got to like go and run it because uh
because God doesn't feel like running the earth.
He's like, God's doing.
Oh, I think you don't think God runs the earth?
I think, I think it's like, he runs the heavens and stuff.
I mean, it's like, he runs everything or, and it's like,
but then he like, I think so he gives like,
he can give his children like earths for themselves
or like rules to themselves.
Cause he wants them to like do what they want to do.
But then he's like, he's like,
ah, I know how hard it's going to be for them.
It's like, you know, but that's cause he, you know,
we are, are
our parents and stuff like we are them as like we're a continuation of our ancestors and they get
chained we're like just taking up the baton like the olympics like we're running our little leg over
the little brace and then
I think that maybe we can reincarnate again in the future,
especially at our own bloodline.
If there's opportunities, but think about all the spirits
compared to all like the minimal amount of bodies
or stuff like, I don't know.
Well, that's interesting that you mentioned bloodline too,
because I was watching this video the other day
to where they were talking about,
what was it about?
It was about bloodlines pertaining to...
It wasn't reincarnation. It was something I was watching but um
Yeah, I do wonder like how much oh it had to do with that
Tartaria do you do you know much about the tartaria lost civilization or Tartarus or
Tartarian
What is it called?
Tartarus, but Tartarus there's like there's a kid like Tartarus is actually the name of hell in Greece and stuff like that
Tartarus, but also are you as so that's Russia and so if you go like to where they're saying it is there?
It's all over Russia
Russia's very known for doing psyopsis and a lot of fake news so just careful Dennis Russia, but
Yeah, so and what in the with the yeah, so anyway, there's like yeah
So
That was this like there's a lot of Russian styles right now
But they got Chernobyl. I don't believe I looked into no Chernobyl photos. There's like mermaid people. There's big foots
There's the fairies. I mean, I think I was like what I think that there are merpeople and I think that
We're like whoever's in charge of the world is aware of it
And I think that's why we haven't explored the oceans more. I think that there is something down there
in Zimbabwe they were like attacking the workers and stuff like that like they
said the roommates were like dragging people under
oh really? yeah everyone's in an African country and that's like that but they
ever have real mermaids and everyone quit the water treatment plant or whatever
it was because they kept being mermaids sitings and stuff because they
they're talking about them spiritually but I think I was watching this real
thing I mean there are people that have very strong beliefs even in voodoo and
like they have like
like Mama Wata, Mama Wata or something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, look, there's reality to all that.
But I think that there's Mer people.
I've always thought that I've never
liked the ocean very much because they're not going to get me.
But I think that there's something down there
that are somehow like humanoid fish or something.
Lantus, here, I think this is like a couple minutes of this, this is called
the mermaid problem in Zimbabwe, and uh, yeah, and it got right here. Okay, here you go.
It has been said that mermaids symbolize life and fertility within the ocean.
Many Zimbabwean indigens have had this traditional belief passed down from generation to generation.
However, they learned something else about mermaids one morning in the middle of 2000,
when one of the districts in Zimbabwe woke up to the news of two men drowning while trying
to chase or catch a mermaid.
Villagers in Mandurogezi district, a district of the province Meshonaland, western Zimbabwe,
woke up on the morning of June 2000 to the news that two men had drowned in a local
dam.
What was more shocking to the villagers was the cause of their death, which was drowning.
Though people had been reported to drown during the rainy seasons, it was surprising
the men drowned while trying to catch or chase a mermaid.
Mondoro-Guessi is a vast district that boasts scrubland, farmland, and sand veld stretching
from south of Harare, around Maniam River, to the Mizzouva's River, around 200 km away.
There was a dam, which was part of the agricultural infrastructure.
Former President Robert Mugabe's government built it in the mid-1990s.
The dam was constructed in an undiluted, shrub-filled flay in the rear course of the Niamakondo,
a river that started on a wetland some kilometers upstream.
Niamakondo swells into the Muppa River, which pours into the Senyati River, as an busy tributary.
Setting the dam at the boulder-strewn edges of the river was quite unusual.
Locals believe the coffees and their environment are the abode of spirits, mythical creatures, and ancestors.
It was even said that if one gets closer to the dam, one can hear the sound of the departed
ancestors' favorite music mysteriously playing from the rock cracks underneath it.
However, many people avoided coming close to the dam during the day, even though the
mermaids were not the initial inhabitants of the dam.
After the dam was constructed, many villagers claimed to have seen a whirlwind in the distance,
while walking on the earthen wall, holding the water.
It was always a towering and narrow whirlwind, moving towards the lake while attempting to
reach the lower stratosphere.
One of the villagers claimed that when she experienced this, she stopped to examine the
situation, looking at the approaching whirlwind.
She held her breath at first with interest.
However, her interest turned into increasing trepidation.
By then, the column of air had reached the middle of the dam, with a splash of water,
An older woman was doing her laundry when she saw the whole incident.
She sagely concluded that a mermaid had come to live in the dam.
Now, the dam in the district was like the other rivers, which didn't entirely set people
at ease.
Strange things started happening with mermaids.
The fantastical half-woman, half-fish creature thought to habituate the dam.
Sometimes in the morning, women would head to the dam to do their laundry, only to find
Another scenario occurred one day as dusk was approaching, a young man came home only
to discover that his mother had not prepared his favorite meal.
So balking on what he considered unappetizing fare, he collected his fishing rod and trotted
to the dam with his dog, running after its master.
He settled down on the rocks that jutted into the dam and began fishing, with his dog sitting
near and watching him.
Suddenly, his dog started barking, convulsed, and jumped into the dam.
The dog momentarily disappeared into the dam, and he could not see anything.
The young man jumped up in fright and fled, leaving the fish he had caught on the rocks
and never setting foot near the dam again.
According to the elders, it was a warning because mermaids are said to hate dogs.
There was also the incident of a power-hungry, fully-fledged cleric who led his congregants
on the wild mermaid chase early one morning, which led to the deaths of two people.
The incident happened at an ambiguous time, neither morning nor night, when the prophet
gathered his church members and led them in songs and prayers.
The cleric had his younger brother and another member with him that day.
He led them to the damn wall, holding shards of clay pots with red cloth tied to them since
it is believed that mermaids ate the red color.
His mission was to place the shards of clay pots with red cloth where the mermaid was
believed to live.
They met with the mermaid as they made their way to the damn wall.
At that moment, the prophet felt that his legs were weak.
But the mythical creature touched his legs, and the prophet regained his composure immediately.
Facing those behind him, the mermaid told them to leave because there was danger in
the place.
However, the prophet commanded his two followers to continue singing and praying.
About eight hours later, the village gathered around the dam by noon, with the news of the
men disappearing.
The villagers did all that they could, but the men were gone.
They even invited a woman who was reputed to have a mermaid spirit, but she couldn't
help them.
Divers were engaged, but came out of the dam, claiming no one was there.
Nothing could also be done when two secondary school students were discovered drowned on
February…
Some things in there. I mean, Africa, we don't really know a lot about Africa. I mean, I think it's known, but we're not told at least a lot about Africa.
And I think that's where there's a lot of creatures that we haven't been told about.
Africa is a huge continent. People don't realize that Africa is a lot larger.
than you think of it being.
It's pretty big.
Yeah, I think that, yeah, is it the largest continent?
I mean, it's got, so I remember I had to memorize
the countries and there's so many countries.
I was like, wow, like a lot to memorize.
It was like one of the hardest continents to,
I even know the 50 States by heart,
but Africa is like, wow, I would forget about it.
But,
And I did like I was around during like the South African stuff with a Mandela doing the election and stuff and
We had we had actually a exchange student for South Africa
So I used to have one of the ballots the voting ballots from the first election in South Africa
It was it was just full pictures. It was it was full pictures because they didn't have to be able to read to vote
And so they had everyone's picture on there and it's like he got like a landslide or whatever
But you know, it's pretty dangerous place to live though
and very racist. It's like the Dutch, it was colonized by the Dutch and stuff and had our part tied until like the, you know, the 90s.
So, yeah, now it's a lot different. We're there.
Well, it's not that that different I was looking at this video about trafficking and about this woman
Who was living in South?
Yeah, yeah, South Africa who sold her child and
The child being basically sought after because of the child's coloring that the child was a black child
But was very very fair and that does kind of link to the whole apartheid
Colorism that still does go on down there, but it's oh, it's I
I'm glad I don't live in Africa. You know as much as you know slavery was a bad thing
I would not want to be living in South Africa or a lot of countries. I mean if I lived in Africa today
My life would be completely different than it is right now. And I really like my life right now
So
Yeah, I mean we're like, I I'd have to be married probably to someone I hate
Oh
Why would you do that by what it's been? It's like, you know, unless they're like, you know, I'd have to I'd have to
Be an immigrant. I still would have escaped Africa somehow
I wouldn't be a living I would I would be somewhere. I wouldn't be there
Well, yeah, I mean it's like he had like a mean of Marcus Garvey tried to get everyone back there and stuff like that
He's like hey, let's go back and that's they didn't make they've been they made a to called
Liberia and it kind of was a disaster
Yes, I were when it's like nobody really wanted to go they're like well
I don't like the we didn't like the boat on the way out here
I don't know it's like it's so weird how like I've watched a lot of stuff about the theories about race and things like that
And the indigenous people of America who are the real indigenous where there really is real life all this kind of stuff
I mean, I've even seen like the black panther kind of like nation of Islam material about you know,
Jacob and the the big-headed scientist and
Yeah, I've watched that in like house how the different races supposedly were manufactured right
That's a very racist
way of thinking when you really think about it. I mean
They're like, well, the nurses would take a needle and they put it in the black baby's brain and the babies that were light skin
They'd let oh, I didn't even know about that part. Oh
Oh my god
It's really bad and then it's like then you're maybe they have like pictures of them like they did paintings
And it just looks like a guy with a big
That sack on his head. I mean it's like just this big like yes
And then they say there's all these people like all these different kinds of people like from this one island in Greece, okay, and then and then
Basically, then it has all this like that has them like kind of like the more
racial kind of stuff. But there's a guy named Wallace Fard.
I think it was Fard. Like Wallace Fard, but then his real name was Ford.
But he just changed it to Fard and it sounded kind of like Muslim.
And he started like the original nation of Islam.
And he was like this, he was actually biracial.
very light skin actually have some pictures. I don't know if you've ever noticed this but almost all
the like you know things that are supposed to be for the blacks and the african americans
if you look at who's at the top of the food chain it's always someone to where you look at them
It never is. That's why I think the whole thing is ridiculous. Really. Right. There's even people like, you know, like, like, uh,
Rachel Doisiel, remember that lady? And she was like that. Rachel Dolezal. Yes. Yes. We all know about Rachel.
But here's the question. Was her mom really white? Did you ever see the picture of the mom?
I mean, I said, I think I did.
I mean, it's like they kind of look like old, old white people to me.
But I mean, it's like, the mom, look, let me, let me find the picture.
Uh, the father definitely was white.
The mother, I think the mother was something, right?
And maybe she just didn't want it known.
You know, sometimes well, I mean, it's all mother.
I want you to, I want you to take a good look at the mom.
Let's see
I mean the Rachel definitely did do you know she did do like a straw set on her hair to make herself look more
Ethnic right
Okay, I found I found the mom I found the picture of the parents
Because when I look at that mom of hers the mom
I mean, it could just be the lighting.
I mean, I want your opinion
because it's probably just my perception.
It probably is, but I really look closely at people.
Okay, let me go over to here.
Upload the video, not video, the photo.
Okay, here it is.
That's her parents right there.
Okay, now the father, I would say, looks very angle of Saxon.
There would be no questioning in my mind, looking at the dad.
That's a white man.
The mom, I'm looking at her nose.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, it's so hard.
Like some people, it's hard to tell, you know?
It's like, you would never, or you would never know.
Like they have descendants of Sally Hemings that are white and black.
I mean, the mom, the mom definitely has fair, she has, she's not as fair as the dad.
The dad has more of a pink undertone.
The mom, she looks a little, um, almost like a Mediterranean person's coloring.
She does have the light hair, but.
If I had to guess the ancestry of the mom, I would guess maybe Sicilian the way her mouth is, her face shape, she looks Italian-ish.
Does the mom have black in her? Maybe she does, but she lives her life as a white woman and maybe she's not, she wasn't willing to ever acknowledge it.
I mean, it looks like a white, I mean, I just, I always, as soon as I saw the parents, when
I looked at the mom, I thought that mom looks like she might have something in her.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's thinking, you know, and sometimes moms do, like usually like,
you know, the, the background is not as important too.
The the I mean Rachel if Rachel was weight was raised as a white girl
She should not have tried to become the leader of the Washington in double ACP
She shouldn't have done that but I I always when that story came out I
Just thought to myself there is no way
I gotta take a look at her parents and when I saw the parents, I don't think that her mom is white. I think the mom is something else
Well, yeah, I think the mom is white tish. I mean, obviously the mom has white in her
But I just think that there's something else
Very possible. I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean you never know. I mean and everyone's mixed with everything nowadays
I mean, it's like there's so many mixed in with us. But I mean, it's like really at this point
We should just say we're human race and
race really is. No, because people have to have some reason to have to feel like they're a part of
something. Right, but it's like that's expensive in another group. I mean, plus white people are
like really like the group people are allowed to talk about because it's like any other group
I mean, people are, I mean, it just, I guess it depends on how you look at the world, but
you don't think people, I mean, people do let the racism happen.
Right, so you can talk about other it just depends on like where in the world
Do you want to live and what group you want to be around a sports team?
It's like everyone likes to think that there's the best and stuff like that in reality
They know they're not gonna win every single game and they think they're not I mean it's a and but right
But it's like still they're she was gonna tear in there. I mean people need to have like a little bit of
Self-confidence narcissism. I think it's a little bit useful like a little bit of it
Like I mean not in a lignet way, but I'm saying just to at least love yourself and like love who you who who we are
Because it's like we have to be with ourselves. So no matter what like, you know
Love yourself always like in the you know, and you can't change people can't change anybody else
We can always change ourselves and by changing ourselves. We do change the world
We change the quick but what would have been and re yeah, you can create new possibilities new timelines
Glitches in the matrix jump like jump some timelines and stuff, you know, you can
Sometimes you can get a second chance on some things
Yeah, you can you can't well, let me ask you if you could have a second chance in any
Point in your life, what would you change or what would you say that point would be if any maybe nothing?
Well, I mean a second chance. I mean it's like I would like maybe if I was like if I had my shit together
I wouldn't like mind like actually going to where I used to work
And I was just like the office manager or whatever and I'd like to like actually do sales
And like see if I would have been able to like be successful and like, you know
Doing that because I would have made a lot more money and I mean I could have changed this trajectory
But I think on the other hand, it's like I'm if like what if we had done anything different in our lives
We would not be who we are now would be a different person
a set of things that happen in everything because every moment in our life we're like we all we all we have is the now
Everything else is a memory or like a or like, you know pulling our brain in either direction
That's not right right now
But all we all experience is the now and so it's like this is like the magical time anytime we're like right in the present
That's like that means oh right now I can do it and it's like a lot of times
We're just like watch ourselves like a memory
or just sitting as a passenger on our own body,
letting other forces run at it and stuff.
Well, which can be my problem a little bit
because I'm such an open mind.
Like I'm so empathic that it's like,
almost like I'm just so very receptive.
And so my brain's always like,
like, you know, it's like,
and so I have like a lot of like other people's thoughts
and emotions and stuff coming into my head.
Which is like me. It's very interesting, but it's also very a little bit difficult socially to
to handle sometimes, you know
so
Yeah, I'm very sensitive. I'm very sensitive, but um
Also, especially the negative energy i'm sensitive to and it's like because I want to but
To know like the positive you need to know the negative. That's the thing. There's always two sides of the coin
You do well or maybe it not even so much the negative
But just like the complete picture right and sometimes like what you think is positive at first
Isn't oh my god
Negative might not be negative right
It's because think of all the time is like, you know, you're like, oh my god
And it's like and you thought I would you wanted something but then he turns out you didn't really want it. It's like you just exactly
Yes, yes, yes, you think oh, it's a good thing. I didn't get that
Avoid it problems rejection
Protection sometimes right it is it is you know, you should make a song about that rejection
Might be protection
You could say it could be God's protection, but if you want to be non denomination, all you could say at times rejection is protection, right?
It's like yeah, I like I love like you know looking at things like in abstract ways like you know
So people can say God or they can say the source or they can say spirit or they can say all it is or they can say
I mean, it's like basically everything is everything and so it's like
That's it's like the but there's there's there's unity in the spiritual world like that. There's not here. There's
duality here so that's why everything's in a billion pieces and there's a million people
but it like really we are all one like in like the spirit like we're all it's like we're all just
like in uh you can't tell the difference between one or another we're just like light and stuff
like that but in but in our world it's like it's useful to be able to put in these meat suits and
like to to have experiences and to actually go through pain and to go through pleasure and go through
like emotions and go through love and it's like I can tell why like if we were angels at one point
we decided to come here because it's like a really good place to come to.
Grow this is good to work through your shit because everyone's there's a lot. Yeah, there's a lot of like interesting people here, too
Like I think that nobody's figured out anybody because it's like our minds are so complicated. There's so much
Cycles and just like cameras and ancestral things. We're all living out still and it's like we have to find out
Where we put it was our voice and where it's like the re are we reacting to something that happened a million years ago like
I'm just rambling because I got high because I got high I got these to really go cool bitch
Well, good good good on you. I'm back to coffee. I had some
THC beverages over the weekend
But I'm on coffee day today. Okay. I fixed my little animation. It's a little bit of a higher quality. Let's let's
Show it to you. Oh
Yeah, people are going to come to your stream like who are those people? Who's that?
Okay, where did it go? Where's the new one?
Okay, Tim. This is a KFC buffet in your area. I don't know KFC is a buffet.
See, I guess this one.
Okay, here we go. Oh, I have to delete some of the videos. I guess I am, let's see, remove,
remove,
remove.
Okay, let's try again.
Okay, there it is.
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, it's a little bit more dark.
I like that. I mean, it's like, I mean, there's, um,
susutographia of Adam and Eve.
Like, they're kind of told hundreds of years after
of, like, what, like, all these stories about the garden
and, like, they go into this cave and they keep,
they keep accidentally killing themselves
or on purpose killing themselves,
and God keeps bringing them back to life
and they're like, what the hell?
And then, then, um, the devil starts to trick them,
They can't tell the difference between God and the devil because it's like, because it's so hard and it's like, God can't, God's like, oh my God, he's raising them up on Mary's Day. Oh my God.
It's kind of funny. There's also Mark Twain actually did an Adam and Eve story too, and it's really satirical one. It's worth reading. It's a Mark Twain, something called Adam and Eve. It's illustrated actually. It's kind of interesting.
Oh, I didn't know that.
You can go to like an archive. There's like all these books. Like I used to just I've definitely so many books that like
Like old uh, there's actually like really crazy art. Um, here's the guy that William William
He did like uh
He did these wood sketchings. I can show you like one of the wood sketchings. This is called. Um, you see, um
Okay, um, let's see
Okay. Yeah, this is called. Well, this is from something called
I'll run about yeah, so there's one okay. He's been the one famous one, but I'll go okay
So his name is William Hogarth, okay, and I'll show you some of his art and this is like
Crazy one of your artists
You'll see the deep the detail in this
Stuff you see okay, so that was his famous one
Live area of like mall Flanders. I guess he did like the original mall
mall Flanders movie. Okay, so it says
Here's something called
Wow, okay
Collection so this is in the Royal Collection and
I'm not gonna look at that one.
I'm gonna look at, there's like,
or some of them were more morality plays
and stuff like that, but, and he would do the,
all these were done by like, by these woodcuts.
And I just remember like, there was,
I'm gonna show you a bit.
And they had, they told stories and stuff.
Also, I'll see if I can find a short little thing about it.
Let me see.
This one is, I'm gonna find like three or four minutes.
Okay, so this is look at this one. Here's one. This is called genuinely fierce and Bear Street. Okay, so here is the
share screen
Okay, this is there. I
Don't see it on the screen
Hello, I think his computer cut out. He'll be back. I'm sorry. He's it's okay
But it's like
Yeah, it's pretty amazing. I can't bring that up. I'll just bring a picture of them a big picture of it
He does these really actually he has a pug in these pictures. He was like
1697 to 1764
and
He he did these woodcuts. Let me see and then oh, yeah, so here's I'll just share his art right here
Here's the page share screen. Okay
We got it
Okay, and then I should be able to put it up right here.
Oh, it's not coming up.
Well, at this stage, at this stage.
Oh, I can try this.
Stop screen.
Okay.
Is there any of my, do I put anything up there?
I don't know why it's not, because of the room.
Let's see.
I can put it right here.
Okay, let me try one.
This is called, it's kind of hard to see.
Oh my god. Yeah, it's like I guess it's too hard to see. I wish I could play the video, but it's like not looking
But I hear here
Here's someone who's hugged. I hope I can play this
KFC had a buffet. I don't believe the KFC ever had a buffet. That's a lie. Okay, you might needs it. Oh, there it is. Oh
No, I now now we're just looking at
Teala tequila and gamble
His humor is evident in these paintings. This is before and then the next one is entitled.
Don't you just love the fact that British artist William Hogarth chose to do a self-portrait with
his dog? But I can't tell you the name of the dog. You'll have to look that up yourself.
The painter William Hogarth was a moralist through and through. He held a mirror up to 18th century
society. I consider him the father of English caricature.
His social satire in his paintings is biting and humorous.
His humor is evident in these paintings.
This is before, and then the next one is entitled after.
His paintings often address the political corruption of the day,
the luxury of the rich,
and often the depraved morals of the wealthier society.
He depicted all classes,
like this painting called The Shrimp Girl.
He was also an outstanding engraver and printmaker.
His prints were so popular and widely distributed,
and some engravers were ripping them off
without giving him credit.
Oh, I'm great!
Oh, I bet, I bet they were.
And in 1735, they passed legislation
that would protect copyright.
It is still on the books
and is still known as Hogarth's Act.
Hogarth wanted to help people. He was a patron of a family hospital for orphans and he persuaded many
of his artist friends to donate pieces to the orphanage. Patrons would come and leave donations.
One of my favorite Hogarth paintings is this one. It's a series of portraits of the servants who
worked within his home. I associate most of his paintings with satire, but this one really has
One of his more popular series of paintings was called Marriage a la Mode.
Each scene tells the story of an arranged marriage.
In the opening scene, we see the families gathered together to make the arrangement.
This gentleman holds a family tree attached to a knight,
hitting of nobility. The men are quarreling over the details,
while the poor bride is crying, while being whispered in her ear by someone named Wormtongue.
The group seems disinterested as he pulls out a pinch of snuff.
Dogs are typically symbolic of faithfulness, and they're looking the other way.
In the second painting, entitled Tet a Tet, we see an interior scene with the couple,
and a very frustrated servant. The room is in disarray, the chair is knocked over.
The groom seems like he may have partied a little bit too much. The clock overhead
shows that it's either midnight or noon the next day, while his dog is sniffing at
something in his pocket, which happens to be a lady's hat, but probably not his wife's.
The bride-to-be seems contented, she's stretching herself, she looks happy, and she holds a mirror over her head.
While there's something on the ground beside of her, playing cards, and a gentleman in a far-off room who seems to be yawning, who was she playing cards with?
while the servant seems endlessly frustrated.
Hogarth held a mirror up to society.
He hoped that people would look at his paintings as moral tales.
Maybe they would gain insight and even change their lives.
And that's why I think he's an artist you should know.
Thank you for the likes and follows and most of all the kind words.
I like the artist.
I'm happy to learn about that artist.
Imagine if he'd had access to the AI.
Right, I mean, but it's like, you know, if you look at the scale of this some of this this art like I mean
I can't try to find like something closer because it's like, you know, it just it's like you can't really see that it's like
carved in the wood
So, I mean, but if you look at how like detail this is and how much how painstaking this meant especially who is etching this
I say it's just amazing how he did it. I don't know if you look at this detail like here's
Let me see here's one
there's one called a rake's progress a rake is okay so there's a British guy
that came on my show yesterday or the other day and he was like oh so what
kind of gay guy are you and I was like what kind of gay guy because we were
talking about like you know bears and twinks and stuff like that what kind of
question is that what
really what kind of gay guy are you so I didn't okay so there's established
categories now I said I said I don't know I don't know I don't know I'd be
consider as like I'm not really like I'm sexually active or like in part of a
community and he's oh so so would you call yourself a Trump and as like a
what a trap like I was like a Trump and he's like no no no it's Trump like a
And I was like, is that like a homeless person?
He's like, well, yeah, because you look like you're homeless.
You look with that wispy hair you have or something like that.
And I was like, excuse me.
And then he started coming up on every single screen.
And I was like, what are you doing?
And then he's like.
And he just was being really weird.
And then I kept kicking him out and he wouldn't leave.
He would just like sit there and sit.
And no matter how many times I banned him,
he would just appear.
It was so weird.
It was like creepy.
I didn't like it.
So, I mean, that was comfortable a little bit.
But-
Well, see, you're willing to talk.
See, you're braver than me because the way your show is
anyone can join. So you get to meet all kinds of people. I'm not willing to meet all kinds of people.
I'm scared. I haven't done that before. But you know, so you'll attract positive and negative.
What is this one? This one says, so this is part of a rake's progress. It says it says a caption a rake's progress
1735 a plate Tom Raikwell is confined to fleet prison
London for debt and being harangued by his wife on the table next to him is a manuscript for a play
He has written and try to make some money and a rejection letter to the left of the room
A sary young has fainted with in a woman with smelling salts tries to revive her fourth and final state of the plate
William Hogarth, and so that's
What that that's the smallest novel of that but it's it's hard to see it's like you can't even see like the beautiful detail because it's like so
crazily like beautifully detailed that it's like insane, but maybe I can find like
More thing about it, but I mean it's like because he's so interesting
And I think my dad shortly passed away told me that he had like this book of disguise art and I was like what and he's like
Yeah
He's like, yeah, and he's like, just go get it.
And I had, of course, something that's so easy to get,
but I would love to get that.
So I'm just looking for anything really short.
Yeah, this is called Gin and Lane on Bear Street.
Okay.
Or, oh, the Four Stages of Violence and Cruelty.
Let me see.
Well, it's a little, this is a little bit long, though.
You can see some of that.
We can watch a little bit of it.
It's crazy.
I can't read what it says, does it have, like, text?
I think I'm on the wrong page.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God.
Obviously, you couldn't see what it said.
Okay.
Here.
Oh, yeah, here.
I'll rewind a little bit, because this is like...
Yeah!
Yeah, this is probably good.
This is the details of the art, so here.
Yeah.
Okay.
Somebody had a super imagination to create that.
Four years after he completed industry and the idleness, Hogarth came out with yet another pictorial series.
This one shorter and darker than any he'd made before.
The Four Stages of Cruelty tells the story of a poor orphan named Tom Nero,
whose character is as black as his name.
Over the course of the series Four Plates, we watch as Tom proceeds
from torturing a dog.
to beating his horse, to murdering his mistress, all of which is rewarded in the final scene
with a fittingly cruel end. In the last lecture, we saw how industry and idleness
marked a shift in Hobarth's artistic practice, away from the sophistication and complexity of
With the stages of cruelty, Hogarth extended this shift even further.
Nero's story is told in a mere four plates, in a deliberately stripped-down visual style,
and he is by far the lowest of the artist's many fictional anti-heroes in both moral and social terms.
Yet paradoxically, it was the stages of cruelty that Hogarth would later cite as one of the works, if not the work,
that he was proudest to have made.
Writing a decade or so after the series publication,
he remarked that if cruelty has been prevented
by these four prints,
I had rather be maker of them than of the cartoons.
By the cartoons, Pogarth meant the seven full scale designs
for tapestries depicting scenes from the lives
of the apostles made by Raphael
for the Vatican's Sistine Chapel.
In Hogarth's time, these paintings, which hung at Hampton Court, were the most celebrated
and revered works of art in all of Britain.
Hogarth's comment was no doubt designed to provoke.
How could a series of prints, plainly etched by a contemporary British artist, and showing
the darkest side of human nature, possibly rival, let alone exceed, a group of biblical
So he was a socialist. He was making some points at that time.
For a commercial society like Britain's, Hogarth seems to be saying,
great paintings to be hung in grand churches were no longer really what was needed,
nor for that matter were they what people wanted.
Instead, this was to be found in modern commercial works,
like Hogarth's own modern moral progressives.
and in particular, in a work like the one we'll be examining here,
which takes square aim at the scourge of human cruelty
through images designed at once to instruct, deter, and delight.
Pretty good.
My name is Meredith Gamer, and I'm delighted to welcome you to the fourth in a series of six films devoted to William Hogarth.
produced as part of the Paul Mellon Center's
2021 Public Lecture Series program.
All have been made in collaboration cruelty,
a series of four prints that Hogarth designed,
engraved and published in the winter of 1751.
Let's start by taking a closer look at the prints themselves,
which, as we've come to expect
with Hogarth's moral subjects,
are packed full of narrative and incident.
The series opens with a scene at childhood mayhem.
On a clean-swept London street, a swarm of young boys are busy tormenting animals in a variety of impressively creative and fiendishly nasty ways.
At right, too blind a bird with a fire-hot needle. Another ties a bone to a hungry dog's tail.
Several mora are about to start a game of throwing a cox.
and still more grin and holler as two cats,
which they've strung up by their tails.
See, this is horrible.
This is horrible.
I'm not gonna look at these pictures,
but you have to look really closely
to even notice what some of these characters are doing.
A young boy dressed in rags, his face and shoe,
is shoving an arrow down the backside of a large dog.
Yeah, I'm not gonna look at these. Let's turn this off. Let's turn that away with tears in his eyes
Yeah, that was that was a little bit more I can't look at certain things
But you'd have to look really closely to even realize some of those
Occurrences are in that artwork
Yeah, I mean it's almost like a picture, but it's like yeah, it's like oh my gosh
Wow, the chat is gape- oh, I agree, okay, yeah, I don't know, I guess there's nurses in the chat about other stuff, but...
But yeah, I guess I was his worst the worst one, but yeah, you saw the worst of it. That was like, yeah
But it's like, you know, I mean there are like six like, you know, like lady bath like
Elizabeth Bathory, I don't know if you know about
I've seen that name forever. It seems to be someone who's up to mischief
consistently. Yeah, she was left alone in a castle and then she had this like lesbian witch come like
Theodora come and move in with her
and um and taught her like so. Oh I thought you meant the username. Oh okay I didn't know you
meant the real thing. There's a real accountants and in Transylvania actually and um and she had a
castle but her husband would be like out fighting war all the time and so
she had like a little dwarf named Fitzko that would like she would have him hide the bodies because she would like get serving girls and then like bait in their blood and stuff or have
other ways like just really disgusting like but she was eventually like just locked in her tower and then all her accomplices were like throwing the fires and stuff like that.
But she had the dwarf go and hide the bodies and so he got really bored with hiding all these hundreds of bodies.
So he just would leave them on the roads and stuff like that. So it's hard to become really obvious what was going on.
and um because
to bury a body if you're like a little door. I mean, it's like, I mean, it's like, I was just like,
throw it over like a, well, now people would just put it in the sewers and stuff, right?
Well, I don't know what people would do, like, you know, what scares me about life is that
the only criminals that we really know about are the ones who are caught, okay?
Which means that you have some super criminals out there who are getting away with all kinds
of stuff.
Right.
But the thing is, it also is really hard these days.
It's like, everyone has a big mouth,
and they're going for this credibility and stuff like that.
And so they're waiting to show off about something.
And then they're going to have people just waiting
for the opportunity to like, you know.
So it's like, I mean, it's like people just
need to hold their cards closer, I guess.
Because it's like, yeah, this world is like,
World it's like especially with like I mean just think there was like the stocci
Like this like the 80s and stuff like that and they there were a spy on everybody
But they didn't have like the spy stuff that we have today. They have computers
I mean they didn't have like this so we could like go so detailed into spy and they've even on them on
GitHub they have this like infrared
Wi-Fi body
Trade so your Wi-Fi can like apparently like find where your body is in your house and stuff
I mean, it's like and then they have it like just the open source for people to run if they want
I mean, it's like wow, I mean, it's like so people have done know a little bit of hacking
It's like but I think that it's like getting so cutthroat that it's like there's like
Rules are not being followed or something. I don't know. I just see like well the real question is who would even enforce the rules
Well, this may you know
Well, it's just that's like the it's like the first amendment people like the people that are out like, you know
Did you take the police and stuff like that? It's like whole people you're being us like we have like a
Society that we there things are brought a certain way innocence before guilty and like, you know
You can like pay for your crime with like it's like, you know my time in prison or whatever or in people can
repent and things like that, but it's like
There's so many people that become very moralistic that like Charles Manson was very moralistic for somebody that like you
Had like a bunch of hippies like kill his enemy and stuff. I mean, it's like, right. It's like he's like
You know, you know, I mean people are being straight up evil things and think that they're good
And it's like that's also in the Bible. It's like so in the end days people will say what's evil is good
and what's good is evil and
Now maybe they're just like two sides of the same coin or whatever
But it's like I think that they're more of like a choice that we have to make
Like to go towards the good or to go towards evil. What is what is good good is God and what is evil?
I mean has the word that like almost like devil evil. I don't know
Wait, does the word devil?
Well, the word devil almost does have the word evil in it. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and and God it's almost like the word good. I mean it's like and so it's like
God and devil is good and evil in Germany and German basically like golden evil
There's even like I was saying today that there was like some the name of like some I guess it's like some
Like Pokemon or something but the name of the guy's daughter is his devil and then it's like his name is Satan and then it's like
And then there's 666 on the license plate or whatever it was on this this cartoon. It's kids cartoon
There's such crazy stuff hidden everywhere
and it's like
A lot of it's bad, like a lot of it's bad just having to study Satanism as a teenager,
which is like basically the only time anybody should, is because that's the only time people
are feeling so stupid and edgy, and if I get to know everything, and it's like basically
the satanists today are like...
Have the mindset of teenagers and it's like also they like look at like people like animals
When you see people like say, oh, you know, they talk about like the low cows and stuff like that
Well, they're they're really dehumanizing people like that. It's like they really
Some people do think that their gods and other people are animals and I think that we need to get back to like
Human beings like we're all human beings. Well, we have a major disconnect right now and a lot of young people's minds between
What reality really like some people really don't think that internet or the internet is real life the internet is real life. Okay, it's real unless I'm dreaming right now the internet is real.
And a lot of young people that they have a disconnect from that they think that they're in person life is one thing. Whatever they do on the internet is different and that there's no overlap or crossover, whereas there is.
Right, but it's like how about like there's movies out there that are like violent movies, right?
So it's like is that so when you watch a violent movie is that you committing a murder or is that just like some kind of like the thing is with the Internet?
What you're doing, I mean unless you have a designated character that you are playing in a designated
fictitional world to where nothing is
Actually affecting anything at all in anyone's personal life, right?
then it is real life if all those things are not applicable.
Like okay, for example, there's some people who might be sending you what like what the
Boxes of cement some people might be sending you the boxes of cement thinking that it's not real, but it is real
You're actually receiving boxes of cement or I'm sorry bags of cement, right?
Okay, so that's real. That's not fictitious, right? I mean that's going real life
I mean so we're real people on the internet, too
But it's like it's I'm just saying that it's like there's activity on the internet like it's like and of course it you can do this
like the illegal activity on the internet like you know and
and uh
You know, I mean there's tons of
I know a guy used to be able to print credit cards
and it's like, you know, I don't know whose credit cards
they were, but they printed it out.
But it's like, they just sell all this stuff
on the dark web basically, right?
And, you know, a lot of it's rip off
and a lot of lessons and stuff.
Not crime is like, crime doesn't pay, first of all,
because I think that even if it does,
like you're not gonna appreciate,
it's not like earning it fair, right?
Even like criminals don't have respect
for other criminals.
When they see like somebody that has a legitimate job,
like doing criminal stuff,
they'll usually look down on them like,
But like what like oh you're not a very you're not doing your job very well
He's like they're like they're like we're professional criminals
But you're like having this other job and pretending to be or trying to be I don't know it's like you know, it's like
I think the greed is like a big problem in this world
because people are just so easily seduced
by like glittery things or sneakers
and designer clothes that have like the fucking label
on them that nobody would ever wear.
And yes, Jamie, I did make the angel song.
I just haven't put it out yet.
I did make it.
Oh, good.
Yeah, you're right. You're you're well. I've been busy quietly with my AI stuff psyche
I've been making stuff, but I've been quiet about it
Well, I I mean I've been like, you know, of course I'm like really loud
But I'm like I've been making a series and then it's like and then I get into like wanting to
I go over my my birthday and
You know, it's like or like my astrology basically with that and I put like the information into songs and everything's very
Committee that creates like the mythology to because it's like there's there's things that I mean
It's like where the AI and and then where the human begins is like now like so it's like it's like
It's very well balanced to that's why I say there's a line in my song
It's like half man half half machine or six million dollar man or whatever like I don't I don't know. I
I do have like
You know, you're able you're able to like put
Some you're able to develop parts of your brain. You weren't able to develop before you and you can like do that intentionally
You can design a like basically it's like you have to figure out what you want how to ask for it
and how to like follow through with it
because it's like you can do anything you want.
Basically-
Well, you're right.
How to ask for it, how to ask for it.
That's a good way to, that's a good point.
People don't know how to ask for what they want very often.
And then they wonder why they're not getting what they want.
Yeah, because you have you do have to like, you know take steps towards whatever you want
It's like it's like things are sometimes things will just fall on people's laps, you know
And I've had that happen before where it's like, you know, I can sit and just attract things
But sometimes you have to do a little work too like where it's like you go
You can it's like things are left for you like and you can meet
Got it. You know what's weird? I watched it blogger the other night and he went and he's he found a $20 bill
He's like is that money on the ground?
He's walking around in the middle of the night or something like that giving drinks
He said he found a $20 bill and he's like oh he's like and I found a 10 yesterday
That's some lady dropped which is coming out of the store and I found a dollar that he before and he's like
And so this I mean it's like yeah, you can like find what you're looking for too
It's like so if you're looking constantly on the look up first for that color
Wow, you'll get really busy in like in like a park or something like that
But yeah, you can usually find usually about you know, you know manifest some some money
And if it doesn't come that way it will come some other way
It'd be I've had it happen a million times. It's like where yeah, I think that that's where it's like
Is it an energy that will come back especially if you spend a lot it like it does come back fast
But it's just like it's like a I think it's more of a fire and air element where it can gun it is
Like it just burns really fast right? It's like you gotta so that enjoy it. Well, we enjoy what we have it because
We can't take it with us nor anything we buy or anything here. It's like and everything here is basically like
temporary
It's nice to enjoy at the moment. It's about the experience not the end result because the end is not usually like great
But it's a journey and stuff, right? It's like I turn gamble into a snake. Would you like to see it? See that?
Okay, I'm a snake now. I'm a snake. I
Don't know his voice that well. Is it right? Um, no, it's just a still picture. Okay. Is it up yet?
Yeah, it's up. It's next to it. I don't I don't know what it looks like on your end. Oh, there we go
It's like, but the movie, oh, like Robin had the animated one with the fox and there's like the King Caw, the snake.
Oh, you're right. It does look a little like that. Huh. Okay. Yeah.
You're just kind of like a lion, too. Like a little bit of like a, like an animal or a dog face, too, in there.
You can see like a little bit of a cane. A little. Yeah. Or dragon, dragon, dragon almost, too.
The dragons and the serpents and like dinosaurs are they all the same thing? I don't know
I don't think that they're all the same thing that they could be maybe
But I think they're different. Well, yeah
I mean, do you think some are like on the astral plane?
You think they're like I believe that the astral plane is just as real as the physical plane because it's a plane of
Imagination, so it's like so even more real because this is like kind of big schools kind of like a copy or a hologram of like the real thing
which is like kind of like the Adam and Eve thing they fell out of like the Garden of Eden which is
maybe like the Sun and they fall to the earth so it's like on the earth you have to like reproduce
and like stuff and it's not just like eternal like the fire and the sun right I don't know
I just I ramble about I just I love it I study I study a lot of stuff and it's like I make a
lot of connections and like I'd love to share it with people
Find a little very interesting but a little bit a little bit a little bit hard to a little bit like I wish there was like more
Which is a little bit easier because there's a lot to get right at the same time that it's like
I'm like not that great at focusing on like one thing. That's why I'm very scattered
And so it's like I don't follow every of my shit together to like just be kept exactly what I want
But then again, we don't know what we want, right? It's like sometimes I don't think you know what you want
I don't think that's okay. I don't think so either. I just like I'm just like what what is it like?
It's like whatever life has in the store for me. I embrace like
like
Um, because it's like it's a magical experience to me and that I've like I've actually like manifested to this point and you know
I actually have a say in it like and
That's a beautiful thing, you know, I'm
Still not bad even if I'm kind of a bad shape. I'm still not bad shape compared like it's like I'm pretty
Well, why do you think you're in bad shape because you're not in bad shape, right? Well, it's like I just like I'm just like
I'm still chasing my dreams, you know, and it's like not like living the traditional thing and you know
Ultimate like you don't have to say if it's a secret dream, but like we're okay here. Where do you see?
ideally
Your life three years from now
I mean, it's like I'd like to like just have like upgraded a little bit
I've had like I'd like to have had success in something like like a big success in something
maybe like be able to buy my own car or like
You know or just be like really successful on YouTube and and be able to like, you know
Parlay that and other things and grow business or something like something I would love like my
Website to grow and me to be doing people websites for other people and me to like okay
You want to be making websites for people. I didn't know that so you need to you could do that now, right?
I mean, it's like, you know, and it's like, like a lot of people, like, I mean, I can also, you know,
I can like, you know, use AI to figure out all the businesses, certain business that have websites that are subpar,
that are in like the 10 mile radius, and I can do research, I can have it do research on all those people and send them personalized letters.
And I can, and it's like, and most of them don't want to do their own stuff.
You know, it's always like, and I can have a good price and I can be like, you know, I have good referrals and.
I just want to get more experience right now doing my own apps.
And then it's like, let's have a good portfolio.
I already have this.
I'm so proud of the website that it's crazy.
It's like, I didn't even know I'd be capable of such a thing.
And Mr. Big Pipes came in the other night.
He was like, I was like doing a little presentation, like a slideshow
of that kind of explaining.
Well, he would be jealous of you at this point.
Just so you know, he was, he was, oh, this is, he goes, that's so bad.
He's like, that's, um, it's like, he just, he just tell Claude code
or Claude what to do.
And I was like.
He can shut up because, well, see, Mr. Bitpipes is interesting.
He actually did achieve a dream of his and I watched him do it.
He wanted to get to the point of being able to play live music in venues.
And he did do that.
OK, but then he kind of stopped.
So he would be watching what you're doing at this point,
because if he's joining your panel, that means that he's really watching you
just so that you know, that's how he is. Yeah.
So he's watching you starting to manifest stuff, but he would try to discourage you
So never listen to him. That's what I'm telling you never listen to mr. Big pipes
Right and a lot of people will discourage and it's like, you know, it's like, you know, I could like, you know
Like with it, you know, I think they just like think that it's like, oh, it's just like you kind of like demean somebody by like putting down that they use AI or something like that and their work or whatever.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's like, I really don't feel the mean because I don't think there's anything wrong with it. And it's actually I have, I have support, I support it and I think everybody should could use it in a certain way like utilize it for creativity for brainstorming for.
Manifesting things fast. It's like I mean, but people are just like making it such like a
bad a word and stuff like that so but at the same time I want like people to like strive well
I'm gonna take it into a bad word because maybe I can hold my competition back by by constantly
berating them be like oh it's AI what's that that's stupid and they're using it yeah everyone is
I know and it's like it's just like I don't know. There's shaming like that's like the worst than bad shaming is a shaming
It's like oh my god. Yeah, it is shaming. You're right. It is
Is it instrument like it has a keyboard to it
I mean, it's like so as you know, it's like you can like it is like you do have to like have like
some kind of dexterity and coordination and an eye and a discernment and say the right
thing then bring up what you want. I mean it's like it wouldn't it's not it's not something
that manifesting itself unless people just have like a really you know they have it all set up
to live just uh just being a loop and reproducing and stuff like that in a loop um but most people
are gonna like I can see how I've improved with it like so much it's like it's like basically like a
and I've learned better ways to do things just like people like learn how to like little tricks
with the guitar and the you know music and stuff and how to read music better and you know how to
play and like you know make make people be like wow how'd you do that like it's like almost like
magic in a certain way like how
If I would have had this all my life, oh my God,
like I would have, so many things would be different, right?
I mean, that's like, I would have like, not be.
Well, things are going to be very different very soon
because of the, I mean, not just the things
that AI can do to help us, but the art, creating,
you know, helping to speed up the...
just the invention process, the creative process.
So I think the world soon is going,
I think it's gonna be perspective.
I think that if you're somebody who thinks optimistically
and you're doing good stuff,
the world's gonna be good for you.
If you're somebody who is negative and depressed and,
you know.
just bad, the world's gonna be bad for you.
That's what I think.
Right, and yeah, you kind of get what you give
and the world can be a perfect mirror
to how what you're putting out there.
So it's like, you know, even how I was saying to dad,
it's like, no matter what's bad in my life,
it's like, ultimately it's my life.
And it's my fault.
It's not anybody else's fault.
All these people are really just teachers
of teaching me my own.
My own weakness is my own insecurities my own triggers and it's like so I should actually be thanking mostly people that like you know
The hating them but you know, but I try to think you know
I try to like I try to like you know put things to the positive at the end of it
I know like there are some like pretty terrible people that I do not wish the best for and I'll say terrible things to you
But at the end of the day, I really don't hate anybody
But you know, it's okay, but it's okay too because hate is another form of love in a certain way
Yeah, it's like expending a lot of emotion on somebody that's this is like ourself
And then it's like on somebody well, that's why you shouldn't bother hating anybody because it is giving them
The basically the equivalent of energy as you would put toward really loving somebody
So I would say if you just don't bother. That's what I've had to work on and learn on
and just learn, you know, don't
Bother so much unless you're planning on like I try to shift or
Transmute my hate into something creative every time it sometimes it works sometimes
Sometimes it's called like I mean in Buddhism. There's all these rat
There's like these pictures of the wrathful deities that the wrath is supposed to be like this
Like an actual positive form of wrath
Kind of like the wrath of like you know if you go running to the street when you're a kid
And then it's like your mom like grabs from the street and yells at you and like has this like she's in she said take like
You know, it's horrifying like scary acting scary and screaming, but it's like it's like in order in order to like
Put you on the right path and to make sure you don't hurt yourself and stuff like that, right? So yeah, there's um, it's called
It's like some kind of wrath. It's like holy wrath or something like that
But it's a kind of like but it's a good version of wrath. It's like not like a evil wrath
It's like they all the all the nature spirits work were
Were kind of subverted and like, you know put in bondage and they had to kind of said kind of promised
So work for Buddhism and then and take their evil and put it towards protecting the Dharma or whatever
And so Padmasambhava supposedly converted all these nature spirits onto the side of Buddhism in Tibet and
Because they were all a place of these
If you see those Tibetan Buddhism, they have a lot of the wrathful deities and they're also peaceful
So there's peaceful and wrathful, but there's the same deity that will have both a peaceful and wrathful side just like
Hmm is two natures we do and it's like part of it isn't we can be a part demon
We can be part of an angel
But it was like mainly we were we have the better both best of both world because we can decide
We're not just like forced to do good or forced to do evil kind of like the
Angels and demons are they have to do what?
Devil's those are kind of slaves to like the higher power
We're like we can actually like decide on our own like what to do all right
I made a higher resolution
Edition of the snake character, okay, and I put him in the garden of Eden